[Script Info]
Title:Chu2 Koi BD 01 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00BB7E10,&H64F3A922,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPlrcJPN,DFGBrushRD-W7,16,&H006C1CDD,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H96000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,4,0,7,10,10,2,1
Style: OPlrcJPN2,DFGBrushRD-W7,16,&HFF6C1CDD,&H000000FF,&H00B480E2,&H96000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,6,0,7,10,10,2,1
Style: OPlrcCHN,华康方圆体W7(P),16,&H006C1CDD,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H96000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,4,0,3,10,10,2,1
Style: OPlrcCHN2,华康方圆体W7(P),16,&HFF6C1CDD,&H000000FF,&H00B480E2,&H96000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,6,0,3,10,10,2,1
Style: aaa,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: bbb,方正兰亭中粗黑_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Title,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,3,2,10,10,10,1
Style: EDlrcJPN,DFGBrushRD-W7,16,&H006C1CDD,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H96000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,3,3,9,10,10,10,1
Style: EDlrcCHN,华康方圆体W7(P),16,&H006C1CDD,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H96000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,3,1,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Title-----
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.92,0:04:43.93,Title,,0,0,0,,{\fad(2000,500)\pos(527,65)}邂逅的…邪王真眼
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----SP-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.98,0:00:39.31,aaa,,0,0,0,,{\p1\fscx128\fscy132\fad(0,1500)\pos(153,311)\blur1.5}m -42 -14 l -42 14 l 42 14 l 42 -14 l 40 -14 l 40 12 l -40 12 l -40 -12 l 40 -12 l 40 -14 l -42 -14  {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.98,0:00:39.31,bbb,,0,0,0,,{\pos(100,289)\fs26\fad(0,1500)\blur1.5\fsp1}影像资料
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPlrcJPN-----
Comment: 0,0:02:13.48,0:02:13.48,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 1,0:02:27.53,0:02:31.57,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}しばらく見つめ合ってから
Dialogue: 1,0:02:31.70,0:02:35.24,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}逸らすまでに　なにを考えてたの？
Dialogue: 1,0:02:37.16,0:02:38.20,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}…気になる
Dialogue: 1,0:02:38.54,0:02:42.58,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}唇尖らせた私を見て
Dialogue: 1,0:02:42.71,0:02:46.09,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}「どうしたの」って聞いてくるの
Dialogue: 1,0:02:46.13,0:02:48.17,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}待ってみるの
Dialogue: 1,0:02:48.38,0:02:53.93,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}誤摩化したあとの独り言は
Dialogue: 1,0:02:54.09,0:02:56.60,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}恥ずかしいから
Dialogue: 1,0:02:56.85,0:02:59.77,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}聞かないでくれる？
Dialogue: 1,0:03:00.35,0:03:02.94,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}後に引けないほど
Dialogue: 1,0:03:03.06,0:03:05.27,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}惹かれ合う恋
Dialogue: 1,0:03:05.48,0:03:10.03,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}もう始まってた
Dialogue: 1,0:03:10.94,0:03:13.45,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}夢ならたくさんみた
Dialogue: 1,0:03:13.53,0:03:17.32,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}醒めたままでもまだ会いたい
Dialogue: 1,0:03:17.37,0:03:19.41,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}君がそうさせた
Dialogue: 1,0:03:19.45,0:03:21.83,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}恋は欲張りだね
Dialogue: 1,0:03:21.87,0:03:24.42,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}飛び跳ねそうな心の
Dialogue: 1,0:03:24.54,0:03:27.33,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}ゆくままにゆこうよ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:27.46,0:03:30.09,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}理想も妄想も現実も
Dialogue: 1,0:03:30.17,0:03:32.84,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}全て君を軸に回る
Dialogue: 1,0:03:32.92,0:03:38.35,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}新しい世界へ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPlrcJPN'-----
Dialogue: 1,0:02:31.57,0:02:31.72,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}しばらく見つめ合ってから
Dialogue: 1,0:02:35.24,0:02:35.39,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}逸らすまでに　なにを考えてたの？
Dialogue: 1,0:02:38.20,0:02:38.35,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}…気になる
Dialogue: 1,0:02:42.58,0:02:42.73,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}唇尖らせた私を見て
Dialogue: 1,0:02:46.09,0:02:46.24,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}「どうしたの」って聞いてくるの
Dialogue: 1,0:02:48.17,0:02:48.32,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}待ってみるの
Dialogue: 1,0:02:53.93,0:02:54.08,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}誤摩化したあとの独り言は
Dialogue: 1,0:02:56.60,0:02:56.75,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}恥ずかしいから
Dialogue: 1,0:02:59.77,0:02:59.92,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}聞かないでくれる？
Dialogue: 1,0:03:02.94,0:03:03.09,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}後に引けないほど
Dialogue: 1,0:03:05.27,0:03:05.42,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}惹かれ合う恋
Dialogue: 1,0:03:10.03,0:03:10.18,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}もう始まってた
Dialogue: 1,0:03:13.45,0:03:13.60,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}夢ならたくさんみた
Dialogue: 1,0:03:17.32,0:03:17.47,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}醒めたままでもまだ会いたい
Dialogue: 1,0:03:19.41,0:03:19.56,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}君がそうさせた
Dialogue: 1,0:03:21.83,0:03:21.98,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}恋は欲張りだね
Dialogue: 1,0:03:24.42,0:03:24.57,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}飛び跳ねそうな心の
Dialogue: 1,0:03:27.33,0:03:27.48,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}ゆくままにゆこうよ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:30.09,0:03:30.24,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}理想も妄想も現実も
Dialogue: 1,0:03:32.84,0:03:32.99,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}全て君を軸に回る
Dialogue: 1,0:03:38.35,0:03:38.50,OPlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}新しい世界へ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPlrcJPN2-----
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.53,0:02:31.57,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}しばらく見つめ合ってから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.70,0:02:35.24,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}逸らすまでに　なにを考えてたの？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.16,0:02:38.20,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}…気になる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.54,0:02:42.58,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}唇尖らせた私を見て
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.71,0:02:46.09,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}「どうしたの」って聞いてくるの
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.13,0:02:48.17,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}待ってみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.38,0:02:53.93,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}誤摩化したあとの独り言は
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.09,0:02:56.60,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}恥ずかしいから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.85,0:02:59.77,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}聞かないでくれる？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.35,0:03:02.94,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}後に引けないほど
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.06,0:03:05.27,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}惹かれ合う恋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.48,0:03:10.03,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}もう始まってた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.94,0:03:13.45,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}夢ならたくさんみた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.53,0:03:17.32,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}醒めたままでもまだ会いたい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.37,0:03:19.41,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}君がそうさせた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.45,0:03:21.83,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}恋は欲張りだね
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.87,0:03:24.42,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}飛び跳ねそうな心の
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.54,0:03:27.33,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}ゆくままにゆこうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.46,0:03:30.09,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}理想も妄想も現実も
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.17,0:03:32.84,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}全て君を軸に回る
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.92,0:03:38.35,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,0,640,20)}{\move(10,22,10,2,0,150)}新しい世界へ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPlrcJPN2'-----
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.57,0:02:31.72,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}しばらく見つめ合ってから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.24,0:02:35.39,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}逸らすまでに　なにを考えてたの？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.20,0:02:38.35,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}…気になる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.58,0:02:42.73,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}唇尖らせた私を見て
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.09,0:02:46.24,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}「どうしたの」って聞いてくるの
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.17,0:02:48.32,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}待ってみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.93,0:02:54.08,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}誤摩化したあとの独り言は
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.60,0:02:56.75,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}恥ずかしいから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.77,0:02:59.92,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}聞かないでくれる？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.94,0:03:03.09,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}後に引けないほど
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.27,0:03:05.42,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}惹かれ合う恋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.03,0:03:10.18,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}もう始まってた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.45,0:03:13.60,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}夢ならたくさんみた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.32,0:03:17.47,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}醒めたままでもまだ会いたい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.41,0:03:19.56,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}君がそうさせた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.83,0:03:21.98,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}恋は欲張りだね
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.42,0:03:24.57,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}飛び跳ねそうな心の
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.33,0:03:27.48,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}ゆくままにゆこうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.09,0:03:30.24,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}理想も妄想も現実も
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.84,0:03:32.99,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}全て君を軸に回る
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.35,0:03:38.50,OPlrcJPN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(10,2,10,-18)}新しい世界へ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.07,0:00:00.07,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPlrcCHN-----
Dialogue: 1,0:02:27.53,0:02:31.57,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}片刻间  四目相视
Dialogue: 1,0:02:31.70,0:02:35.24,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}转移视线之前  你在想些什么
Dialogue: 1,0:02:37.16,0:02:38.20,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}我很在意
Dialogue: 1,0:02:38.54,0:02:42.58,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}看到撅起嘴的我
Dialogue: 1,0:02:42.71,0:02:46.09,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}你会问我「怎么了」吗？
Dialogue: 1,0:02:46.13,0:02:48.17,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}亦或静静等待？
Dialogue: 1,0:02:48.38,0:02:53.93,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}蒙混过后的自言自语
Dialogue: 1,0:02:54.09,0:02:56.60,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}实在太害羞了
Dialogue: 1,0:02:56.85,0:02:59.77,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}能别偷听吗？
Dialogue: 1,0:03:00.35,0:03:02.94,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}已经没有退路
Dialogue: 1,0:03:03.06,0:03:05.27,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}这份两情相悦的恋情
Dialogue: 1,0:03:05.48,0:03:10.03,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}悄然拉开帷幕
Dialogue: 1,0:03:10.94,0:03:13.45,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}做过无数次美梦
Dialogue: 1,0:03:13.53,0:03:17.32,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}醒后还想再次沉醉其中
Dialogue: 1,0:03:17.37,0:03:19.41,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}这一切都拜你所赐
Dialogue: 1,0:03:19.45,0:03:21.83,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}贪婪是恋爱的本质
Dialogue: 1,0:03:21.87,0:03:24.42,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}解放渴求自由的心灵
Dialogue: 1,0:03:24.54,0:03:27.33,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}做一回真正的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:03:27.46,0:03:30.09,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}理想、妄想和现实
Dialogue: 1,0:03:30.17,0:03:32.84,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}都伴随在你左右
Dialogue: 1,0:03:32.92,0:03:38.35,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}共步崭新的世界
Comment: 0,0:00:00.07,0:00:00.07,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPlrcCHN'-----
Dialogue: 1,0:02:31.57,0:02:31.72,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}片刻间  四目相视
Dialogue: 1,0:02:35.24,0:02:35.39,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}转移视线之前  你在想些什么
Dialogue: 1,0:02:38.20,0:02:38.35,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}我很在意
Dialogue: 1,0:02:42.58,0:02:42.73,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}看到撅起嘴的我
Dialogue: 1,0:02:46.09,0:02:46.24,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}你会问我「怎么了」吗？
Dialogue: 1,0:02:48.17,0:02:48.32,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}亦或静静等待？
Dialogue: 1,0:02:53.93,0:02:54.08,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}蒙混过后的自言自语
Dialogue: 1,0:02:56.60,0:02:56.75,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}实在太害羞了
Dialogue: 1,0:02:59.77,0:02:59.92,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}能别偷听吗？
Dialogue: 1,0:03:02.94,0:03:03.09,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}已经没有退路
Dialogue: 1,0:03:05.27,0:03:05.42,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}这份两情相悦的恋情
Dialogue: 1,0:03:10.03,0:03:10.18,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}悄然拉开帷幕
Dialogue: 1,0:03:13.45,0:03:13.60,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}做过无数次美梦
Dialogue: 1,0:03:17.32,0:03:17.47,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}醒后还想再次沉醉其中
Dialogue: 1,0:03:19.41,0:03:19.56,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}这一切都拜你所赐
Dialogue: 1,0:03:21.83,0:03:21.98,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}贪婪是恋爱的本质
Dialogue: 1,0:03:24.42,0:03:24.57,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}解放渴求自由的心灵
Dialogue: 1,0:03:27.33,0:03:27.48,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}做一回真正的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:03:30.09,0:03:30.24,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}理想、妄想和现实
Dialogue: 1,0:03:32.84,0:03:32.99,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}都伴随在你左右
Dialogue: 1,0:03:38.35,0:03:38.50,OPlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}共步崭新的世界
Comment: 0,0:00:00.07,0:00:00.07,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPlrcCHN2-----
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.53,0:02:31.57,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}片刻间  四目相视
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.70,0:02:35.24,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}转移视线之前  你在想些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.16,0:02:38.20,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}我很在意
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.54,0:02:42.58,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}看到撅起嘴的我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.71,0:02:46.09,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}你会问我「怎么了」吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.13,0:02:48.17,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}亦或静静等待？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.38,0:02:53.93,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}蒙混过后的自言自语
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.09,0:02:56.60,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}实在太害羞了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.85,0:02:59.77,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}能别偷听吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.35,0:03:02.94,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}已经没有退路
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.06,0:03:05.27,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}这份两情相悦的恋情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.48,0:03:10.03,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}悄然拉开帷幕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.94,0:03:13.45,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}做过无数次美梦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.53,0:03:17.32,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}醒后还想再次沉醉其中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.37,0:03:19.41,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}这一切都拜你所赐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.45,0:03:21.83,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}贪婪是恋爱的本质
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.87,0:03:24.42,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}解放渴求自由的心灵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.54,0:03:27.33,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}做一回真正的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.46,0:03:30.09,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}理想、妄想和现实
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.17,0:03:32.84,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}都伴随在你左右
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.92,0:03:38.35,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\clip(0,340,640,360)}{\move(630,338,630,358,0,150)}共步崭新的世界
Comment: 0,0:00:00.07,0:00:00.07,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPlrcCHN2'-----
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.57,0:02:31.72,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}片刻间  四目相视
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.24,0:02:35.39,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}转移视线之前  你在想些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.20,0:02:38.35,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}我很在意
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.58,0:02:42.73,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}看到撅起嘴的我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.09,0:02:46.24,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}你会问我「怎么了」吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.17,0:02:48.32,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}亦或静静等待？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.93,0:02:54.08,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}蒙混过后的自言自语
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.60,0:02:56.75,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}实在太害羞了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.77,0:02:59.92,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}能别偷听吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.94,0:03:03.09,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}已经没有退路
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.27,0:03:05.42,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}这份两情相悦的恋情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.03,0:03:10.18,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}悄然拉开帷幕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.45,0:03:13.60,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}做过无数次美梦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.32,0:03:17.47,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}醒后还想再次沉醉其中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.41,0:03:19.56,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}这一切都拜你所赐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.83,0:03:21.98,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}贪婪是恋爱的本质
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.42,0:03:24.57,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}解放渴求自由的心灵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.33,0:03:27.48,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}做一回真正的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.09,0:03:30.24,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}理想、妄想和现实
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.84,0:03:32.99,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}都伴随在你左右
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.35,0:03:38.50,OPlrcCHN2,,0,0,0,,{\move(630,358,630,378)}共步崭新的世界
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----EDlrcJPN-----
Comment: 0,0:22:06.55,0:22:06.59,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.69,0:22:09.19,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}INSIDE　IDENTITY
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.19,0:22:11.99,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}居場所はどこ？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.12,0:22:24.63,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}勘違いが恥だとか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.71,0:22:27.21,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}素直さが痛いとか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.34,0:22:29.55,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}誰がなんと言いようと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.55,0:22:32.43,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}正しさなんてわかんないぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.47,0:22:35.05,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}普通に流れていく日常に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:37.64,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}無理して馴染ませた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.68,0:22:40.39,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}沈んじまった個性たちを
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.48,0:22:42.60,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}噛んで飲んで吐いて笑う
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.64,0:22:47.23,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}こんな僕をわかってほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.32,0:22:52.57,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}言いたいけど言えなくって
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.65,0:22:57.53,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}なんで誰もわかってくんないのと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.66,0:23:02.62,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}思うのは贅沢なのかな？なのかなぁ？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.83,0:23:07.92,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}感情的な太陽は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.00,0:23:10.63,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}熱をあげすぎて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.71,0:23:13.05,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}どうにかなりそう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.17,0:23:18.14,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}叫びたくてしょうが無い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.30,0:23:24.14,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}がむしゃらに求めてるIDENTITY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.14,0:23:26.60,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}INSIDE　MY　FEELING
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.69,0:23:29.19,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}INSIDE　MY　JUSTICE
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.23,0:23:31.73,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}邪魔しないで
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.82,0:23:33.78,EDlrcJPN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}居場所はどこ？
Comment: 0,0:00:00.09,0:00:00.09,Default,,0,0,0,,-----EDlrcCHN-----
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.69,0:22:09.19,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}INSIDE  IDENTITY
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.19,0:22:11.99,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}我的栖身之地在哪儿？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.12,0:22:24.63,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}误解令人感到害羞什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.71,0:22:27.21,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}率真令人难以忍受什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.34,0:22:29.55,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}无论他人怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.55,0:22:32.43,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}我也不知到底「正确」为何物
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.47,0:22:35.05,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}强迫自己去习惯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:37.64,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}一成不变的日常
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.68,0:22:40.39,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}将沉沦的种种个性
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.48,0:22:42.60,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}啃食饮尽  唾弃嘲笑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.64,0:22:47.23,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}希望你能理解这样的我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.32,0:22:52.57,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}欲言又止
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.65,0:22:57.53,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}连思考「为什么谁人都无法理解我」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.66,0:23:02.62,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}都已成为一种奢侈了吗？了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.83,0:23:07.92,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}多愁善感的太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.00,0:23:10.63,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}释放出过多的热量
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.71,0:23:13.05,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}把我晒得快不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.17,0:23:18.14,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}按耐不住呐喊的冲动
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.30,0:23:24.14,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}不顾一切地渴求IDENTITY
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.14,0:23:26.60,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}INSIDE  MY  FEELING
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.69,0:23:29.19,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}INSIDE  MY  JUSTICE
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.23,0:23:31.73,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}千万别妨碍我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.82,0:23:33.78,EDlrcCHN,,0,0,0,,{\fad(150,150)}我的栖身之地在哪儿？
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----TXT-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.43,0:00:06.02,Default,,0,0,0,,大家知道中二病这个词吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.60,0:00:10.31,Default,,0,0,0,,传言病发在迎来青春期的初中二年级
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.40,0:00:12.44,Default,,0,0,0,,可爱又可怕的疾病
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.07,0:00:17.65,Default,,0,0,0,,逐渐形成的自我意识和非理性的幼稚想法互相混杂
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.74,0:00:21.12,Default,,0,0,0,,从而做出奇怪的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.82,0:00:24.91,Default,,0,0,0,,昨天为止还只看周刊少年志的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.95,0:00:27.62,Default,,0,0,0,,突然之间开始阅读英语原版书籍
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.91,0:00:30.50,Default,,0,0,0,,明明还无法理解咖啡的苦味
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.58,0:00:32.46,Default,,0,0,0,,却坚持要买黑咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.88,0:00:35.42,Default,,0,0,0,,深信自己拥有某种特别的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.50,0:00:38.63,Default,,0,0,0,,深陷超自然系中不能自拔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.76,0:00:42.97,Default,,0,0,0,,那么  这位少年在初中时代
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.01,0:00:45.93,Default,,0,0,0,,也是位完美的中二病患者
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.27,0:00:49.06,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs18\pos(350,328)}Dark·Flame  Master
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.27,0:00:49.06,Default,,0,0,0,,自称为「漆黑烈焰使」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.19,0:00:50.44,Default,,0,0,0,,标志台词是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.74,0:00:58.53,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an7\fs16\fad(200,0)}Dark Flame Master（漆黑烈焰使）\N14岁时自己的力量觉醒便踏上旅途。\N途中与盯上暗黑龙力量的组织\N以及数次重生的昔日宿敌不停歇的战斗\N背负着这命中注定的宿命
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.10,0:00:53.86,Default,,0,0,0,,「被漆黑烈焰吞噬殆尽吧」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.20,0:01:00.91,Default,,0,0,0,,好丢人…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.95,0:01:03.16,Default,,0,0,0,,快忘记…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.49,0:01:04.33,Default,,0,0,0,,就像这样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.45,0:01:09.37,Default,,0,0,0,,仅仅是回忆起来就会郁闷死人的羞人疾病
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.40,0:01:35.36,Default,,0,0,0,,好疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.75,0:01:51.50,Default,,0,0,0,,看见了？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.33,0:01:54.63,Default,,0,0,0,,啊  没
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.17,0:01:56.09,Default,,0,0,0,,要看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.75,0:01:57.34,Default,,0,0,0,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.46,0:03:50.54,Default,,0,0,0,,呐  樟叶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.71,0:03:51.96,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么了  哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.25,0:03:53.29,Default,,0,0,0,,看起来如何
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.92,0:03:58.88,Default,,0,0,0,,普通
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.34,0:04:00.34,Default,,0,0,0,,很普通对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.38,0:04:00.89,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.18,0:04:02.43,Default,,0,0,0,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.51,0:04:03.80,Default,,0,0,0,,好奇怪的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.39,0:04:10.56,Default,,0,0,0,,这堆垃圾是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.60,0:04:13.73,Default,,0,0,0,,那是我的  我过会儿会拿走的  不用管了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.98,0:04:15.69,Default,,0,0,0,,还真不少呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.61,0:04:21.07,Default,,0,0,0,,这玩意是哥哥用辛辛苦苦攒的压岁钱买的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.20,0:04:22.53,Default,,0,0,0,,好了啦  别玩那个了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.78,0:04:23.49,Default,,0,0,0,,买了这个的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.62,0:04:26.99,Default,,0,0,0,,是不是还说过「这下子世界就是我的了」之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.04,0:04:28.37,Default,,0,0,0,,没说过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.58,0:04:29.71,Default,,0,0,0,,说过了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.87,0:04:31.58,Default,,0,0,0,,那时候还经常穿着奇怪的外套
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.62,0:04:34.54,Default,,0,0,0,,好烦  不用回忆那些多余的事情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.46,0:04:37.00,Default,,0,0,0,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.67,0:04:40.55,Default,,0,0,0,,妈妈  今天是哥哥的入学典礼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.59,0:04:41.51,Default,,0,0,0,,还记得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.63,0:04:43.09,Default,,0,0,0,,啊  差点忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.14,0:04:45.26,Default,,0,0,0,,没关系啦  高中的入学典礼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.26,0:04:46.76,Default,,0,0,0,,父母不来也没事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.61,0:05:01.36,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.40,0:05:04.78,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉  那个…您请
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.53,0:05:06.49,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.45,0:05:11.37,Default,,0,0,0,,那身制服  跟我是同一所学校吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.09,0:05:23.88,Default,,0,0,0,,那家伙  是昨天的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.69,0:05:33.60,Default,,0,0,0,,打开了！？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.70,0:05:43.78,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然不太明白
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.82,0:05:46.57,Default,,0,0,0,,但我错过了一班车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.79,0:05:53.46,Default,,0,0,0,,呜哇  一个人都不认识
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.58,0:05:54.67,Default,,0,0,0,,不过也对
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.96,0:05:58.21,Default,,0,0,0,,我特意选择了初中那帮家伙不会来的学校
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.25,0:06:02.55,Default,,0,0,0,,第一印象最关键  不要太过于在意
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.80,0:06:04.76,Default,,0,0,0,,不知不觉融入进去就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.59,0:06:06.80,Default,,0,0,0,,我是富樫勇太
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.55,0:06:10.26,Default,,0,0,0,,这只手臂的绷带由于些许缘故不能解开
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.02,0:06:13.73,Default,,0,0,0,,因为黑炎龙会出来扰乱世间的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.56,0:06:18.44,Default,,0,0,0,,心好疼啊  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.02,0:06:20.98,Default,,0,0,0,,从那以后我在班里就是形单影只
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.40,0:06:23.53,Default,,0,0,0,,嘛  算了  不要被过去给束缚了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.99,0:06:26.95,Default,,0,0,0,,这里已经没有人知道过去的我了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.12,0:06:30.08,Default,,0,0,0,,吾名为「漆黑烈焰使」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.53,0:06:32.95,Default,,0,0,0,,「被漆黑烈焰吞噬殆尽吧」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.33,0:06:35.00,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.62,0:06:38.08,Default,,0,0,0,,生涯封印！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.42,0:06:44.09,Default,,0,0,0,,是这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.72,0:06:47.34,Default,,0,0,0,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.34,0:06:50.72,Default,,0,0,0,,对不住  能分我根自动铅芯吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.06,0:06:52.18,Default,,0,0,0,,啊  可以
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.02,0:06:54.43,Default,,0,0,0,,你初中是哪儿的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.56,0:06:55.68,Default,,0,0,0,,菱山中学
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.06,0:06:58.65,Default,,0,0,0,,诶  离这还挺远的呐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.98,0:07:02.11,Default,,0,0,0,,所以初中的同学一个都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.15,0:07:03.15,Default,,0,0,0,,啊  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.82,0:07:05.82,Default,,0,0,0,,我也没什么熟人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.20,0:07:07.40,Default,,0,0,0,,总之请多指教了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.11,0:07:09.74,Default,,0,0,0,,我叫一色诚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.99,0:07:11.95,Default,,0,0,0,,我叫富樫勇太
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.70,0:07:15.33,Default,,0,0,0,,对对  要的就是这种普通的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.41,0:07:16.91,Default,,0,0,0,,高中出道  万岁
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.41,0:07:19.17,Default,,0,0,0,,话说  你怎么看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.37,0:07:20.71,Default,,0,0,0,,这个班里的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.38,0:07:21.92,Default,,0,0,0,,女生？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.04,0:07:24.30,Default,,0,0,0,,不觉得聚集了很多美人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.88,0:07:29.30,Default,,0,0,0,,我是觉得不错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.68,0:07:32.22,Default,,0,0,0,,我还不是很清楚…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.93,0:07:35.72,Default,,0,0,0,,啊  是同一个班的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.48,0:07:37.64,Default,,0,0,0,,眼光不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.81,0:07:39.27,Default,,0,0,0,,看上丹生谷了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.52,0:07:40.44,Default,,0,0,0,,丹生谷？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.60,0:07:42.31,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯  丹生谷森夏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.48,0:07:45.15,Default,,0,0,0,,目前在我心目中暂居首位
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.57,0:07:49.66,Default,,0,0,0,,这就是所谓命运的红线吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.66,0:07:57.96,Default,,0,0,0,,终于和你邂逅了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.62,0:08:03.29,Default,,0,0,0,,眼睛…眼睛在共鸣…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.50,0:08:04.42,Default,,0,0,0,,认识的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.84,0:08:06.05,Default,,0,0,0,,啊  不  不认识
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.38,0:08:07.63,Default,,0,0,0,,为了寻找你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.88,0:08:10.22,Default,,0,0,0,,历经无数岁月来到了这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.55,0:08:12.76,Default,,0,0,0,,好像在告白啊  羡慕死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.80,0:08:14.68,Default,,0,0,0,,啊  这不是那回事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.97,0:08:16.47,Default,,0,0,0,,对  这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.72,0:08:18.23,Default,,0,0,0,,中  中…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.43,0:08:19.94,Default,,0,0,0,,中二病啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.31,0:08:24.73,Default,,0,0,0,,眼睛…眼睛…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.28,0:08:27.36,Default,,0,0,0,,眼睛…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.99,0:08:31.53,Default,,0,0,0,,我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.66,0:08:32.78,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.87,0:08:35.37,Default,,0,0,0,,最下面那一层…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.58,0:08:36.49,Default,,0,0,0,,下面的…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.70,0:08:37.41,Default,,0,0,0,,是这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.87,0:08:39.75,Default,,0,0,0,,保健室的老师有点事出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.79,0:08:41.17,Default,,0,0,0,,让我帮你点些眼药水
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.79,0:08:45.13,Default,,0,0,0,,再不抓紧点的话  入学典礼就要开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.84,0:08:49.55,Default,,0,0,0,,昨晚也是你在阳台上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.05,0:08:52.09,Default,,0,0,0,,你打算做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.84,0:08:55.60,Default,,0,0,0,,因为这只眼睛共鸣了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.97,0:08:58.72,Default,,0,0,0,,没错  在悠久的过去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.89,0:09:00.73,Default,,0,0,0,,你和我曾相遇过
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.10,0:09:02.56,Default,,0,0,0,,在看到你的瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.77,0:09:05.77,Default,,0,0,0,,这只邪王真眼向我诉说了那份因缘
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.19,0:09:08.65,Default,,0,0,0,,所以一直在伺机跟你接触
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.03,0:09:15.03,Default,,0,0,0,,这个苦味  果然是黑暗组织…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.45,0:09:17.45,Default,,0,0,0,,果断封印
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.87,0:09:19.91,Default,,0,0,0,,这家伙  果然…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.25,0:09:24.92,Default,,0,0,0,,邪王真眼是以圣洁的心灵来制御黑暗的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.13,0:09:27.96,Default,,0,0,0,,因此被黑暗侵蚀之物自不必说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.17,0:09:31.63,Default,,0,0,0,,就连净化过的圣水也是危险之物  不可碰触
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.84,0:09:34.13,Default,,0,0,0,,毫无疑问  是中二病
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.43,0:09:36.85,Default,,0,0,0,,差点就陷入敌人的圈套了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.55,0:09:40.64,Default,,0,0,0,,从今往后请多加谨慎  「漆黑烈焰使」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.77,0:09:41.14,Default,,0,0,0,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.85,0:09:45.65,Default,,0,0,0,,「被漆黑烈焰吞噬…」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.73,0:09:47.52,Default,,0,0,0,,住口！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.61,0:09:48.94,Default,,0,0,0,,你为什么会知道这些
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.02,0:09:49.86,Default,,0,0,0,,在哪里听到的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.11,0:09:53.70,Default,,0,0,0,,我的邪王真眼拥有看破一切的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.99,0:09:57.16,Default,,0,0,0,,拥有level  7魔导士力量的勇太的情报…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.24,0:09:58.41,Default,,0,0,0,,在哪里听到的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.58,0:10:00.70,Default,,0,0,0,,我只看一眼  过去与未来的一切…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.87,0:10:03.04,Default,,0,0,0,,在哪里听到的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.33,0:10:08.42,Default,,0,0,0,,勇太  好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.46,0:10:10.84,Default,,0,0,0,,我问你在哪里听到的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.92,0:10:13.88,Default,,0,0,0,,看不见了  勇太  我什么都看不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.22,0:10:16.55,Default,,0,0,0,,刚才在体育馆的下面听到的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.30,0:10:18.26,Default,,0,0,0,,体育馆？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.30,0:10:21.60,Default,,0,0,0,,我还以为没人听到…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.97,0:10:25.19,Default,,0,0,0,,听好了  那件事情绝对不能对别人说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.35,0:10:26.52,Default,,0,0,0,,我很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.77,0:10:29.15,Default,,0,0,0,,不可视境界线上的扭曲法则
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.23,0:10:30.90,Default,,0,0,0,,以及事像的构造变化…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.90,0:10:31.86,Default,,0,0,0,,不是说这个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.11,0:10:33.49,Default,,0,0,0,,我是指我的过去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.74,0:10:35.11,Default,,0,0,0,,Dark·Flame  Master也好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.36,0:10:37.07,Default,,0,0,0,,漆黑烈焰使也好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.45,0:10:39.03,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么  好帅的说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.20,0:10:40.33,Default,,0,0,0,,一点都不帅！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.58,0:10:41.24,Default,,0,0,0,,我先说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.41,0:10:44.29,Default,,0,0,0,,我已经决定从这一切中毕业了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.58,0:10:45.58,Default,,0,0,0,,干干脆脆地
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.75,0:10:46.67,Default,,0,0,0,,彻底地
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.38,0:10:49.21,Default,,0,0,0,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.42,0:10:50.00,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.88,0:10:53.09,Default,,0,0,0,,那你终于成为了level  8的魔导士？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.21,0:10:55.30,Default,,0,0,0,,才不是！！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.55,0:10:56.76,Default,,0,0,0,,是从中二病毕业！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.84,0:10:58.64,Default,,0,0,0,,我既不是漆黑烈焰使
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.72,0:11:00.01,Default,,0,0,0,,也不是魔导士
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.14,0:11:02.39,Default,,0,0,0,,是普普通通的高中一年级学生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.89,0:11:05.18,Default,,0,0,0,,你能别那么惊讶么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.56,0:11:06.48,Default,,0,0,0,,我先说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.64,0:11:08.85,Default,,0,0,0,,你也是普通的高中生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.19,0:11:11.15,Default,,0,0,0,,我有着邪王真眼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.27,0:11:12.73,Default,,0,0,0,,跟那种东西没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.90,0:11:15.86,Default,,0,0,0,,再说了  那种东西本来就不存在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.32,0:11:17.40,Default,,0,0,0,,是存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.57,0:11:18.66,Default,,0,0,0,,不存在的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.24,0:11:21.24,Default,,0,0,0,,那么你要见证下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.37,0:11:26.87,Default,,0,0,0,,我的眼睛  要看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.08,0:11:28.75,Default,,0,0,0,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.04,0:11:30.79,Default,,0,0,0,,不  那种事情不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.67,0:11:33.13,Default,,0,0,0,,啊  让我看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.30,0:11:43.01,Default,,0,0,0,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.64,0:11:50.15,Default,,0,0,0,,不是吧…！！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.40,0:12:02.69,Default,,0,0,0,,别…别过来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.15,0:12:06.19,Default,,0,0,0,,好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.95,0:12:12.70,Default,,0,0,0,,等等  我重新戴一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.95,0:12:14.37,Default,,0,0,0,,是彩瞳啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.70,0:12:17.54,Default,,0,0,0,,讨厌…进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.71,0:12:18.79,Default,,0,0,0,,进到我里面来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.92,0:12:20.08,Default,,0,0,0,,别发出奇怪的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.84,0:12:23.75,Default,,0,0,0,,残像
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.17,0:12:26.51,Default,,0,0,0,,给我听好  刚才说很多遍了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.55,0:12:28.59,Default,,0,0,0,,我已经从中二病毕业了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.84,0:12:30.84,Default,,0,0,0,,所以别和我扯上关系
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.01,0:12:32.51,Default,,0,0,0,,以前的事也不许说哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.85,0:12:34.64,Default,,0,0,0,,但是你看到我的眼睛了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.97,0:12:37.31,Default,,0,0,0,,这样一来契约就缔结完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.85,0:12:41.48,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs18\pos(390,328)}Soul  Mates
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.85,0:12:41.48,Default,,0,0,0,,共有黑暗灵魂的魂友
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.52,0:12:42.90,Default,,0,0,0,,魂字真多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.36,0:12:44.69,Default,,0,0,0,,那我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.78,0:12:46.36,Default,,0,0,0,,你也赶快吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.82,0:12:49.40,Default,,0,0,0,,有请新生致词
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.82,0:12:52.45,Default,,0,0,0,,新生代表——丹生谷森夏
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.57,0:12:53.16,Default,,0,0,0,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.74,0:12:55.62,Default,,0,0,0,,居然会被那种家伙缠上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.08,0:12:58.16,Default,,0,0,0,,难道我身上还有奇怪的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.91,0:12:59.04,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs19\an8}在樱花盛开  春光明媚的今天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.46,0:13:03.13,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs19\an8}我们成功迎来了入学典礼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.50,0:13:05.55,Default,,0,0,0,,她是新生代表吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.38,0:13:10.43,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs19\an8}非常感谢今日为我们新生准备了这般盛大的入学典礼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.05,0:13:13.05,Default,,0,0,0,,那么既然大家都自我介绍完了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.26,0:13:15.43,Default,,0,0,0,,今天就到此结束吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.89,0:13:19.94,Default,,0,0,0,,请大家回家后仔细确认下课程表哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.89,0:13:22.23,Default,,0,0,0,,喂喂  富樫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.81,0:13:24.19,Default,,0,0,0,,一会儿有空吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.52,0:13:29.36,Default,,0,0,0,,班里有人组织一起去吃顿饭
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.36,0:13:32.78,Default,,0,0,0,,你…你是在邀请我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.91,0:13:33.41,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.83,0:13:38.95,Default,,0,0,0,,但是我去真的好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.08,0:13:39.70,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.25,0:13:43.04,Default,,0,0,0,,难道是小鸟游同学吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.33,0:13:44.21,Default,,0,0,0,,小鸟游？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.38,0:13:46.88,Default,,0,0,0,,就是刚才你带去保健室的那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.59,0:13:51.63,Default,,0,0,0,,该不会是和小鸟游同学约好一起回家了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.63,0:13:52.80,Default,,0,0,0,,才没有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.22,0:13:55.22,Default,,0,0,0,,我和她一点关系都没
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.47,0:13:57.39,Default,,0,0,0,,井水不犯河水！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.81,0:14:00.81,Default,,0,0,0,,什么…你难道是「这个」吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.89,0:14:01.69,Default,,0,0,0,,才不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.73,0:14:05.81,Default,,0,0,0,,只不过  传出奇怪的流言多不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.23,0:14:07.23,Default,,0,0,0,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.69,0:14:09.53,Default,,0,0,0,,一色君  怎么说？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.86,0:14:11.11,Default,,0,0,0,,我去我去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.61,0:14:13.24,Default,,0,0,0,,好  那我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.49,0:14:14.49,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.91,0:14:16.32,Default,,0,0,0,,富樫君~
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.20,0:14:19.12,Default,,0,0,0,,过来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.50,0:14:23.83,Default,,0,0,0,,她的钱包好像丢了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.75,0:14:29.38,Default,,0,0,0,,小鸟游同学刚搬家到这里  对附近不太了解
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.75,0:14:31.67,Default,,0,0,0,,富樫君可以送她回去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.76,0:14:33.26,Default,,0,0,0,,诶  为什么是我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.80,0:14:36.60,Default,,0,0,0,,因为她家貌似就在你家旁边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.26,0:14:37.89,Default,,0,0,0,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.68,0:14:42.43,Default,,0,0,0,,就在我家楼上嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.56,0:14:44.56,Default,,0,0,0,,所以才这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.27,0:14:46.77,Default,,0,0,0,,那么拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.98,0:14:50.03,Default,,0,0,0,,真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.57,0:14:51.94,Default,,0,0,0,,下次一定去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.86,0:14:54.57,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯  再见
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.45,0:15:00.66,Default,,0,0,0,,你从什么时候开始住这儿的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.20,0:15:04.54,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs18\pos(410,328)}OL
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.20,0:15:04.54,Default,,0,0,0,,我记得楼上住的是独居的女白领来着
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.71,0:15:06.37,Default,,0,0,0,,前天刚搬过来住的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.67,0:15:08.59,Default,,0,0,0,,小鸟游十花是我的姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.96,0:15:09.84,Default,,0,0,0,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.09,0:15:11.67,Default,,0,0,0,,是到姐姐家里来住了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.92,0:15:13.47,Default,,0,0,0,,表面上是这样的设定
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.76,0:15:17.93,Default,,0,0,0,,但实际上十花是「不可视境界线」管理局中的一名魔术师
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.35,0:15:18.93,Default,,0,0,0,,是敌人！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.22,0:15:19.89,Default,,0,0,0,,我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.56,0:15:22.64,Default,,0,0,0,,一旦她觉醒  那就大事不妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.85,0:15:24.60,Default,,0,0,0,,就算依靠邪王真眼也无能为力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.35,0:15:26.06,Default,,0,0,0,,太可怕了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.35,0:15:27.60,Default,,0,0,0,,这么可怕吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.02,0:15:30.02,Default,,0,0,0,,绝不服输的六花！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.82,0:15:34.74,Default,,0,0,0,,你要整天说这种莫名其妙的话  姐姐肯定会生气吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.15,0:15:36.70,Default,,0,0,0,,我希望勇太能协助我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.07,0:15:39.12,Default,,0,0,0,,若是有漆黑烈焰使的协助
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.28,0:15:43.58,Default,,0,0,0,,一定能突破管理局的阻碍  找到「不可视境界线」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.79,0:15:45.58,Default,,0,0,0,,所以别再提这名字了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.38,0:15:50.42,Default,,0,0,0,,我想到了一个你的新技能
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.88,0:15:57.01,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs18\pos(320,328)}Judgement  Lucifer
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.88,0:15:57.01,Default,,0,0,0,,路西法之审判
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.76,0:15:59.26,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.35,0:16:02.60,Default,,0,0,0,,居然穿暴走鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.81,0:16:03.60,Default,,0,0,0,,你是小孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.93,0:16:05.60,Default,,0,0,0,,它的机动性很出众
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.27,0:16:09.35,Default,,0,0,0,,而且若是有这个  在受到敌人攻击时…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.19,0:16:18.32,Default,,0,0,0,,肋骨断了两三根吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.74,0:16:20.49,Default,,0,0,0,,就可以这么说  很帅气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.78,0:16:22.37,Default,,0,0,0,,住手  别在这种地方丢人…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.58,0:16:26.37,Default,,0,0,0,,要喝哪个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.62,0:16:27.50,Default,,0,0,0,,我请客
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.08,0:16:28.75,Default,,0,0,0,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.21,0:16:37.22,Default,,0,0,0,,{\pos(320,328)\fs19\fsp4}↑↑↓↓←→←→
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.21,0:16:37.22,Default,,0,0,0,,上上下下左右左右
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.92,0:16:35.01,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs19\an8}喂  小鸟游同学
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.42,0:16:37.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs19\an8}电车来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.38,0:16:39.05,Default,,0,0,0,,现在投硬币！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.18,0:16:39.59,Default,,0,0,0,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.34,0:16:43.01,Default,,0,0,0,,现在按BA！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.34,0:16:44.18,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an7\fs17}KONAMI秘技：在包括《魂斗罗》等多款游戏中登场的秘技
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.26,0:16:44.18,Default,,0,0,0,,BA是什么！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.60,0:16:50.27,Default,,0,0,0,,补充魔力的饮料
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.65,0:16:53.48,Default,,0,0,0,,是管理局在各地偷偷设置的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.86,0:16:56.86,Default,,0,0,0,,电车都开走了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.78,0:16:59.16,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an7\fs17}（中奖了哦  再来一瓶）
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.76,0:16:59.31,Default,,0,0,0,,中奖了哦  真棒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.66,0:17:03.45,Default,,0,0,0,,知道我的厉害了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.58,0:17:06.54,Default,,0,0,0,,不  你刚才明显露出一副很意外的表情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.58,0:17:11.67,Default,,0,0,0,,顺带一提  B和A是Banana和Apple
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.75,0:17:14.00,Default,,0,0,0,,会随着季节而变化  要多加注意哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.09,0:17:14.88,Default,,0,0,0,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.46,0:17:17.96,Default,,0,0,0,,终于回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.42,0:17:20.80,Default,,0,0,0,,你到底在途中耽误了多久…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.88,0:17:21.89,Default,,0,0,0,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.64,0:17:24.05,Default,,0,0,0,,大事不妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.85,0:17:28.18,Default,,0,0,0,,好像都是要送到小鸟游家里的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.31,0:17:31.69,Default,,0,0,0,,但等了很久都没人回来  所以就说先放我们家了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.85,0:17:33.27,Default,,0,0,0,,这什么搬家公司啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.11,0:17:34.90,Default,,0,0,0,,是你的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.57,0:17:38.94,Default,,0,0,0,,由于管理局的阻碍  回家稍晚了一些
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.28,0:17:41.07,Default,,0,0,0,,原本按照计划是下午三点回到家的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.57,0:17:43.99,Default,,0,0,0,,哥哥  这位是？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.32,0:17:46.20,Default,,0,0,0,,楼上的小鸟游家的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.53,0:17:47.95,Default,,0,0,0,,说是和姐姐一起住
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.54,0:17:49.62,Default,,0,0,0,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.00,0:17:51.75,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么有这么多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.21,0:17:54.50,Default,,0,0,0,,你一人的行李也太多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.21,0:17:56.96,Default,,0,0,0,,所有东西都很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.21,0:17:59.92,Default,,0,0,0,,这里面不会全是这种垃圾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.13,0:18:03.05,Default,,0,0,0,,哥哥  我先去买晚餐了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.30,0:18:04.84,Default,,0,0,0,,实用的东西也有
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.01,0:18:07.35,Default,,0,0,0,,啊  是自动伞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.64,0:18:08.47,Default,,0,0,0,,这可以成为武器
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.89,0:18:09.56,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs18\pos(320,328)}Gungnir
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.89,0:18:09.56,Default,,0,0,0,,永恒之枪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.18,0:18:12.14,Default,,0,0,0,,防御的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.23,0:18:14.44,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs18\pos(320,328)}Schwarzschild
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.23,0:18:14.44,Default,,0,0,0,,漆黑伞盾
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.48,0:18:17.61,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs18\pos(320,328)}Schwarzschild
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.48,0:18:17.61,Default,,0,0,0,,漆黑伞盾
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.98,0:18:19.23,Default,,0,0,0,,行了行了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.28,0:18:20.86,Default,,0,0,0,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.86,0:18:22.99,Default,,0,0,0,,赶紧拿走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.54,0:18:35.96,Default,,0,0,0,,我明白了…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.43,0:18:48.81,Default,,0,0,0,,这是最后一箱了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.02,0:18:52.85,Default,,0,0,0,,非常感谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.89,0:18:54.73,Default,,0,0,0,,好好感谢我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.11,0:18:58.94,Default,,0,0,0,,你姐姐呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.44,0:19:01.36,Default,,0,0,0,,她回家一般都很晚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.83,0:19:11.75,Default,,0,0,0,,是小鸟游的妹妹吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.20,0:19:14.37,Default,,0,0,0,,姐妹都是美人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.08,0:19:16.79,Default,,0,0,0,,勇太  要好好加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.92,0:19:17.79,Default,,0,0,0,,加个什么油啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.29,0:19:20.25,Default,,0,0,0,,那个…请问你的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.59,0:19:23.88,Default,,0,0,0,,别在意  其实没有任何毛病
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.22,0:19:28.47,Default,,0,0,0,,说到底  邪王真眼是通过神圣力量来制御黑暗力量…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.55,0:19:31.18,Default,,0,0,0,,不用你大费口舌了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.22,0:19:32.22,Default,,0,0,0,,了解了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.52,0:19:34.64,Default,,0,0,0,,下地狱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.44,0:19:38.52,Default,,0,0,0,,梦叶  你怎么可以把这个随便拿出来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.56,0:19:39.11,Default,,0,0,0,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.56,0:19:40.52,Default,,0,0,0,,好帅
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.86,0:19:41.86,Default,,0,0,0,,一点都不帅
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.23,0:19:43.19,Default,,0,0,0,,好帅
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.94,0:19:46.32,Default,,0,0,0,,这个要是装备在背后就完美了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.53,0:19:47.53,Default,,0,0,0,,完美？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.78,0:19:49.70,Default,,0,0,0,,以前哥哥经常这么干哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.82,0:19:51.95,Default,,0,0,0,,穿着黑色的外套  把剑背在身后
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.04,0:19:52.87,Default,,0,0,0,,樟叶！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.04,0:19:56.00,Default,,0,0,0,,那时候的勇太真是很奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.41,0:19:59.58,Default,,0,0,0,,在吃饭前还要念咒文什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.79,0:20:00.67,Default,,0,0,0,,妈妈！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.88,0:20:02.75,Default,,0,0,0,,你也该准备去上夜班啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.01,0:20:04.88,Default,,0,0,0,,是~
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.67,0:20:06.76,Default,,0,0,0,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.05,0:20:14.68,Default,,0,0,0,,都说这是垃圾  别随便拿来玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.93,0:20:15.60,Default,,0,0,0,,垃圾？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.39,0:20:18.85,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.27,0:20:21.77,Default,,0,0,0,,这明明是漆黑烈焰使的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.82,0:20:25.19,Default,,0,0,0,,所以说我已经毕业了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.65,0:20:26.36,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.20,0:20:28.28,Default,,0,0,0,,太难为情了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.91,0:20:29.74,Default,,0,0,0,,好帅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.24,0:20:31.45,Default,,0,0,0,,不帅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.99,0:20:33.12,Default,,0,0,0,,一点都不帅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.91,0:20:39.46,Default,,0,0,0,,再说了  就算这么做也是毫无意义的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.29,0:20:44.17,Default,,0,0,0,,漆黑烈焰也好暗黑龙的力量也好  都是不存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.09,0:20:46.92,Default,,0,0,0,,而我却像个笨蛋一样地追求…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.22,0:20:48.68,Default,,0,0,0,,有的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.13,0:20:50.05,Default,,0,0,0,,力量是存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.01,0:20:51.72,Default,,0,0,0,,没有的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.85,0:20:52.39,Default,,0,0,0,,有的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.85,0:20:55.64,Default,,0,0,0,,我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.93,0:20:57.52,Default,,0,0,0,,有的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.81,0:21:02.15,Default,,0,0,0,,所以  请别舍弃它
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.12,0:21:19.29,Default,,0,0,0,,被漆黑烈焰吞噬殆尽吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.01,0:21:33.05,Default,,0,0,0,,别误会了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.10,0:21:36.81,Default,,0,0,0,,我只是觉得丢掉太可惜了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.35,0:21:39.18,Default,,0,0,0,,之后拿去拍卖换钱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.06,0:21:42.69,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.36,0:21:46.57,Default,,0,0,0,,回屋里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.23,0:21:49.82,Default,,0,0,0,,一直呆这里会感冒的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.65,0:21:51.20,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.70,0:22:01.00,Default,,0,0,0,,话虽如此  但今年的春雨却令人稍感温暖
