[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: Default Aegisub file
Original Script: 漫游字幕組
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 848
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF8000,&H0058281B,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF8000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,1
Style: ED1,ＤＦＰまるもじ体W3,22,&H28FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H004F4F4F,&H8CF4AF2F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,9,30,30,10,1
Style: ED2,华康少女文字W5,23,&H28FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H004F4F4F,&H8CF4AF2F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,9,30,30,10,1
Style: OP1,ＤＦＰまるもじ体W3,28,&HF0FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0F4AF2F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP2,华康少女文字W5,25,&HF0FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0F4AF2F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,3,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.83,0:21:49.03,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由动漫国字幕组制作(bbs.dmguo.com)\N仅供试看,请支持购买正版音像制品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.03,0:21:52.76,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}翻译:银子&はばやし  校对:はばやし  时间:幽幽子  后期:火猫少女  MKV:小圣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.67,0:00:04.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直令人感动
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.82,0:00:06.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.07,0:00:10.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我昨天说的那个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.38,0:00:11.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.64,0:00:13.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 六花
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.56,0:00:15.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:16.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那确实很可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.57,0:00:21.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是魔法结社中封存的梵蒂冈纳米冻结资料
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.43,0:00:24.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第八次魔导战争就要爆发了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.61,0:00:25.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.88,0:00:30.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说嘛 那不是没必要对六花你藏着躲着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.85,0:00:32.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 此言甚是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.88,0:00:37.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 必须隐瞒住作为契约者的我的数据…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.10,0:00:41.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对方一色吧 肯定又不是什么好东西
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.46,0:00:44.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回忆一下当年的可爱女生排位赛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.90,0:00:45.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.16,0:00:47.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.78,0:00:51.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富樫同学 坐过来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.42,0:00:52.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只有一股不祥的预感
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.16,0:00:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太 依据契约 我要审问你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.32,0:00:58.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.47,0:02:32.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 放开我 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.13,0:02:35.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹 马上就会结束的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.57,0:02:39.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了那是作业要用的数据啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.65,0:02:42.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1500,400)\pos(563,325)\3c&H000000&\fs29}Extra Episode  再生之…邪王真眼默示录
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.65,0:02:42.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1500,400)\pos(688,298)\3c&H000000&\fs21}The Rikka Wars
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.70,0:02:41.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么不给我看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.30,0:02:43.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那是因为…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.60,0:02:45.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然必须亲自确认一下了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.88,0:02:49.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万幸 解析用魔导机械已经准备完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.34,0:02:50.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是借用一下而已哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.79,0:02:52.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师你也是的 到底在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.88,0:02:55.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要这么拚命
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.50,0:02:58.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然里面有不可告人的东西是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.35,0:02:59.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.22,0:03:01.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被你们看见也…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.90,0:03:03.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么不…好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.50,0:03:05.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茴香学姐 打开吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.03,0:03:06.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.10,0:03:09.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富樫同学好像很可怜耶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.60,0:03:10.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来打开
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.48,0:03:13.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六花比平常更大胆了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.87,0:03:17.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个书包当中充满了不祥的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.82,0:03:20.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪王真眼感受到了非同寻常的反应
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.04,0:03:23.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.93,0:03:24.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.72,0:03:26.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹生谷…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.72,0:03:27.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒戈了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.79,0:03:28.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.38,0:03:34.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我觉得 他们交易的是男生之间悄悄地传递的数据
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.86,0:03:36.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且当得知这件事情将被暴露于大庭广众之下的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.90,0:03:38.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富樫同学那份动摇…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.19,0:03:41.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结合这些具体推断 这里面的内容该不会是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.52,0:03:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.21,0:03:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.23,0:03:46.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 里面是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.15,0:03:49.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么啦 你倒是说清楚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.50,0:03:52.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是你先说的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.97,0:03:53.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凸守
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.48,0:03:56.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…也就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.37,0:04:02.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗列出智人特别是其中的雌性的…原始的姿态…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.37,0:04:02.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(230,437)\fs21}Homo Sapiens
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.41,0:04:03.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,类似这种的东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.23,0:04:04.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原始的？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.70,0:04:05.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原始的？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.20,0:04:07.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.05,0:04:11.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太狡猾了 明明是你先说的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.24,0:04:12.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可什么都没说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.19,0:04:12.98,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.15,0:04:14.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸红了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.65,0:04:16.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸红的到底是谁啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.38,0:04:19.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里可是学校啊 不管怎么说也不可能把那种东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.13,0:04:22.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富樫同学
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.24,0:04:24.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个该死的格尔松尼盎斯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.24,0:04:24.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,437)\fs21}Ghelzonianses
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.34,0:04:27.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在想象什么呢 不是的 不是的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.22,0:04:28.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 完全搞不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.21,0:04:35.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住 手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.88,0:04:40.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等 等
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.75,0:04:48.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.84,0:04:50.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹子？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.86,0:04:52.07,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以啊 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.71,0:04:53.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真的是很肮脏的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.92,0:04:55.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 要是在这里看那种东西的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.49,0:04:57.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳装…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.49,0:04:58.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.74,0:05:02.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹子 妹子 妹子 妹子 妹子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.35,0:05:04.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.66,0:05:07.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶像？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.44,0:05:12.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 有个偶像 我国中的时候挺崇拜的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.63,0:05:13.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然现在已经隐退了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.74,0:05:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一色他有她的图像数据
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.65,0:05:20.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富樫同学原来也会崇拜偶像吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.50,0:05:24.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关你什么事 为什么我一定要跟你们说这些事情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.19,0:05:26.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为会发展成什么不可挽回的事态呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.75,0:05:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为格尔松尼盎斯已经坠入了真正的黑暗面了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.75,0:05:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(306,437)\fs21}Ghelzonianses
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.87,0:05:34.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这一切只是你自己天马行空的想象而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.90,0:05:38.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢 凸守什么都没说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.50,0:05:42.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的还不是一回事 脸红红地说着什么「原始的」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.66,0:05:43.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.74,0:05:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是既然已经知道内容了 就这样算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.03,0:05:48.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.50,0:05:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能就这样算了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.33,0:05:54.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六花…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.60,0:05:55.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.82,0:05:59.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这重大地违反了勇太与我之间的契约
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.16,0:06:02.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于依据盟约而互相结合的对象
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.52,0:06:06.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密地观看这种东西 简直不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.30,0:06:07.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该不会在生气吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.25,0:06:10.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我藏着掖着确实是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.86,0:06:14.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这算不上违反契约吧 我只是看看而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.15,0:06:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 因此它必须被废弃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.12,0:06:17.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是别人的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.00,0:06:19.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你去还给他
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.99,0:06:22.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了啦 明天还
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.81,0:06:23.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 立刻
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.28,0:06:25.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天也没什么不好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.73,0:06:27.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 以整个魔界驳回你的要求
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.05,0:06:30.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 你就那么想看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.78,0:06:32.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是那样的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.12,0:06:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富樫同学你以前说过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.97,0:06:37.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六花 我的眼中只有你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.08,0:06:39.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必说出来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.62,0:06:44.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说那只是个艺人 对方根本就认不得我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.40,0:06:46.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和不存在有什么区别
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.07,0:06:48.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.38,0:06:50.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么小鸟游同学也可以做同样的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.83,0:06:55.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个男人有点厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.31,0:06:58.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以整个暗炎龙驳回你的要求
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.57,0:07:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 女孩子也是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.60,0:07:04.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了的话就给我拿回去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.05,0:07:06.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赞成森大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.99,0:07:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.84,0:07:11.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.95,0:07:14.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你还没看吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.86,0:07:21.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次别被发现了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.82,0:07:22.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.70,0:07:23.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.11,0:07:24.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茴香学姐 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.57,0:07:28.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 到底要让人费多大功夫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.63,0:07:32.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是富樫同学遵守了约定 真是太好了 六花
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.04,0:07:46.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子也是一样的…吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.96,0:07:49.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.38,0:07:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然发生了这种事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.63,0:07:58.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苏菲亚你认识吗 过去曾经夺走勇太心灵的妹子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.97,0:08:04.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实类似的人是有过 虽然他本人根本不承认
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.91,0:08:09.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 我已经舍弃掉凡夫俗子的恋爱感情了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.38,0:08:12.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 将一切归于混沌的彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.82,0:08:17.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样 那又怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.64,0:08:20.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闇炎色主…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.64,0:08:20.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(406,437)\fs21}Dark Flame Sukebe Master
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.43,0:08:24.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没那么夸张 他只是偶尔看看照片而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.06,0:08:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟勇者也是男孩子啊 现在应该也会偶尔看看小黄书吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.77,0:08:32.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是两回事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.35,0:08:37.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妹子在我和勇太缔结契约之前就抓住了他的心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.77,0:08:38.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.88,0:08:39.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.72,0:08:44.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 现在他是邪王真眼的契约者 有什么不好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.34,0:08:47.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 因为我这个地方感觉闷闷的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.49,0:08:54.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪王真眼的占有欲真强
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.57,0:08:56.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.27,0:08:59.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这或许是件好事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.64,0:09:00.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好事？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.15,0:09:06.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.88,0:09:13.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六花 我只注视你一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.59,0:09:14.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.05,0:09:19.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必担心 我只注视你一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.93,0:09:20.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.47,0:09:38.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许他还有别的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.42,0:09:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无异常
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.76,0:09:58.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然契约是绝对的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.24,0:10:06.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂且告诉你 只是以防万一
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.10,0:10:11.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富樫勇太一定会把重要的东西藏在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.00,0:10:14.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这附近…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.80,0:10:20.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是拿过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.99,0:10:22.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确认一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.20,0:10:33.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙虫牙痛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.60,0:10:38.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对契约造成了恶劣的影响
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.07,0:10:42.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六花 你还没睡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.30,0:10:50.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.10,0:10:53.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好像有什么动静
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.47,0:10:59.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 六花 要迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.28,0:11:05.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 你想吃早餐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.32,0:11:10.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒是整理一下房间啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.24,0:11:19.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.89,0:11:22.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.81,0:11:33.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.07,0:11:34.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.82,0:11:39.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在隐藏什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.85,0:11:42.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在闇炎的环抱之中燃尽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.10,0:12:00.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵架？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.33,0:12:02.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来好像是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.87,0:12:08.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去问了富樫同学以后 他说六花把昨天的存储器给弄坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.09,0:12:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅擅自乱翻别人的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.45,0:12:13.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且什么也不说就把别人的东西拿走了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.79,0:12:15.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这简直是偷窃啊偷窃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.58,0:12:17.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她自己根本不理解这件事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.06,0:12:19.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六花是这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.98,0:12:22.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太明明说了要还回去的 却没有还回去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.94,0:12:24.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这完全违反了契约
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.94,0:12:29.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我破坏的 而是黑暗之力降下的天罚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.92,0:12:32.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他们两个才变成那样了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.21,0:12:36.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.46,0:12:39.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不管呢 放着就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.26,0:12:42.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在应该是森大人的登场了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.71,0:12:43.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.93,0:12:46.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你真的要撒手不管吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.78,0:12:51.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.34,0:12:52.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.28,0:12:55.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你们两个 好好地看着这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.25,0:12:58.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 别老是多管闲事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.24,0:13:01.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是没办法吧 没人来周旋周旋的话怎么行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.60,0:13:05.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也不像普通的恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.61,0:13:06.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.30,0:13:11.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,字面意思 反正又是说着黑暗之力怎么怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.86,0:13:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本对不上话题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.02,0:13:16.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没什么的怎么的呢 依凭邪王真眼…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.68,0:13:18.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的好的 我明白了我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.73,0:13:20.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是富樫同学的错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.76,0:13:23.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必担心 因为我也是这么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.70,0:13:24.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会这么想
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.05,0:13:28.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为先撒谎的不是富樫同学你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.34,0:13:30.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明答应了要还回去 却还是拿回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.95,0:13:32.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是两码事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.63,0:13:35.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是两码事 要是富樫同学你不打破约定的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.86,0:13:37.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情就不会变成这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.10,0:13:41.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有打破吧 我可是好好地去还他了的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.66,0:13:43.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没说已经还给他了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.31,0:13:45.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太差劲了 你这算什么歪理
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.52,0:13:46.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.11,0:13:47.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是难看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.21,0:13:50.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,森大人可不能吵起来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.87,0:13:53.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我总是说要是把事情交给这个冒牌货
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.44,0:13:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情只会变麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.80,0:13:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凸守
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.82,0:14:00.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你要过来啊 你这样只会让事情变麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.63,0:14:01.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.93,0:14:03.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为随从的凸守
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.09,0:14:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于被契约者背叛的主人的心情 感同身受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.23,0:14:10.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凸守
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.22,0:14:12.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须将这件事情传达给格尔松尼盎斯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.22,0:14:12.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(570,437)\fs21}Ghelzonianses
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.40,0:14:16.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他所谓契约到底是何等珍贵的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.95,0:14:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说 我现在也正在做这件…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.72,0:14:20.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我靠边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.19,0:14:20.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.76,0:14:21.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.03,0:14:25.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,契约之珍贵是无法用语言体会的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.44,0:14:28.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须用…魔力！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.32,0:14:30.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔力…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.80,0:14:32.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 难道您遗忘了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.84,0:14:37.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人的邪王真眼的魔力传递给格尔松尼盎斯的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.84,0:14:37.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(570,437)\fs21}Ghelzonianses
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.58,0:14:40.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人由更为强力的契约联结在了一起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.19,0:14:43.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实如此 那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.97,0:14:45.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.33,0:14:46.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.37,0:14:52.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以邪王真眼的力量 将我的想法灌入勇太心中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.66,0:14:53.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爆裂吧 现实
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.70,0:14:54.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绽开吧 神经突触
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.17,0:14:57.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vanishment this world！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.37,0:15:04.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜后
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.37,0:15:04.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,437)\fs21}K·nigin der Nacht
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.76,0:15:07.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.58,0:15:11.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿瓦隆粉碎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.58,0:15:11.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,437)\fs21}Avalon Smash
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.33,0:15:14.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷霆龙卷
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.33,0:15:14.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,437)\fs21}Mjolnir Tornado
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.42,0:15:19.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懒得陪你们玩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.87,0:15:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人 不可以放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.07,0:15:28.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,默示之锤
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.07,0:15:28.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,437)\fs21}Apocalypse Hammer
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.98,0:15:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十亿地狱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.98,0:15:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,437)\fs21}Giga Inferno
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.46,0:15:34.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.93,0:15:36.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不知好歹
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.83,0:15:37.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凸守
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.22,0:15:39.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事已至此 只能发合体技了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.42,0:15:43.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强实魅惑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.59,0:15:46.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯狂雷霆猛击
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.59,0:15:46.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,437)\fs21}Lunatic Mjolnir Crasher
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.64,0:15:49.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我懒得陪你们玩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.99,0:15:51.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是棘手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.62,0:15:53.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都被看破了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.32,0:15:57.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然的 你以为我和你们战斗了多少次
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.53,0:15:59.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么你不加入战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.04,0:16:00.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.92,0:16:04.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近你已经开始萌生作为格尔松尼盎斯的自觉了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.92,0:16:04.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(512,437)\fs21}Ghelzonianses
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.67,0:16:06.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能会萌生那种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.71,0:16:10.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六花 在你好好道歉之前我是不打算原谅你的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.94,0:16:14.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近我一直在反省自己 是不是对你太宠了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.74,0:16:18.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种居高临下的视线简直不能忍
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.80,0:16:28.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不让步
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.69,0:16:30.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就是这种气势
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.63,0:16:33.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 突然来打扰
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.34,0:16:35.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是不介意
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.69,0:16:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是为什么森大人也在一起呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.35,0:16:40.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说因为很在意 所以没办法只能跟来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.31,0:16:44.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是这么说的好不好 我只是没办法放着他们不管而已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.77,0:16:46.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 富樫同学呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.45,0:16:48.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好像回来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:54.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.00,0:16:56.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥你终于回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.45,0:17:00.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了 有乖乖听话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.53,0:17:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 现在不是说这个的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.93,0:17:10.99,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H3A3C3D&\bord0}获得道歉之前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.93,0:17:10.99,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H3A3C3D&\bord0}拒绝归还权 发动 六花
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.64,0:17:10.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说她不会回来了是不是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.25,0:17:13.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用在意 很快就会回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.71,0:17:16.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚饭也不用准备了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.02,0:17:17.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.33,0:17:19.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.64,0:17:27.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样真的没问题吗 还是去找找看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.31,0:17:29.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的 已经很晚了去睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.42,0:17:34.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.00,0:17:42.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是毫不动摇
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.51,0:17:44.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是真的生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.85,0:17:48.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊 已经这么晚了女朋友还没回来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.38,0:17:50.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他完全不担心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.06,0:17:53.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对她的爱已经流失到如此程度了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.71,0:17:58.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为邪王真眼她本来这个时间也总是外出啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.34,0:18:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.08,0:18:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 平时他看起来会稍稍担心一点的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.63,0:18:08.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 还曾经为了主人拖着住院的身体奔跑
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.29,0:18:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是格尔松尼盎斯火热的思念啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.29,0:18:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(378,437)\fs21}Ghelzonianses
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.56,0:18:15.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 大家都说恋情的火热并不具有持续性
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.92,0:18:22.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 勇太已经将和我的契约…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.75,0:18:27.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 灯亮了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.39,0:18:36.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…夜宵？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.04,0:18:39.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是给邪王真眼的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.08,0:18:47.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.66,0:18:48.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.77,0:18:54.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道 我并不想和勇太吵架
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.98,0:18:58.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 对于不喜欢的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.42,0:19:01.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想就这样保持不痛快的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.28,0:19:03.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.87,0:19:07.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才说不回去也可以 然后就来了这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.65,0:19:11.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是这样的话 好好和他说清楚会比较好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.55,0:19:13.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茴香
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.45,0:19:18.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为勇太和六花已经在一起一年多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.54,0:19:19.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.48,0:19:24.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想勇太一定是理解六花的心情的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.78,0:19:27.09,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H3A3C3D&\bord0}想吃就吃吧！！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.78,0:19:27.09,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H3A3C3D&\bord0}From Dark Flame Master
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.22,0:19:29.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为理解对方的心情 所以也认为对方应该是理解自己的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.70,0:19:32.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以也会认为对方只是任性而已
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.07,0:19:33.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茴香
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.32,0:19:37.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想富樫同学一定很想和你好好说清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.20,0:19:42.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然可能会吵起来 但我觉得也不失为一件好事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.17,0:19:44.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好事？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.52,0:19:46.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是很好的事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.90,0:20:09.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚你是在七宫那里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.47,0:20:13.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好事？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.29,0:20:16.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是很好的事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.21,0:20:21.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好地吵一架吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.10,0:20:25.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常言道 打是亲 骂是爱 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.27,0:20:30.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我可没有半点想和你搞好关系的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.70,0:20:35.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 无论你多么想和我搞好关系 我都会拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.34,0:20:36.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会想那种事情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.80,0:20:40.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然你们两个感情很好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.48,0:20:42.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说不是了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.16,0:20:45.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇太
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.22,0:20:47.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 格尔松尼盎斯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.22,0:20:47.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(426,437)\fs21}Ghelzonianses
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.40,0:20:49.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话对你说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.77,0:20:50.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.36,0:20:54.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便拿了勇太的东西是我不好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.04,0:20:58.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 违反约定就是勇太的不对
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.92,0:21:04.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实 违反约定是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.68,0:21:08.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但以此为由就随便把别人的东西拿走也是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.32,0:21:10.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.96,0:21:11.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.58,0:21:12.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯有抗战到底了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.32,0:21:19.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后花了一整个晚上吵架后的结果
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.23,0:21:26.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成这样了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.11,0:21:27.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.84,0:21:28.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.04,0:21:31.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 偶尔这样也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.51,0:21:40.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们两个人是恋人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.65,0:22:05.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3}中二病也想谈{\r\3c&H880FF1&\be3}恋爱{\r\be3}！{\r\3c&H880FF1&\be3}恋  {\r\be3}全剧终
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,【OP】
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.58,0:01:07.38,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}I wanna fallin' LOVE.....
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.42,0:01:24.05,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}予感--… 夢が続く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.54,0:01:29.90,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}約束しても　心がどこかで怯えてるみたい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.50,0:01:33.00,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}ひとりじゃないって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.27,0:01:35.75,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}信じたいのに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.05,0:01:41.46,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}思い続けてる だけで幸せなんて言えないね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.64,0:01:47.26,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}虚ろな自信背負っていても　君が笑う
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.62,0:01:53.39,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}そして私の勇気になる 一つの言葉で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.52,0:01:55.99,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}君の世界を変えられたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.29,0:02:00.52,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}二つの恋が進化する
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.82,0:02:04.74,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}ホントだよ　巡らせた迷いが
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:07.09,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}見つけた答えは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.43,0:02:09.97,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}いつでも君に導かれた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.02,0:02:14.50,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}届ける覚悟が 様にならなくても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.68,0:02:17.26,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}素直に伝えたい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.26,0:02:19.91,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}ココロアルガママコエガキラメク
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.10,0:02:21.19,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}Real come on voice
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.42,0:02:25.70,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}響き渡るよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.42,0:01:24.05,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}预感--… 梦想延续
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.54,0:01:29.90,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}尽管许下约定 心中某处依旧胆怯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.50,0:01:33.00,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}你不是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.27,0:01:35.75,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}明明想要这样相信
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.05,0:01:41.46,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}思念不断滋生 但是却无法说出幸福二字
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.64,0:01:47.26,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}虽背负着虚无的自信 你依然嘴角上扬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.62,0:01:53.39,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}你的一句话就能成为我的勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.52,0:01:55.99,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}若能改变你的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.29,0:02:00.52,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}就能进化成为两份爱恋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.82,0:02:04.74,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}真的哦 冥思苦想依旧迷茫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:07.09,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}最终找到的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.43,0:02:09.97,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}无论何时都能引领着你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.02,0:02:14.50,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}就算没有做好能够传达给你的觉悟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.68,0:02:17.26,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}大声地说出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.26,0:02:19.91,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}心灵深处的声音熠熠生辉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.42,0:02:25.70,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be8}响亮地传达给他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,part2
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.58,0:01:07.38,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}I wanna fallin' LOVE.....
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.42,0:01:24.05,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}予感--… 夢が続く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.54,0:01:29.90,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}約束しても　心がどこかで怯えてるみたい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.50,0:01:33.00,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}ひとりじゃないって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.27,0:01:35.75,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}信じたいのに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.05,0:01:41.46,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}思い続けてる だけで幸せなんて言えないね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.64,0:01:47.26,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}虚ろな自信背負っていても　君が笑う
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.62,0:01:53.39,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}そして私の勇気になる 一つの言葉で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.52,0:01:55.99,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}君の世界を変えられたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.29,0:02:00.52,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}二つの恋が進化する
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.82,0:02:04.74,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}ホントだよ　巡らせた迷いが
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:07.09,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}見つけた答えは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.43,0:02:09.97,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}いつでも君に導かれた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.02,0:02:14.50,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}届ける覚悟が 様にならなくても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.68,0:02:17.26,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}素直に伝えたい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.26,0:02:19.91,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}ココロアルガママコエガキラメク
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.10,0:02:21.19,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}Real come on voice
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.42,0:02:25.70,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,470)}響き渡るよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.42,0:01:24.05,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}预感--… 梦想延续
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.54,0:01:29.90,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}尽管许下约定 心中某处依旧胆怯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.50,0:01:33.00,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}你不是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.27,0:01:35.75,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}明明想要这样相信
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.05,0:01:41.46,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}思念不断滋生 但是却无法说出幸福二字
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.64,0:01:47.26,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}虽背负着虚无的自信 你依然嘴角上扬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.62,0:01:53.39,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}你的一句话就能成为我的勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.52,0:01:55.99,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}若能改变你的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.29,0:02:00.52,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}就能进化成为两份爱恋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.82,0:02:04.74,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}真的哦 冥思苦想依旧迷茫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:07.09,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}最终找到的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.43,0:02:09.97,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}无论何时都能引领着你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.02,0:02:14.50,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}就算没有做好能够传达给你的觉悟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.68,0:02:17.26,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}大声地说出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.26,0:02:19.91,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}心灵深处的声音熠熠生辉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.42,0:02:25.70,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\pos(424,10)}响亮地传达给他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,part3
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.58,0:01:07.38,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}I wanna fallin' LOVE.....
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.42,0:01:24.05,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}予感--… 夢が続く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.54,0:01:29.90,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}約束しても　心がどこかで怯えてるみたい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.50,0:01:33.00,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}ひとりじゃないって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.27,0:01:35.75,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}信じたいのに
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.05,0:01:41.46,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}思い続けてる だけで幸せなんて言えないね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.64,0:01:47.26,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}虚ろな自信背負っていても　君が笑う
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.62,0:01:53.39,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}そして私の勇気になる 一つの言葉で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.52,0:01:55.99,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}君の世界を変えられたら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.29,0:02:00.52,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}二つの恋が進化する
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.82,0:02:04.74,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}ホントだよ　巡らせた迷いが
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:07.09,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}見つけた答えは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.43,0:02:09.97,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}いつでも君に導かれた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.02,0:02:14.50,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}届ける覚悟が 様にならなくても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.68,0:02:17.26,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}素直に伝えたい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.26,0:02:19.91,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}ココロアルガママコエガキラメク
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.10,0:02:21.19,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}Real come on voice
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.42,0:02:25.70,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,470)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur10\be6}響き渡るよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.42,0:01:24.05,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}预感--… 梦想延续
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.54,0:01:29.90,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}尽管许下约定 心中某处依旧胆怯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.50,0:01:33.00,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}你不是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.27,0:01:35.75,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}明明想要这样相信
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.05,0:01:41.46,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}思念不断滋生 但是却无法说出幸福二字
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.64,0:01:47.26,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}虽背负着虚无的自信 你依然嘴角上扬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.62,0:01:53.39,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}你的一句话就能成为我的勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.52,0:01:55.99,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}若能改变你的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.29,0:02:00.52,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}就能进化成为两份爱恋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.82,0:02:04.74,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}真的哦 冥思苦想依旧迷茫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:07.09,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}最终找到的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.43,0:02:09.97,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&HFF8000&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}无论何时都能引领着你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.02,0:02:14.50,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}就算没有做好能够传达给你的觉悟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.68,0:02:17.26,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}大声地说出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.26,0:02:19.91,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}心灵深处的声音熠熠生辉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.42,0:02:25.70,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be2\pos(424,10)\1c&H5400D7&\1a&H00&\bord0\blur12\be8}响亮地传达给他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.89,0:22:23.03,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&HDB00E9&}芽吹いた闇夜が 波乱へと爬行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.15,0:22:25.45,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&H56FF26&}わくわくするねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.03,0:22:30.16,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&HDB00E9&}七つの音 永劫より放たれて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.26,0:22:31.48,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&H56FF26&}どきどきするねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.59,0:22:35.42,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&H20FFF5&}魔鎚の烙印 暗礁に閃く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.54,0:22:37.38,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&HFBF72B&}まだ続ける気なの?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.45,0:22:41.19,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&H20FFF5&}愛の摂理に 極光瞬く
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.30,0:22:42.97,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&HFBF72B&}もう止めなさい…。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.07,0:22:48.49,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HDB00E9&}僕らは一つになり {\r\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFBF72B&}天を翔て
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.59,0:22:54.30,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&56FF26&}誇りを叫び散る{\r\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&H20FFF5&}花火のようだ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.40,0:22:59.72,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}輝(かがやき)は刹那に…爆ぜた!!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.08,0:23:05.65,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}道化は正義の鬣を奔らせて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.82,0:23:11.40,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}愚者は月影に虚妄を抱く
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.58,0:23:14.21,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}現実世界-ゲーム-が僕らを
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.33,0:23:17.17,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}追いつめるために存在(あ)るならば
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.29,0:23:22.28,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}せめて朽ちぬほどの馬鹿でありたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.37,0:23:27.47,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}励起する魂で吼えた―――…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.57,0:23:31.78,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}Van!shment Th!s World!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.89,0:22:23.03,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&HDB00E9&}方才伊始的闇夜 向波澜爬行而去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.15,0:22:25.45,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&H56FF26&}令人心动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.03,0:22:30.16,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&HDB00E9&}七音 由永恒的未来弹奏而出
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.26,0:22:31.48,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&H56FF26&}令人心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.59,0:22:35.42,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&H20FFF5&}魔锤的烙印 在暗礁上闪烁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.54,0:22:37.38,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&HFBF72B&}你还打算继续吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.45,0:22:41.19,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&H20FFF5&}在爱的法则面前 极光转瞬即逝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.30,0:22:42.97,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&HFBF72B&}住手吧…。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.07,0:22:48.49,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1\blur2\bord1\3c&HDB00E9&}我们将会合而为一 {\r\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFBF72B&}飞翔在天空中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.59,0:22:54.30,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&56FF26&}就像散漫自己的荣耀的{\r\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&H20FFF5&}烟花一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.40,0:22:59.72,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}光辉就在剎那间…爆发！！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.08,0:23:05.65,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}小丑赶跑了正义的鬣毛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.82,0:23:11.40,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}愚者在月影之中怀抱虚妄
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.58,0:23:14.21,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}现实世界-游戏-是为将我们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.33,0:23:17.17,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}追到穷途末路而存在的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.29,0:23:22.28,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}至少我想做一个不朽的笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.37,0:23:27.47,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}激昂的灵魂吼叫着---…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.57,0:23:31.78,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be6\blur8\bord1\3c&HFF35FF&}Van!shment Th!s World!!

