[Script Info]
Title:Chu2 Koi BD Short Movie 02 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00BB7E10,&H64F3A922,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.59,0:00:36.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正瘦金书_GBK\shad0\3c&H8F8F90&\blur3\fs32\bord2\fad(500,0)}6小时{\c0000ff\3c&H091AF4&\bord1}2{\cffffff\3c&H8F8F90&\bord2}4分钟前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.44,0:00:55.64,Default,,0,0,0,,已经无处可逃了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.77,0:00:59.62,Default,,0,0,0,,堂堂正正地与我决一死战吧  主人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.52,0:01:02.75,Default,,0,0,0,,不  小鸟游六花
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.82,0:01:06.40,Default,,0,0,0,,与你战斗没有任何意义
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.89,0:01:09.32,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么要背叛军队
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.68,0:01:13.31,Default,,0,0,0,,我还以为可以永远和你在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.10,0:01:17.26,Default,,0,0,0,,出现吧  迪克鲁特！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.10,0:01:17.26,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fs18\pos(345,328)}{\fsp-4}Dé{\fsp0}colle{\fsp-4}té{\fsp0}e
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.37,0:02:11.48,Default,,0,0,0,,我一直都很想和主人一决胜负
