[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2010-06-01 18:34:16
; // 版本: 0.74
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:KissXsis 01 gb
Original Script:HKG CASO SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0054538C,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default1,方正准圆_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0054538C,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: biaoti1,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00CD9BFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,4,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: biaoti2,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FBA064,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,4,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,23,&H00FF62FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H1E0F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: warn,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H0071403D,&H00EDB199,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,0,0,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.29,0:00:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.84,0:00:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许欺负圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.97,0:00:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了不许欺负他
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.74,0:00:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.57,0:00:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐 理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.22,0:00:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.11,0:00:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再让狗追也不要紧 姐姐们会保护你的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.02,0:00:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.75,0:00:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是圭太也是男孩子 要学会自己解决才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.12,0:00:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能学会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.76,0:00:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能的 一定能
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 到那时候姐姐们就不会和我在一起了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.26,0:00:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.44,0:00:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么可能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.59,0:00:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直都会陪着你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.17,0:01:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远都会
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.50,0:01:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？ 那我们来平时那个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.58,0:01:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭真是 不管长多大
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.44,0:01:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都那么爱撒娇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.00,0:01:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐…理香姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.08,0:01:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！受死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.25,0:01:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.98,0:01:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.43,0:01:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上课睡觉想必是因为睡眠不足吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.16,0:01:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.89,0:01:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有万人迷的亚香学姐和理香学姐做姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.39,0:01:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且她们俩居然好选不选 都对这废柴男死心塌地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.72,0:01:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坦白吧圭太 睡眠不足的原因到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.99,0:01:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别是整晚都在做叫人羡慕的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.33,0:01:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了多少次 我们可是姐弟啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.27,0:02:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能有那种工口漫画一样的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.05,0:02:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此话当真？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.58,0:02:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敢骗我们有你好看！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.06,0:02:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是真的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.96,0:02:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 我们可是姐弟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.01,0:02:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种工口漫画一样的剧情…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.00,0:02:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.55,0:02:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来啦 小圭x2
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.40,0:02:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼 适可而止点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.69,0:02:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐 理香姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.72,0:02:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种工口漫画一样的剧情…就发生在我家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.13,0:02:53.58,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Kiss me(Kiss me)　二人同時に恋したから　受け止めてよね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.58,0:02:59.56,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}空想(妄想)暴走しちゃってる　答えのないリアルなら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.60,0:03:02.58,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}夢を見たっていいんじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.60,0:03:07.51,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}シアワセ　エンドレス　未来　ツナガル　どこまでも
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.80,0:03:10.64,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}リア友には(隠しても)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.75,0:03:13.47,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}言っちゃう的な　(バレバレね)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.54,0:03:18.71,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ラブはいつもガチで駆け引き
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.02,0:03:24.70,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}デ·ジャ·ブみたい(ふたりいるよ)　秘密だけど　(ホンネは)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.79,0:03:29.99,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}私一人を見つめてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.30,0:03:35.65,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}教えてあげたい色んなこと(いけないこと)私が
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.92,0:03:38.90,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誘惑したはずなのに(ぬけがけはダメだよ)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.98,0:03:45.18,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}いつかマジな恋に　変わってた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.92,0:03:51.68,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Kiss me(Kiss me)　二人同時に愛したから　受け止めてよね
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.70,0:03:57.10,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Happy (Lucky)　なことたくさんしよう 好奇心止めないで
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.16,0:04:02.86,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Love me(Love me)　二人の違いを教えて　恋の大きさは
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.90,0:04:09.92,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}半分よりも二倍にして　幸せはエンドレスがいい

Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.95,0:04:19.84,biaoti1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(510,323)}Wonderful Days
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.76,0:04:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就再来一次
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.88,0:04:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来了 小圭x2
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.23,0:04:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要先吃饭？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.66,0:04:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是先洗澡？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.40,0:04:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说…先吃我？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.18,0:04:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么呀 真不知羞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.73,0:04:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饭洗澡之后就顺着接下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.52,0:04:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.54,0:04:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.43,0:04:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？ 问我？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.71,0:04:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看见理香的了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.10,0:04:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 啥看见不看见的 因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.48,0:04:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只看理香的 真赖皮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.28,0:04:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.96,0:04:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然都看了理香的 我也不能例外
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.10,0:05:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧 小圭！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.78,0:05:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.32,0:05:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 别老为这种事较劲好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.73,0:05:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.88,0:05:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太的潜台词是 亚香的搓衣板不值一看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.96,0:05:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不是跟我一个罩杯！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.65,0:05:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比你大两公分
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.70,0:05:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦人！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.07,0:05:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼 搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.15,0:05:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该说她们那叫天真无邪呢 还是清纯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.82,0:05:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直就和小时候一模一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.27,0:05:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说她们喜欢我不是件坏事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.67,0:06:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 味道真好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.30,0:06:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.16,0:06:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 手一滑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.46,0:06:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你就别管切了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.25,0:06:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我搅锅来 别让汤糊了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.93,0:06:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.31,0:06:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁这会儿准备好换的衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.62,0:06:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭差不多该洗完了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.96,0:06:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.40,0:06:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.86,0:06:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭的换洗衣服在哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.20,0:07:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.63,0:07:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态 这有变态
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.06,0:07:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香…你什么时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.11,0:07:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.54,0:07:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.23,0:07:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然要做的话 给你这个
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.59,0:07:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这个难道是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.24,0:07:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 这可不是一般的内裤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.60,0:07:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是圭太刚刚换下来的内裤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.36,0:07:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用浸满圭太的气味和汗水的这个蹭啊蹭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.58,0:07:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你是从哪弄来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.70,0:07:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 到底谁是变态啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.88,0:07:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把那个给我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.49,0:07:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不给
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.51,0:07:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别胡闹 快把那个给我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.53,0:07:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去和洗衣粉的气味蹭不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.14,0:07:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我的汤啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.80,0:07:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼 都在搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.70,0:07:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的内裤哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.70,0:08:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜呜…对不起小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.62,0:08:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.24,0:08:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过亚香姐会把饭做坏真是少见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.84,0:08:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不是因为对某人太过相信了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.28,0:08:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你试图偷跑的不对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.73,0:08:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算啦 先喝一杯吧 虽然是可乐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.06,0:08:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饭时不能喝可乐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.33,0:08:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是先吃这个吧 小圭张嘴～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.14,0:08:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个更不能吃吧 先干一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.13,0:08:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先吃一口嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.20,0:08:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个先不急…老爸老妈去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.22,0:08:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们参加街道组织的旅游去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.86,0:08:40.23,*Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}拜托看好家啊 姐弟要好好相处
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.74,0:08:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说得明天晚上才回家
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.08,0:08:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅游？ 晚上？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.49,0:08:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？ 你没听说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.66,0:08:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找他们俩有事？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.39,0:08:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 也没什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.55,0:08:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭真奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.43,0:08:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之今天晚上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.53,0:08:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只有我们几个x2
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.20,0:09:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在去哪门子旅游嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.44,0:09:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天的三方面谈该怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.50,0:09:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 真是不负责任的爹娘
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.30,0:09:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼 睡觉睡觉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.61,0:09:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚只有我们几个x2
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.92,0:09:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这样就OK了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.48,0:09:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好重…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.97,0:10:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.03,0:10:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.33,0:10:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.27,0:10:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.41,0:10:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 你们是怎么进来的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.98,0:10:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 我们可是姐弟啊 这可不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.87,0:10:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 只是西式问候而已嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.96,0:10:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候还自己讨来着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.72,0:10:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和小时候可不一样！快住手…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.73,0:10:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.03,0:10:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意别在意
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.46,0:10:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都这么伟岸了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.40,0:10:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.18,0:10:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是西式问候而已啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.91,0:10:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗 骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.66,0:10:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住 住手…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.34,0:11:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是梦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.43,0:11:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？ 咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.53,0:11:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 早上好 小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.49,0:11:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你着什么急啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.87,0:11:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.03,0:11:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.79,0:11:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 这么好的机会被浪费了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.42,0:11:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.86,0:11:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也上学去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.84,0:11:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 理香
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.13,0:11:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去把小圭的垃圾桶倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.83,0:11:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.55,0:11:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许闻！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.70,0:11:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.88,0:12:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…

Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.50,0:12:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太学长
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.63,0:12:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了  请用这个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.80,0:12:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是三日月啊  别吓我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.19,0:13:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是干劲十足呢 别的三年级学生都忙着备考
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.08,0:13:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还来晨练
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.37,0:13:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长是因为拿到推荐了所以淡定了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.96,0:13:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算…算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.22,0:13:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太学长请等着我  明年我也会进入同一所高中
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.64,0:13:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会再次担任圭太学长的经理人的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.44,0:13:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫做我的经理人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.49,0:13:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说也该是田径部的经理人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.91,0:13:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细节不必在意  对我来说别的部员根本不算一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.65,0:13:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.26,0:13:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太学长  放学的时候再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.11,0:13:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放学的时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.56,0:13:58.73,*Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}1467年  细川胜元等有力守护大名引起的应仁之乱…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.44,0:13:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三方面谈啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.80,0:14:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说小圭还没有告诉班主任
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.83,0:14:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打算放弃推荐参加高中考试的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.58,0:14:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说  以小圭现在的成绩要考上是挺玄的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.61,0:14:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三方面谈也很重要呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.12,0:14:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.56,0:14:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭  快点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.21,0:14:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢吞吞的小心迟到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.48,0:14:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了实现梦想的高中生活  现在就要…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.25,0:14:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.96,0:14:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.99,0:14:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我头疼  要早退
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.56,0:14:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.98,0:14:50.72,*Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}参加三方面谈的人请到职员室
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.14,0:14:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去也不是办法  走一步是一步了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.81,0:14:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是赶上了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.45,0:15:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎我们想到一块去了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.29,0:15:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是小圭重要的三方面谈的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.57,0:15:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了小圭也要努力尝试一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.40,0:15:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.20,0:15:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…那是做梦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.71,0:15:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.17,0:15:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.22,0:15:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有理香学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.55,0:15:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 亚香学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.38,0:15:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是理香学姐！？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.96,0:15:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.89,0:15:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天有何贵干？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.03,0:15:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来给您带路吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.36,0:15:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.24,0:15:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不用了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.59,0:15:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香  走这边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.40,0:15:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请等等啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.94,0:15:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们学校的男生啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.56,0:15:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.56,0:16:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 小圭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.06,0:16:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.40,0:16:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我～好～幸～福～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.18,0:16:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.08,0:16:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香学姐　也踹我吧　对这里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.74,0:16:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.56,0:16:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼　那两个人在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.28,0:16:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事情那么吵啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.98,0:16:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊　又是那家的姐弟
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.57,0:16:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫什么来着
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.53,0:16:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,D班的住之江…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.02,0:16:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.85,0:16:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说跟两个双胞胎姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.46,0:16:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每晚都过着酒池肉林的生活 是性之大魔人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.56,0:16:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.81,0:16:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐们也不成体统
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.61,0:16:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前阵子甚至特地跑来学校跟弟弟告白
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.60,0:16:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传言也不完全是假的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.75,0:16:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样  姐弟…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.96,0:16:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开让开
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.13,0:17:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.51,0:17:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.99,0:17:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.81,0:17:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住之江圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.80,0:17:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之是对不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.80,0:17:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在赶时间
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.82,0:17:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我站住
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.17,0:17:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三国  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.60,0:17:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香学姐  也对我来一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.35,0:17:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请听听我创作的歌曲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.00,0:17:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  请让我们过去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.01,0:17:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有要紧的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.79,0:17:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们适可而止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.12,0:17:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐  理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.03,0:17:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.11,0:17:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.41,0:17:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个场面我都觉得不好办了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.38,0:17:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么不早点出来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.91,0:17:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.23,0:18:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐你们到底是为什么来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.45,0:18:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也知道你们一来就会造成大骚动的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.66,0:18:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前也是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.00,0:18:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那是…但我们…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.70,0:18:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是为了圭太来的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.00,0:18:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你们真的为我考虑就不要再到这里来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.37,0:18:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐们来了会给我添麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.76,0:18:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…麻烦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.22,0:18:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  不用说到这份上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.38,0:18:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  亚香学姐和理香学姐无论什么时候来我们都热烈欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.13,0:18:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们觉得高兴  我可一点也不高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.65,0:18:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天还有重要的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.20,0:18:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩赶快给我回去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.08,0:18:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是为了这件重要的事情来的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.56,0:18:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看起来是我们太自作主张了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.20,0:18:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起啊  小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.80,0:18:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.61,0:19:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.44,0:19:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…为什么会掉在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.82,0:19:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说  亚香姐和理香姐是为了这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.74,0:19:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐  理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.79,0:19:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他生我们的气了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.30,0:19:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不过毕竟是我们给他添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.19,0:19:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐  理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.01,0:19:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.31,0:19:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.09,0:19:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  亚香姐  理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.03,0:20:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我没听你们解释
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.50,0:20:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没考虑到姐姐们的心情  就说了过分的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.16,0:20:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.22,0:20:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.20,0:20:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在大家面前这样做啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.86,0:20:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐和理香姐毕竟是我姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.57,0:20:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也没办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.53,0:20:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙在搞什么  刚才突然发火  现在又算哪一出啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.40,0:20:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们成小丑了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.88,0:20:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光对亚香理香学姐这样 太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.32,0:20:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在众人面前那样做？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.48,0:20:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说傻话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.20,0:20:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前就说过了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.73,0:21:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你们的妈妈双方都是带着孩子再婚的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.72,0:21:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太是我的儿子  而你们俩是妈妈的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.40,0:21:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说你们根本没有血缘关系
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.29,0:21:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用在意他人眼光  尽情地上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.71,0:21:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情地！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.57,0:21:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情地…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.81,0:21:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.96,0:21:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.90,0:21:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了圭太  亚香和理香在是你姐姐之前
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.13,0:21:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更是正当妙龄的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.51,0:21:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算无视女孩子的感情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.69,0:21:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸我不记得自己是这样教育你的！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.98,0:21:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太将来是要跟亚香结婚吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.74,0:21:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀  还是说要跟理香呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.29,0:21:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并没有…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.22,0:21:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是这样说  其实你想要香吻都想得心痒痒了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.35,0:21:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.49,0:21:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.42,0:21:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭真是 不管长多大
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.12,0:21:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都那么爱撒娇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.12,0:22:09.17,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Teady Boy 大切な Our! Steady Boy
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.19,0:22:12.56,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誰より一番　そばにいさせてね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.58,0:22:17.97,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}このいとしさは本物　ずっとずっと大好き
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.43,0:22:31.98,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}キュンてするのシンクロ ドキッてするのもシンクロ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.99,0:22:37.45,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねぇなんでだろ ハートが騒ぐたび盛り上がる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.50,0:22:43.13,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}「私1回しゃべった」 「私3回目が合った」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.15,0:22:48.64,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もしかしたら...や! 実際 ほんとは恋敵なのにね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.70,0:22:54.06,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}二人して片想いなんてウケる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.08,0:23:01.00,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}カッコ悪い けど楽しい　争奪フリアレ あ、ほら彼が来た!!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.10,0:23:06.03,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Teady Boy 生意気な My! Steady Boy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.06,0:23:12.32,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}おはようさえ言ってくれない　微笑み返しもしてくんない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.33,0:23:17.10,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}でもね ほっとけない Our! Steady Boy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.12,0:23:20.54,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねぇ彼のこと　何とかしたいよね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.55,0:23:25.94,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}このときめきは　ぱなくて　今日も作戦ミーティング
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.37,0:23:28.89,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}どうよ? どうやってアピる!?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.84,0:23:49.78,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(195,188)\blur2}一对一授课
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.81,0:23:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭终于开始努力学习准备参加玉秀高中考试了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.07,0:23:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  但是合格率只有50%啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.32,0:23:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  这里就交给姐姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.91,0:23:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香老师会教你珍藏的学习方法的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.70,0:23:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一集  一对一授课
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.09,0:23:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你一个吻


