[Script Info]
;  This is a Sub Station Alpha v4 script.
;  For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
;  go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
;  or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
;  Script created by cySub 1.4.0 Release Build 1203
; 
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2010-12-18 16:46:24
; // 版本: 0.74
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0054538C,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default1,方正准圆_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0054538C,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H0054538C,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: biaoti1,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00CD9BFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: biaoti2,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FBA064,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ed,ＤＦブラッシュＲＤW7,23,&H00FF62FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H1E0F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: warn,方正准圆_GBK,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H0071403D,&H00EDB199,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,0,0,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.18,0:01:14.63,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Kiss me(Kiss me)　二人同時に恋したから　受け止めてよね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.63,0:01:20.61,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}空想(妄想)暴走しちゃってる　答えのないリアルなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.65,0:01:23.63,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}夢を見たっていいんじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.65,0:01:28.56,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}シアワセ　エンドレス　未来　ツナガル　どこまでも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.85,0:01:31.69,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}リア友には(隠しても)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.80,0:01:34.52,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}言っちゃう的な　(バレバレね)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.59,0:01:39.76,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ラブはいつもガチで駆け引き
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.07,0:01:45.75,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}デ·ジャ·ブみたい(ふたりいるよ)　秘密だけど　(ホンネは)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.84,0:01:51.04,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}私一人を見つめてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.35,0:01:56.70,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}教えてあげたい色んなこと(いけないこと)私が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.97,0:01:59.95,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誘惑したはずなのに(ぬけがけはダメだよ)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.03,0:02:06.23,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}いつかマジな恋に　変わってた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.97,0:02:12.73,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Kiss me(Kiss me)　二人同時に愛したから　受け止めてよね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.75,0:02:18.15,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Happy (Lucky)　なことたくさんしよう 好奇心止めないで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.21,0:02:23.91,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Love me(Love me)　二人の違いを教えて　恋の大きさは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.95,0:02:30.97,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}半分よりも二倍にして　幸せはエンドレスがいい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.32,0:22:09.37,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Teady Boy 大切な Our! Steady Boy
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.39,0:22:12.76,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}誰より一番　そばにいさせてね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.78,0:22:18.17,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}このいとしさは本物　ずっとずっと大好き
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.63,0:22:32.18,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}キュンてするのシンクロ ドキッてするのもシンクロ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.19,0:22:37.65,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねぇなんでだろ ハートが騒ぐたび盛り上がる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.70,0:22:43.33,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}「私1回しゃべった」 「私3回目が合った」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.35,0:22:48.84,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もしかしたら...や! 実際 ほんとは恋敵なのにね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.90,0:22:54.26,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}二人して片想いなんてウケる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.28,0:23:01.20,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}カッコ悪い けど楽しい　争奪フリアレ あ、ほら彼が来た!!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.30,0:23:06.23,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Teady Boy 生意気な My! Steady Boy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.26,0:23:12.52,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}おはようさえ言ってくれない　微笑み返しもしてくんない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.53,0:23:17.30,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}でもね ほっとけない Our! Steady Boy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.32,0:23:20.74,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねぇ彼のこと　何とかしたいよね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.75,0:23:26.14,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}このときめきは　ぱなくて　今日も作戦ミーティング
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.57,0:23:29.09,ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}どうよ? どうやってアピる!?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.60,0:00:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…这情况下slut会更接近题意
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.60,0:00:09.86,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（slut：妓女 囧…）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.88,0:00:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很重要 明白了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.23,0:00:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用了slut的例句是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.40,0:00:18.21,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}瞧一瞧看一看 甩了甩了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.40,0:00:20.78,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}今天上到好货色喽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.79,0:00:23.20,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}这么大的山药才80块一个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.29,0:00:28.10,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}再加上秋葵和纳豆  就是稠糊糊的三角关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.37,0:00:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨子烧肉加煮蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.31,0:00:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撒上一点调味料
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.55,0:00:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷面马上就做好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.22,0:00:30.38,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}来买啦来买啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.88,0:00:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.95,0:00:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.80,0:00:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.31,0:00:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,slut slut…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.63,0:00:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏季庙会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.00,0:02:42.00,biaoti1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(490,325)}八月的固定节目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.10,0:02:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎么样 舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.11,0:02:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从书上…研究来的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.10,0:02:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊对 就是那里 那里舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.96,0:02:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.83,0:02:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.03,0:03:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？预科学校的特别夏季补习班
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.18,0:03:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 很不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.57,0:03:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比学校教的东西好懂多了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.67,0:03:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3Q 多亏你介绍个好地方给我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.85,0:03:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过那我也没去过 是听朋友说的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.13,0:03:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面转过来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.85,0:03:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.20,0:03:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等啦 该吃夜宵了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.99,0:03:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚 亚香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.96,0:03:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 这 这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.20,0:03:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么快就到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.40,0:03:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚就到这里吧 要加油啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.48,0:03:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜宵我就放桌子上了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.90,0:03:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完把盘子拿出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.78,0:04:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.32,0:04:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 最近他们仨突然很爽朗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.55,0:04:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气氛那么安静 又稍微有那么点紧张感
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.02,0:04:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是理想的The·备考生和其姐姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.61,0:04:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家说备考生都要在夏天分出高下呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.68,0:04:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是件好事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.36,0:04:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是件好事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.86,0:04:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放松一下放松一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.70,0:04:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的事 还有这样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.28,0:04:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但都是没办法的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.90,0:04:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为又热又挤
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.32,0:04:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贴得又近 还是晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.99,0:04:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天的回忆真难忘啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.25,0:05:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,备考生的休息日 就在这一天
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.63,0:05:09.55,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(0,800)}（弟祭！姐祭！永恒不灭！夏天回忆之亲亲热热狂欢大作战）
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.12,0:05:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正所谓暴风雨前的宁静嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.04,0:05:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 暴风雨嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.86,0:05:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭要和我去看庙会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.50,0:05:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么呢 该和我去才对
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.88,0:05:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛痛…快停手 我们三个一起去不好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.58,0:05:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.65,0:05:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.13,0:05:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别乱来啊 我又不能一分为二
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.96,0:05:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.08,0:05:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这招啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.68,0:05:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕和疼只有开始那一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.53,0:05:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就会舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.68,0:06:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我积攒了很多压力啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.68,0:06:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锵锵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.25,0:06:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.51,0:06:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.33,0:06:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.90,0:06:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.16,0:06:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.21,0:06:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.52,0:06:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也让我们品尝一下夏天的酸酸甜甜中元节吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.73,0:06:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下一张充满大家回忆的照片！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.06,0:06:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少再让我们看一眼！拜托了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.21,0:06:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.12,0:07:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这搞什么吗 也太挤了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.63,0:07:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真吵
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.60,0:07:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 庙会就得是这样才行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.20,0:07:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 放松一下放松一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.21,0:07:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是安静的地方适合放松
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.41,0:07:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.36,0:07:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.23,0:07:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走！我走还不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.25,0:07:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以快放手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.80,0:07:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都跑哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.50,0:07:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得人家来叫 也没想想就来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.53,0:07:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可还是在家念书比较好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.90,0:07:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前穿的浴衣又那么紧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.72,0:08:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.25,0:08:03.73,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}来这边啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.79,0:08:05.64,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}别在这里吵啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.88,0:08:04.81,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}要去那边
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.74,0:08:07.96,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}还是这边好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.98,0:08:09.59,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}你老是那么爱强迫人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.61,0:08:12.14,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}怎么会 你瞧还是这边好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.21,0:08:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 就得来这边
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.48,0:08:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住 住之江同学
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.33,0:08:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得 得赶紧跑…现在马上！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.10,0:08:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.22,0:08:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.85,0:08:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.10,0:09:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.68,0:09:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为 为啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.73,0:09:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.35,0:09:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说和理香姐彻底走散了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.45,0:09:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事 过会儿就能看见她了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.35,0:09:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.78,0:09:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟她也想让小圭放松一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.43,0:09:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗 难得的庙会…好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.22,0:09:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.53,0:09:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 放松一下放松一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.41,0:10:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.00,0:10:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没创意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.80,0:10:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀旧有啥不好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.70,0:10:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我内心小鹿乱撞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.30,0:10:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庙会  这都是庙会的错吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.22,0:10:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭也来一口吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.25,0:10:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.07,0:10:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次倒不要了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.91,0:10:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.23,0:10:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候去庙会时
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.38,0:10:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭啊  死缠烂打要跟姐姐吃同一个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.80,0:10:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果三人吃了一个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.01,0:10:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭那时真可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.07,0:10:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这回事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.62,0:10:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.05,0:10:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.73,0:11:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.00,0:11:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小 鸡 鸡 X4
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.85,0:11:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,软绵绵的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.86,0:11:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.35,0:11:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭  帮我抓掉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.72,0:11:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.68,0:11:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再深入点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.63,0:11:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭  那里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.80,0:11:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.81,0:11:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.62,0:11:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.81,0:11:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干啥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.51,0:11:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.30,0:11:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.76,0:11:56.97,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}真是的  总是在正热火的时候来捣乱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.78,0:12:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住之江同学他们  又做出那种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.32,0:12:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  突然…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.72,0:12:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.46,0:12:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.47,0:12:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次该我了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.08,0:12:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞎说个啥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.88,0:12:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.28,0:12:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.45,0:12:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.10,0:12:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.00,0:12:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧  姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.38,0:12:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要哪个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.03,0:13:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你扯啥啊  理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.66,0:13:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切  又走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.21,0:13:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香也一样是想让圭太放松下的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.26,0:13:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷清啊  为什么要来这
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.52,0:13:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太还怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.08,0:13:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「还」是什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.12,0:13:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.56,0:13:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候去庙会时的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.21,0:13:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷路进了树林的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.15,0:13:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭太一直扯着我们的袖子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.46,0:13:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说怕黑要离开
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.22,0:13:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为圭太是胆小鬼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.23,0:13:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁怕啊  又不是小孩了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.00,0:13:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  还可以更深入吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.40,0:13:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深入？去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.00,0:13:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更黑暗幽静的  灵·山·宝·地
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.70,0:14:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是庙会怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.72,0:14:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要找亚香姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.69,0:14:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不就是庙会吗  只属于两人的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.43,0:14:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.51,0:14:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理…理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.48,0:14:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不害怕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.41,0:14:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会去…吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.21,0:14:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.20,0:14:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.00,0:14:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.87,0:14:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.90,0:14:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  恭喜
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.55,0:14:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洋溢着开放感的夏天是最危险的季节
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.63,0:14:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须好好指导学生们不沉湎于花花世界的诱惑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.65,0:14:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比方说在这种店铺的后面…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.90,0:15:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.19,0:15:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是住之江姐弟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.22,0:15:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是战斗  登上成人阶梯的盛夏夜之战
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.15,0:15:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.31,0:15:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为教师
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.30,0:15:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.50,0:15:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  身为一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.90,0:15:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.46,0:15:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐弟什么的是不可原谅的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.12,0:15:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙  开溜了圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.02,0:15:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.86,0:15:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都叫你们站住了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.23,0:15:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.00,0:15:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎能因这么点事而放弃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.56,0:15:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了学生要不惜拼上性命
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.67,0:15:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越是困难越能体现真正的价值
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.90,0:15:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是教育  这才是爱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.14,0:15:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  是爱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.40,0:15:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上天啊  这是「劳我筋骨 饿我体肤」的精神吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.20,0:15:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吧  兼续大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.70,0:16:01.60,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(200,0)}这是山中鹿之助说的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.90,0:16:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐生夕月  出发
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.52,0:16:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕月…夕月已经尽了最大努力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.31,0:16:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兼续大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.80,0:16:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何其凄凉哉  只剩头盔可凭吊  凄惨蝈鸣伴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.60,0:16:43.25,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(200,0)}那是芭蕉说的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.73,0:16:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.97,0:16:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于跟两人都走散了么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.20,0:16:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  圭太学长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.57,0:17:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿咻嘿咻…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.72,0:17:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三…三日月  你在搞啥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.10,0:17:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年的神轿小姐是我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.31,0:17:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神轿小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.95,0:17:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  性感吗 诱人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.49,0:17:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像盛夏的妖精吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.78,0:17:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…呃…嗯  挺可爱的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.40,0:17:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.35,0:17:36.76,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}大伙们  嘿咻嘿咻…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.38,0:17:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  慢着…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.90,0:17:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也没空位
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.60,0:17:50.01,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}嘿咻嘿咻…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.29,0:17:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这搞什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.44,0:18:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这过的什么夏季庙会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.31,0:18:07.23,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}圭太
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.32,0:18:11.53,Default1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.90,0:18:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚香你这什么样子  黏黏糊糊的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.80,0:18:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理香你才是  大汗淋漓  头发上还黏着蜘蛛网
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.90,0:18:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人都灰头土脸的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.52,0:18:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭（圭太）才是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.52,0:18:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  好失败的夏季庙会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.05,0:18:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确  这想忘都忘不了呢  糟糕透顶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.39,0:18:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我们为什么会笑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.26,0:18:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.27,0:19:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大声叫喊会让心情舒畅嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.60,0:19:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么莫名其妙的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.51,0:19:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憋不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.92,0:19:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能在这…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.55,0:19:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  快开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.90,0:19:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要放烟火了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.71,0:19:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你去哪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.52,0:19:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭（圭太）
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.81,0:19:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.60,0:19:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊  请饶恕我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.05,0:19:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要漏出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.51,0:19:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住了…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.60,0:20:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.10,0:20:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小便…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.03,0:21:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  小圭回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.54,0:21:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.34,0:21:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烟火都要放完了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.20,0:21:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭（圭太）…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.99,0:23:49.99,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(205,188)\bord4\blur2}临阵要磨枪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.80,0:23:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  有种护身符在应考时很灵验？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.28,0:23:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.06,0:23:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都是为了小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.15,0:23:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狠下心来  我拔
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.67,0:23:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.29,0:23:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一集
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.05,0:23:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临阵要磨枪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.95,0:23:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你一个吻
