[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2013-09-15 19:02:25
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: Nakaimo 01
Original Script: SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H004528D7,&H802917B0,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPFuun-W7,18,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正毡笔黑简体,22,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: EDJP,DFPHSMincho-W9,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,10,10,6,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,10,10,6,1
Style: Title,方正毡笔黑简体,26,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP2,@DFPFuun-W7,18,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,1,2,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPCN2,@方正毡笔黑简体,22,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,1,2,0,5,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------OPJP--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.30,0:01:51.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}言ったでしょ　抜けがけ禁止なんだけど
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.53,0:01:54.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}言ったよね　好きだもん　おさえらんないっ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.68,0:01:57.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}今すぐに　友好条約破棄して
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.87,0:02:01.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}love me love me　もっと　わたしだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.74,0:02:14.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}この恋に　限りなく　ウンメイを　感じちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.11,0:02:19.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}なのになんで　矢印が1234　嘘　アリエナイ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.45,0:02:24.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}わたしより　可愛いコ　映さないで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.88,0:02:27.82,OPJP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(20,180)}ダメだって瞳をガードガード
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.85,0:02:32.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}火花散って　ごめんなさい　choose me my ダーリン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.89,0:02:39.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}わかるよ　最初から　みんな　ヒロイン志望
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.64,0:02:47.16,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}最高の　最愛の　たったひとりに　なりたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.51,0:02:50.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}優しいだけじゃ困る
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.69,0:02:53.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ぎゅっと奪ってほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.10,0:03:00.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}事情とか　ぬきにして　正直に恋して
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.31,0:03:06.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}傷ついたっていい　あなたに決めたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.11,0:03:07.00,OPJP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(20,180)}約束
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.90,0:03:09.16,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}友情だって大切
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.98,0:03:10.59,OPJP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(20,180)}それなのに
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.10,0:03:12.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}非常事態じゃしょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.51,0:03:16.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}誰がライバル　わたしを選んで
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------OPCN--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.30,0:01:51.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我可说过吧  偷跑可是禁止的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.53,0:01:54.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我可说过哦  喜欢你已经不能克制
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.68,0:01:57.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}现在马上撤销友好条约
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.87,0:02:01.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}{\fn華康布丁體\fs20}love me love me{\r}  更加地仅仅爱我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.74,0:02:14.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}这份恋情中  我感受到命运的味道四处弥漫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.11,0:02:19.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但是为什么  箭矢的印记  1234  骗人  不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.45,0:02:24.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}比起我来  不要将视线  转向更可爱的她
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.88,0:02:27.82,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(620,180)}不可以眼睛突然放光
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.85,0:02:32.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}一不小心就火星四射  对不起  {\fn華康布丁體\fs20}choose me my darling
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.89,0:02:39.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我可是知道的哦  从最初开始大家就都想要成为女主角
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.64,0:02:47.16,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}最好的最爱的仅有的那一人  祈祷会是我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.51,0:02:50.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}只是温柔的话我会困扰哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.69,0:02:53.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}想要你紧紧地争夺我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.10,0:03:00.27,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}麻烦的事情统统省略掉  坦率地来恋爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.31,0:03:06.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}即使受伤也没关系  已经决定是你了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.11,0:03:07.00,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(620,180)}约定了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.90,0:03:09.16,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}友情虽然也很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.98,0:03:10.59,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(620,180)}即使如此
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.10,0:03:12.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}紧急状况无法抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.51,0:03:16.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}谁才是敌手  请选择我吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------EDJP--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.25,0:22:25.25,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}走りだした恋はエデンを探してる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.25,0:22:32.02,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}あなたからの引力　戸惑いながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.21,0:22:36.65,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}わたしわかってたよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.89,0:22:42.24,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}ふたりは果実にふれたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.43,0:22:48.51,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}切ないウソが出会いを責めるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.51,0:22:54.32,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}傷つくだけじゃないと言って？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.52,0:23:01.79,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}やさしいその手でさらってくれる明日は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.19,0:23:07.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}ずっと過去からの約束
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.13,0:23:11.96,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}きっと結ばれる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.12,0:23:14.92,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}だって信じてる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.12,0:23:20.75,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}ときめくココロはもうとまらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.12,0:23:23.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}やっとはじまるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.12,0:23:31.85,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}そんな愛しさで眩しい世界へと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.00,0:23:34.80,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}迷わずに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.01,0:23:38.43,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}Heavenly lover
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------EDCN--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.25,0:22:25.25,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}勇敢迈出的恋情  寻找着伊甸园的踪迹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.25,0:22:32.02,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}你所释放的引力  虽令我踌躇不前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.21,0:22:36.65,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}但我可是知道的哟
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.89,0:22:42.24,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}两个人触碰到了恋爱的果实
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.43,0:22:48.51,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}悲伤的谎言苛责着这份相会
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.51,0:22:54.32,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}你说这不仅只是刻印的伤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.52,0:23:01.79,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}那双温柔的手中攫取的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.19,0:23:07.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}一定  将过去的约定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.13,0:23:11.96,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}一直  连结在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.12,0:23:14.92,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}因为  我一直相信着
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.12,0:23:20.75,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}小鹿乱撞的心情已经无法停止
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.12,0:23:23.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}终于  得以开始
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.12,0:23:31.85,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}和可爱的你共同迈向耀眼的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.00,0:23:34.80,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}不再迷茫
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.01,0:23:38.43,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}Heavenly lover
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------Title--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.53,0:03:22.82,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(479,286)}绽放的妹妹们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.00,0:24:10.07,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(311,91)\fs25\fsp-1}妹妹的陷阱
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------Staff--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}本字幕由澄空学园&华盟字幕社联合制作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片源：阿爽 / 10thMystery  翻译：ゾンビ / 巫贼  校对：detectivexsc\N特效：AfterFX  后期：yjywybb / Lantis  繁化：阿爽
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------EP--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.95,0:00:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我还真是吓了一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.33,0:00:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人真是的  突然惊慌失措地冲进来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.27,0:00:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.89,0:00:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  有点兴奋过度了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.63,0:00:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.60,0:00:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就能证明柚璃奈真的是我妹妹了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.25,0:00:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人真讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.40,0:00:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话从刚才起都说几回了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.85,0:00:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.80,0:00:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.21,0:00:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我突然想到一个点子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.97,0:00:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的派对  能选我作为同行的伴侣吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.65,0:00:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说没能带恋人去参加
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.55,0:00:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但若同行的是身为亲戚的我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.58,0:00:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹿野子夫人想必就不会非常生气了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.39,0:00:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同行去参加派对的并非都是恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.05,0:01:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带家人去参加也是很正常的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.22,0:01:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家人…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.76,0:01:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了  因为我的真实身份是无法公之于众的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.56,0:01:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就让我以从表妹的身份尽一份力
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.02,0:01:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为兄长大人的家人  作为妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.02,0:01:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亮相于世人面前…吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.24,0:01:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柚璃奈…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.07,0:01:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.84,0:01:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很在意朋友们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.08,0:01:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…是的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.36,0:01:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就无需担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.35,0:01:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,养育我长大的是熊五郎大人的父亲的表亲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.33,0:01:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在集团里也有一定的发言权
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.27,0:01:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拜托他们再多准备一些请帖就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.01,0:01:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  柚璃奈
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.30,0:00:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.09,0:03:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人…你很紧张吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.11,0:03:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒也不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.02,0:03:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的话需要我贴身随行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.16,0:03:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  别开我玩笑啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.17,0:03:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎赴宴  国立同学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.68,0:03:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承蒙邀请  不胜光荣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.92,0:03:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝野学长…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.68,0:03:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.02,0:03:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱菜到达目的地
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.30,0:03:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天导会长  这样很危险的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.06,0:03:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不行哦  凛香
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.60,0:04:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是受邀而来的  所以要好好打招呼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.59,0:04:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟君  感谢邀请
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.90,0:04:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.52,0:04:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你们在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.32,0:04:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲切的蹭脸抱哦  我蹭我蹭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.70,0:04:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要抱到什么时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.82,0:04:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.54,0:04:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么接下来轮到心乃枝了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.82,0:04:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个  那么就…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.30,0:04:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嵯峨良学姐  你这身衣服…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.41,0:04:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是魔女的正装  有这么奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.36,0:04:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.78,0:04:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干…干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.09,0:04:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  舞会那时的礼服虽说很不错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.84,0:04:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但今天这身也很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.90,0:05:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  快点去派对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.02,0:05:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱菜太期待宴会料理了  连午饭都没吃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.55,0:05:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在肚子都快饿瘪了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.08,0:05:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天导会长
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.50,0:05:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此  那就赶紧准备进场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.81,0:05:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  那么我给大家带路
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.68,0:05:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,料理料理
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.52,0:05:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可事实上  基于动荡起伏的社会经济形势
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.05,0:05:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我集团依旧被诸多严峻的问题所困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.18,0:05:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中每个都是无法忽视的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.08,0:05:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了在这般状况中逆境求生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.11,0:05:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今后更会齐心协力共度难关
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.17,0:05:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我还有许多想和大家说的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.71,0:05:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但俗话说  致词如同裙子  越短越好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.77,0:05:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就不占用大家的时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.29,0:06:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  妈妈的致词还是一如既往地长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.03,0:06:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.13,0:06:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.13,0:06:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.19,0:06:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…这个味道不错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.70,0:06:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许能添加到LYRICAL☆SISTERS的新菜单里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.69,0:06:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.12,0:06:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.12,0:06:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是本酒店特制的鲜榨葡萄汁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.15,0:06:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那是IT业界知名的原霸主——奈亚盖尔氏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.73,0:06:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Oh…Nice to meet you
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.35,0:06:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是帝野少主吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.91,0:06:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.78,0:06:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫帝野将悟
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.46,0:06:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Oh! Very  good!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.37,0:07:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,IT业界的人果然都会转陶轮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.37,0:07:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs16}注：此处的捏他来自某推特用户的提问「为什么IT人士在聊天时都喜欢\N摆出转陶轮的手势」，具体见将悟的手势。仔细想想似乎的确如此
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.25,0:07:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝野
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.30,0:07:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嵯峨良学姐  再怎么为自己店里着想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.81,0:07:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能老是偷窃别人的料理菜单哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.76,0:07:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像一直没看到神凪  你有见到过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.55,0:07:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.70,0:07:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好像不在会场里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.68,0:07:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是去厕所了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.82,0:07:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就谢天谢地了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.84,0:07:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神凪从今天乘上轿车之后就很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.40,0:07:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很是心不在焉…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.56,0:07:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在考虑心事的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.18,0:07:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.27,0:07:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…好像雅突然不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.65,0:07:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手机也打不通
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.59,0:07:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防万一我觉得还是去找下她比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.50,0:07:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是雅那家伙…到底跑哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.40,0:07:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是迷路了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.54,0:08:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…濑利小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.34,0:08:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  拜托濑利小姐帮我们一起找的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.07,0:08:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟君  是我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.83,0:08:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衣楠…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.34,0:08:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.30,0:08:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  果然在存放于保险柜的物品里找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.90,0:08:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  这样关于熊五郎大人丑闻的证据就确凿了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.32,0:08:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遗憾的是并没有可以直接证明他有私生子的办法
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.69,0:08:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但信封和信纸都是特别定制的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.94,0:08:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笔迹也大概是本人的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.32,0:08:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切按照计划进行的话  定能把将悟少爷拉下社长候补之位
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.69,0:08:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我拉下社长候补之位？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.95,0:08:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  你也多多加油
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.57,0:08:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后见
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.66,0:08:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衣楠  这是什么情况
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.33,0:08:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点  将悟君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.57,0:08:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来濑利秘书是属于不想让你当上社长的那一派的爪牙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.42,0:08:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.66,0:09:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近我发现她的行为有些古怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.31,0:09:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以变装之后潜伏在她周围
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.80,0:09:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到她居然在谋划着这样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.44,0:09:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事得赶紧告诉妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.13,0:09:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈肯定也被濑利小姐蒙在鼓里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.47,0:09:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.72,0:09:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前鹿野子氏肯定完全信任濑利秘书
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.40,0:09:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我们并没有足以说服她的客观证据
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.79,0:09:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且要是现在就说出去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.40,0:09:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,势必会让鹿野子氏知道私生子的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.75,0:09:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟君你已经做好保护妹妹的准备了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.88,0:09:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.15,0:09:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到底该如何是好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.99,0:09:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹿野子氏肯定也知道在集团中有自己的敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.09,0:09:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人可不是这么容易就能击败的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.50,0:09:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是…这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.94,0:09:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之现在还是要继续跟踪  抓住她的把柄
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.98,0:09:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证会竭尽全力的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.78,0:09:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那就拜托你了  衣楠
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.54,0:09:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  将悟君也要千万小心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.29,0:10:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  濑利小姐居然背叛妈妈  还欺骗了我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.42,0:10:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给这样的人做DNA鉴定
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.80,0:10:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直是把妹妹的真相给她双手奉上
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.66,0:10:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.92,0:10:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  发生什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.68,0:10:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…神凪同学…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.87,0:10:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到神凪同学了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.25,0:10:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.36,0:10:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  你不是在找神凪同学吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.57,0:10:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.79,0:10:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮我找到她真是帮大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.66,0:10:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神凪同学好像在酒店里迷路了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.25,0:10:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在就准备回会场  兄长大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.42,0:10:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  柚璃奈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.75,0:10:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前我想和你谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.42,0:10:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想想…你能来三楼的休息室吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.03,0:10:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在那儿等你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.72,0:11:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么莫非那封信…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.67,0:11:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么头绪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.77,0:11:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.92,0:11:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上那封信是熊五郎父亲连同抚养费一起寄给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.04,0:11:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为它是证明我与熊五郎父亲牵绊的佐证
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.29,0:11:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就作为护身符随身携带了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.37,0:11:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该就是那个了…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.95,0:11:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定是在DNA鉴定之后得知了柚璃奈身份
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.02,0:11:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以在寻找证据吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.07,0:11:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道接下来会发展成什么样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.54,0:11:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但真是变成麻烦事了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.45,0:11:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.60,0:11:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得即使自己的身份被公之于众也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.16,0:11:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.59,0:11:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我是私生子这件事或许会变成丑闻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.13,0:11:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是说到底也只是熊五郎父亲的丑闻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.60,0:11:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们并不需要为此感到内疚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.33,0:11:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柚璃奈真坚强啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.38,0:11:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有  坚强什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.07,0:12:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  你如果真的这样想的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.52,0:12:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请兄长大人也变得更加坚强
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.54,0:12:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.62,0:12:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再过像现在一样淫乱的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.14,0:12:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是好好寻找一个恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.38,0:12:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后证明你是可以贯彻对一个女性的爱的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.10,0:12:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贯彻对一个女性的爱…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.51,0:12:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.62,0:12:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样结婚成家的话  周围也肯定会承认
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.77,0:12:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人是一个相称的社长
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.88,0:12:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  说得也是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.77,0:12:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来转学到深流院学园也是因为这个目的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.06,0:12:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  柚璃奈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.99,0:12:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要认真地寻找恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.83,0:12:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后向世界证明我是可以贯彻对一个女性的爱的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.68,0:12:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样才是我的兄长大人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.19,0:12:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那么  差不多回到会场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.73,0:12:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能一直放着招待的女孩子们不管
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.16,0:12:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢  神凪同学也肯定等着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.67,0:13:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  雅吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.25,0:13:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.34,0:13:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到神凪同学以后
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.33,0:13:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟她说了很多话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.02,0:13:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一直在和我谈论你的事  或许神凪同学对兄长大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.70,0:13:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可  可是  那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.37,0:13:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是找我茬
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.66,0:13:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神凪同学虽然看起来那样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.57,0:13:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得她其实是一个非常细腻的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.50,0:13:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  就算是想着兄长大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.26,0:13:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有办法和你诚实相对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.56,0:13:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柚璃奈觉得那家伙怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.51,0:13:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢  我觉得我或许可以和神凪同学成为好朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.72,0:13:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果神凪同学成为了兄长大人的恋人…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.27,0:14:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为了找到终身伴侣进入了学园
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.55,0:14:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是直到现在因为妹妹的事情没有达到目的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.56,0:14:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在已经知道她就是柚璃奈了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.51,0:14:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  以后可以放心寻找恋人…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.24,0:14:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}将悟！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.10,0:14:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  干…干什么  雅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.86,0:14:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底去哪了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.66,0:14:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的台词好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.27,0:14:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟  亲亲吧  亲亲
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.31,0:14:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲亲什么的  你在这么多人面前说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.14,0:14:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  难道你…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.29,0:14:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟同学
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.16,0:14:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅到底怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.29,0:14:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神凪同学好像以为这是葡萄汁  喝了点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.75,0:14:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝了一口不就知道了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.42,0:14:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现了之后是想提醒她一下的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.87,0:14:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是她拿到杯子后就一口气全部喝掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.44,0:14:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神凪这家伙  回到会场以后看她的样子很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.71,0:14:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有做什么奇怪的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.14,0:15:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啊  再说发现雅的是柚璃奈
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.86,0:15:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我被发现啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.02,0:15:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  雅
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.09,0:15:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神凪同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.86,0:15:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.68,0:15:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.23,0:15:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔  唔  唔噗噗  恶心…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.67,0:15:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.66,0:15:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.69,0:15:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒店的行政套房
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.70,0:15:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你睡着了所以拜托母亲要了一间房间
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.00,0:15:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.55,0:15:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟  难道趁我睡觉的时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.10,0:15:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  我才不会做出那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.21,0:16:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  也是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.61,0:16:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浴室在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.98,0:16:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.30,0:16:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出了点汗  我去洗个澡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.30,0:16:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.73,0:17:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.28,0:17:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  雅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.44,0:17:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅  你…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.73,0:17:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.04,0:17:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.13,0:17:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的胸怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.59,0:17:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.87,0:17:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来比平时大吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.86,0:17:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.30,0:17:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是这个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.21,0:17:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  将悟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.76,0:17:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  和我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.21,0:17:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你在说什…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.66,0:17:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.16,0:17:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可…可是  我…心理…心理准备还
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.48,0:17:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我给你做心理准备
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.14,0:18:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.77,0:18:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.68,0:18:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟  求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.24,0:18:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远  永远在我身边  不要离开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.43,0:18:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  不要消失掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.90,0:18:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心  我就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.02,0:18:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.58,0:18:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.72,0:18:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是骗人的  因为将悟不是消失掉了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.81,0:18:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来一直在一起玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.68,0:18:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但后来却见不到面了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.60,0:18:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.67,0:18:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实我们曾经分开过
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.59,0:18:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  不又这样见面了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.47,0:18:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从现在开始会在雅的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.54,0:18:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？真的会在我身边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.69,0:18:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  当然
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.28,0:19:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是约定啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.84,0:19:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的…真的约定好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.08,0:19:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.98,0:19:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟同学  承您款待了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.11,0:19:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱菜吃太多都撑到了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.18,0:19:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开心就好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.90,0:19:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢你今天招待我们来到这美妙的派对
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.20,0:19:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我改天会再向母亲大人正式打招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.00,0:19:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…神凪同学怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.84,0:19:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡得很舒服的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.76,0:19:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让她睡到自然醒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.45,0:20:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒了之后我会把她送到女生宿舍的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.30,0:20:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.21,0:20:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  帝野  别因为神凪在睡觉就做出一些奇怪的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.67,0:20:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的  我怎么会做那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.43,0:20:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  盯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.59,0:20:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  也罢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.96,0:20:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果出了什么差错我可要诅咒你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.07,0:20:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这身打扮还真有说服力呢  学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.04,0:20:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嵯峨良同学真关心神凪同学啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.93,0:20:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个人关系很好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.89,0:20:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说雅和嵯峨良学姐什么时候…？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.93,0:20:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.58,0:20:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母…母亲  怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.17,0:20:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.77,0:20:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天这是什么狼狈样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.66,0:20:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不好好陪同招待的女士
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.38,0:20:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还让她不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.76,0:20:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  雅…不是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.98,0:21:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神凪同学的事怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.00,0:21:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为她本人一不小心…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.62,0:21:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想听你解释
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.72,0:21:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说你一直就那么半吊子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.91,0:21:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小学生时候的暑假作业也一直拖到最后
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.96,0:21:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  说那么以前的事也…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.08,0:21:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧  柚璃奈也说点什…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.94,0:21:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.47,0:21:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我从一开始就不赞同你招待五名朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.76,0:21:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我知道你根本不能陪同那么多人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.75,0:21:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  濑利说你在学校里也有自己的交际圈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.38,0:21:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才没有办法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.89,0:21:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  濑利小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.17,0:21:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备了五人份请帖的是濑利小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.97,0:21:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  因为她说你无论如何都拜托她
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.72,0:21:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后要去好好去道谢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.78,0:22:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样  棋子就凑齐了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.85,0:22:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来只要…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.12,0:23:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凛香  今天的派对好开心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.48,0:23:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有我展示跳舞的机会真是太可惜了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.59,0:23:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次舞会之后  你有拼命特训对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.53,0:23:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了超越海豚探戈的必杀舞蹈
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.45,0:23:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,推开云雾  如同天龙般强力的舞蹈
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.88,0:23:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其名正是龙之华尔兹
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.85,0:24:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集真想让你们看看
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.96,0:24:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的下集是第11话  妹妹的陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.18,0:24:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙之华尔兹  云和龙…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.33,0:24:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说是云龙型啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.33,0:24:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs20}云龙型：相扑架势的一种
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.72,0:24:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看招！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.72,0:24:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs20}看招：相扑时鼓舞自己士气的口号
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
