[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2013-09-15 19:31:49
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: Nakaimo 01
Original Script: SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H004528D7,&H802917B0,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Staff,黑体,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFPFuun-W7,18,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,10,1
Style: OPCN,方正毡笔黑简体,22,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: EDJP,DFPHSMincho-W9,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,10,10,6,1
Style: EDCN,方正小标宋_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,10,10,6,1
Style: Title,方正毡笔黑简体,26,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP2,@DFPFuun-W7,18,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,1,2,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: OPCN2,@方正毡笔黑简体,22,&H0066CC8A,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,1,2,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: INJP,DFPFuun-W7,18,&H0092A5D1,&H000000FF,&H00D4EBFC,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,10,10,1
Style: INCN,方正毡笔黑简体,19,&H0092A5D1,&H000000FF,&H00D4EBFC,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------OPJP--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.20,0:00:55.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}言ったでしょ　抜けがけ禁止なんだけど
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.43,0:00:58.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}言ったよね　好きだもん　おさえらんないっ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.58,0:01:01.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}今すぐに　友好条約破棄して
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.77,0:01:05.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}love me love me　もっと　わたしだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.64,0:01:17.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}この恋に　限りなく　ウンメイを　感じちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.01,0:01:23.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}なのになんで　矢印が1234　嘘　アリエナイ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.35,0:01:28.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}わたしより　可愛いコ　映さないで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.78,0:01:31.72,OPJP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(20,180)}ダメだって瞳をガードガード
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.75,0:01:36.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}火花散って　ごめんなさい　choose me my ダーリン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.79,0:01:43.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}わかるよ　最初から　みんな　ヒロイン志望
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.54,0:01:51.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}最高の　最愛の　たったひとりに　なりたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.41,0:01:54.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}優しいだけじゃ困る
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.59,0:01:57.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ぎゅっと奪ってほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.00,0:02:04.17,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}事情とか　ぬきにして　正直に恋して
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.21,0:02:10.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}傷ついたっていい　あなたに決めたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.01,0:02:10.90,OPJP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(20,180)}約束
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.80,0:02:13.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}友情だって大切
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.88,0:02:14.49,OPJP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(20,180)}それなのに
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.00,0:02:16.41,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}非常事態じゃしょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.41,0:02:20.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}誰がライバル　わたしを選んで
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------OPCN--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.20,0:00:55.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我可说过吧  偷跑可是禁止的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.43,0:00:58.58,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我可说过哦  喜欢你已经不能克制
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.58,0:01:01.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}现在马上撤销友好条约
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.77,0:01:05.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}{\fn華康布丁體\fs20}love me love me{\r}  更加地仅仅爱我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.64,0:01:17.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}这份恋情中  我感受到命运的味道四处弥漫
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.01,0:01:23.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但是为什么  箭矢的印记  1234  骗人  不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.35,0:01:28.78,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}比起我来  不要将视线  转向更可爱的她
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.78,0:01:31.72,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(620,180)}不可以眼睛突然放光
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.75,0:01:36.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}一不小心就火星四射  对不起  {\fn華康布丁體\fs20}choose me my darling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.79,0:01:43.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我可是知道的哦  从最初开始大家就都想要成为女主角
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.54,0:01:51.06,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}最好的最爱的仅有的那一人  祈祷会是我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.41,0:01:54.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}只是温柔的话我会困扰哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.59,0:01:57.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}想要你紧紧地争夺我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.00,0:02:04.17,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}麻烦的事情统统省略掉  坦率地来恋爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.21,0:02:10.14,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}即使受伤也没关系  已经决定是你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.01,0:02:10.90,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(620,180)}约定了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.80,0:02:13.06,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}友情虽然也很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.88,0:02:14.49,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)\pos(620,180)}即使如此
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.00,0:02:16.41,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}紧急状况无法抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.41,0:02:20.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}谁才是敌手  请选择我吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------EDJP--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.15,0:22:26.15,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}走りだした恋はエデンを探してる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.15,0:22:32.92,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}あなたからの引力　戸惑いながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.11,0:22:37.55,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}わたしわかってたよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.79,0:22:43.14,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}ふたりは果実にふれたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.33,0:22:49.41,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}切ないウソが出会いを責めるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.41,0:22:55.22,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}傷つくだけじゃないと言って？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.42,0:23:02.69,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}やさしいその手でさらってくれる明日は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.09,0:23:08.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}ずっと過去からの約束
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.03,0:23:12.86,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}きっと結ばれる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.02,0:23:15.82,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}だって信じてる
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.02,0:23:21.65,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}ときめくココロはもうとまらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.02,0:23:24.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}やっとはじまるね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.02,0:23:32.75,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}そんな愛しさで眩しい世界へと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.90,0:23:35.70,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}迷わずに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.91,0:23:39.33,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}Heavenly lover
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------EDCN--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.15,0:22:26.15,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}勇敢迈出的恋情  寻找着伊甸园的踪迹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.15,0:22:32.92,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}你所释放的引力  虽令我踌躇不前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.11,0:22:37.55,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}但我可是知道的哟
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.79,0:22:43.14,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}两个人触碰到了恋爱的果实
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.33,0:22:49.41,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}悲伤的谎言苛责着这份相会
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.41,0:22:55.22,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}你说这不仅只是刻印的伤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.42,0:23:02.69,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}那双温柔的手中攫取的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.09,0:23:08.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}一定  将过去的约定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.03,0:23:12.86,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}一直  连结在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.02,0:23:15.82,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}因为  我一直相信着
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.02,0:23:21.65,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}小鹿乱撞的心情已经无法停止
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.02,0:23:24.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}终于  得以开始
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.02,0:23:32.75,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}和可爱的你共同迈向耀眼的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.90,0:23:35.70,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}不再迷茫
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.91,0:23:39.33,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur3\fad(200,200)}Heavenly lover
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------INJP--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.14,0:17:56.88,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そっぽ向いていても　カラダの右っかわが
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.39,0:18:03.10,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ドキドキしちゃうの　キンチョーしてバカみたい
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.25,0:18:09.02,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}視界映り込んでる横顔　マジメぶっててヘンな顔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.37,0:18:16.15,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}こっち見ないなんて生意気よ　あたしばっかり気にしてるの
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.21,0:18:21.54,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}隣にいるのに　近くて遠い
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.64,0:18:27.30,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}授業中はブルー　話したいなぁ…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.36,0:18:33.63,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あぁ、でもねチャイムが鳴ったとたんに
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.73,0:18:41.83,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}素直なあたしごと　休み時間　行っちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.83,0:18:47.78,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}気まぐれにもし見えているなら
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.78,0:18:54.75,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}それはキミのせいなんだ　自覚して！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.75,0:19:00.32,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もっと可愛い部分
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.40,0:19:09.40,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}見せるからには　ソレナリの二人でなきゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.86,0:19:16.25,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}曖昧な態度　生まれつきなの？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.29,0:19:21.89,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}みんなに優しい　切ないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.99,0:19:28.12,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ねぇ、二人をつないでる糸が
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.44,0:19:36.49,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}何色だとしても　特別だと思わせて
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.49,0:19:42.42,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}気まぐれにもし見せているなら
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.42,0:19:49.41,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}それは計算違いで　どうしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.41,0:19:54.93,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もっとあのコみたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.09,0:20:04.62,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}可愛いあたしでいたいのに　難しいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.81,0:20:12.76,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}気まぐれにもし見えているなら
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.87,0:20:19.78,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}それはキミのせいなんだ　わかってよ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.78,0:20:25.14,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}絶対誰にも負けない
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.48,0:20:34.42,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}可愛いあたしになるからね　覚悟してて
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------INCN--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.14,0:17:56.88,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}就算把脸转向一旁　光是在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.39,0:18:03.10,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我也会紧张得心跳不止　简直像个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.25,0:18:09.02,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你的侧脸映入我的眼帘　那装作认真的奇怪脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.37,0:18:16.15,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}居然敢不看着我　太嚣张啦　难道只有我自己很在意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.21,0:18:21.54,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}明明近在眼前　却又觉得远在天边
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.64,0:18:27.30,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}上课时好忧郁　想和你说话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.36,0:18:33.63,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}啊　但是下课铃声一响
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.73,0:18:41.83,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}老实的我就去享受课间时光了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.83,0:18:47.78,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如果你觉得我反复无常
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.78,0:18:54.75,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那就快察觉到这都是你  害  的！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.75,0:19:00.32,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想要看到我更可爱的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.40,0:19:09.40,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那我们俩的关系就需要更加亲密
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.86,0:19:16.25,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}暧昧的态度　是天生的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.29,0:19:21.89,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你对大家都温柔　我好难受
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.99,0:19:28.12,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}呐　牵起我们的丝线
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.44,0:19:36.49,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无论是什么颜色　都让我觉得很特别
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.49,0:19:42.42,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如果你觉得我反复无常
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.42,0:19:49.41,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那是因为算盘打错了　怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.41,0:19:54.93,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变得更像她一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.09,0:20:04.62,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想要一直展现可爱的自己　还真是难啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.81,0:20:12.76,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如果你觉得我反复无常
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.87,0:20:19.78,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}那就快意识到这都是你  害  的！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.78,0:20:25.14,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我绝对不会输给任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.48,0:20:34.42,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我会变成可爱的自己　你做好觉悟吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------Title--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.51,0:02:27.30,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\pos(547,286)}妹妹的陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.03,0:24:11.05,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,90)\fs24}不识萌妹真面目 只缘实妹在身旁
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------Staff--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}本字幕由澄空学园&华盟字幕社联合制作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片源：阿爽 / 10thMystery  翻译：ゾンビ / 巫贼  校对：detectivexsc\N特效：AfterFX  后期：yjywybb / Lantis  繁化：阿爽
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//--------------------EP--------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.53,0:00:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.44,0:00:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.75,0:00:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.53,0:00:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.71,0:00:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人…兄长大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.04,0:00:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人…兄长大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.09,0:00:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳公公晒屁股了哦  再不起床就要迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.28,0:02:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  请享用~
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.13,0:02:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  还麻烦你为我准备早餐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.72,0:02:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚的派对累坏了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.45,0:02:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确发生了很多事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.18,0:02:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这样总有种新婚夫妇的感觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.71,0:02:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.81,0:02:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么新…新婚啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.53,0:02:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人  是先吃饭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.56,0:02:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是先洗澡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.74,0:03:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是先品·尝·我？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.59,0:03:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.74,0:03:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人…兄长大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.62,0:03:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.38,0:03:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.17,0:03:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌  我只是开个小玩笑而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.74,0:03:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩笑…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.36,0:03:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么柚璃奈  那时你也是在开玩笑的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.47,0:03:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.60,0:03:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是父亲葬礼的那天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.11,0:03:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从窗外…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.08,0:03:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是兄长大人的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.17,0:03:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人已经不再孤单
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.61,0:03:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后我会陪在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.23,0:03:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我是为了和兄长大人结婚而来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.70,0:03:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…我好像没做过这种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.46,0:03:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她那时的确说是我妹妹…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.06,0:03:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是恶作剧吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.10,0:03:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果光就口头上说是你妹妹的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.51,0:03:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都能做到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.01,0:03:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.68,0:04:03.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶作剧…吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.19,0:04:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,矢部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.82,0:04:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.58,0:04:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉冈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.47,0:04:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.74,0:04:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和久井
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.54,0:04:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.31,0:04:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有神凪没到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.23,0:04:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小都里老师
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.68,0:04:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神凪同学请假的理由是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.90,0:04:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…好像说是感冒了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.13,0:04:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问老师
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.01,0:04:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  田中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.31,0:04:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师如果感冒了请务必传染给我…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.38,0:04:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这没出息的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.65,0:04:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来很困嘛  衣楠
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.72,0:04:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近都在彻夜行动
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.32,0:04:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是一直在调查吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.96,0:04:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么收获吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.47,0:04:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  目前还没有找到突破口
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.51,0:04:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.34,0:04:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是想把你拉下社长之位的那些人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.92,0:05:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经把爪牙布置在你周围了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.09,0:05:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万要小心行事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.67,0:05:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.14,0:05:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吧  你看起来真像是睡眠不足
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.17,0:05:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来真到生理活动的临界点了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.71,0:05:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.26,0:05:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来要干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.35,0:05:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.76,0:05:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没看到  我们什么都没看到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.50,0:05:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.77,0:05:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你们想象中的那样…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.24,0:05:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了  看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.27,0:05:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好丢人啊  讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.33,0:05:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说在这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.68,0:06:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  心乃枝
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.32,0:06:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.59,0:06:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Marie Chocolate」里  布丁是推荐品吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.94,0:06:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  最推荐的是泡芙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.63,0:06:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但既然是感冒  布丁会更好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.37,0:06:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅的房间在三楼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.50,0:06:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  在我正楼上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.70,0:06:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.26,0:06:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟  为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.65,0:06:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  听说你感冒了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.02,0:06:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.58,0:06:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来探病了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.84,0:06:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来感冒并无大碍了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.50,0:06:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  只是有点乏力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.21,0:06:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那我就安心了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.56,0:06:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  谢谢  我去倒点茶一起吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.50,0:07:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去倒茶好了  神凪同学还是要多多休息
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.41,0:07:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.03,0:07:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…茶叶在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.62,0:07:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.29,0:08:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一包泡三杯有些不够啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.07,0:08:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我回自己家去拿点过来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.48,0:08:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.21,0:08:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我马上就回来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.04,0:08:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟同学  我去去就来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.40,0:08:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  心乃枝  拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.70,0:08:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我马上就回来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.88,0:08:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心乃枝还真慢啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.50,0:08:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  将悟…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.31,0:08:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.74,0:09:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吻我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.69,0:09:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你你你…你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.96,0:09:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  为什么唯独不能吻我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.52,0:09:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你问我为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.39,0:09:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不吻我的话  我明天也不去学校
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.90,0:09:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不肯吻我的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.39,0:09:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不肯的话用约会来代替也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.04,0:09:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样总行了吧  约好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.76,0:09:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么约好了…太独断了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.56,0:09:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个礼拜天  一定要来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.35,0:09:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  因为一时匆忙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.51,0:09:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不小心把砂糖打翻了  收拾了一会儿才回来…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.41,0:10:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  感觉真不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.38,0:10:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止是早餐  连晚餐都帮我准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.00,0:10:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小事一桩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.49,0:10:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.44,0:10:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.14,0:10:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.91,0:10:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  兄长大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.17,0:10:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上你说过的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.27,0:10:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊五郎父亲的葬礼上出现的自称是妹妹的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.39,0:10:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.22,0:10:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实当时我也出席了葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.05,0:10:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且记得鹤真同学也到场了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.04,0:10:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心乃枝来父亲的葬礼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.40,0:11:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  当初见到鹤真同学的时候总感觉似曾相识
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.25,0:11:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过没能马上反应过来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.76,0:11:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但听到你早上说的…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.12,0:11:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仔细回想了下当天的情况  于是就发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.83,0:11:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微等下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.04,0:11:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心乃枝当天应该在参加深流院学园的入学考试
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.19,0:11:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能来葬礼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.81,0:11:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我真的看见了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.96,0:11:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你的意思是说心乃枝在撒谎？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.97,0:11:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没这个意思…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.96,0:11:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且心乃枝做这事的目的是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.32,0:11:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这无从得知
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.57,0:11:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  兄长大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.91,0:11:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请千万小心别被人给骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.80,0:11:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后请务必看清
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.04,0:11:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正为兄长大人着想的人是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.22,0:11:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正需要兄长大人来支持的人是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.41,0:11:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要我来支持的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.72,0:11:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远  永远待在我的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.62,0:11:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要去任何地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.78,0:11:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  我不要你消失
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.04,0:12:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道  心乃枝是那时的？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.16,0:12:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是兄长大人的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.80,0:12:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人已经不是一个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.31,0:12:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今以后我和你在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.72,0:12:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我是为了和兄长大人结婚而来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.61,0:12:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  可是心乃枝她…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.45,0:12:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  熊五郎先生葬礼那天？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.60,0:12:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没能去葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.24,0:12:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那天正好和深流院学园的入学考试重叠了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.70,0:12:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果  如果那真的是心乃枝的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.40,0:12:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的目的到底是什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.87,0:12:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是想把你拉下社长之位的那些人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.24,0:12:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经把爪牙布置在你周围了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.56,0:13:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄长大人  请千万小心别被人给骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.51,0:13:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能…呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.81,0:13:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青山
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.69,0:13:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.55,0:13:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饭塚
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.34,0:13:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.83,0:13:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那以后考虑了好多事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.96,0:13:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天几乎没合过眼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.74,0:13:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神凪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.38,0:13:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.39,0:13:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喊得不错啊  感冒已经好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.26,0:13:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了慰问品的布丁就治好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.26,0:13:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  采访我？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.43,0:13:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  从中学时代开始就在游泳上崭露头角
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.38,0:13:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以体育特长被推荐到我校的神凪雅
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.62,0:13:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临近县比赛预选的当下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.82,0:13:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的第二人格告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.48,0:14:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该采访应成为水瓶座时代的新人鱼公主的你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.25,0:14:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是希望能在泳池边拍摄几张你的泳装照
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.35,0:14:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  还有写真特集吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.79,0:14:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真头疼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.37,0:14:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  也不是要弄写真特集  来几张普通的照片就好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.67,0:14:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么接下来就是社团活动了  如果部长同意的话就行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.49,0:14:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经借助水晶之力预想到了这点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.05,0:14:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,许可已经拿到了  你就放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.20,0:14:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新谷部长还真是老样子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.27,0:14:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先回去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.86,0:14:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  等一下  来这边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.11,0:14:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.03,0:14:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约定
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.81,0:14:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的约定  不可以不算数啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.55,0:14:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星期日的约会  绝对要来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.55,0:14:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我去接受采访了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.66,0:14:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.89,0:15:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅那家伙很得意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.48,0:15:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是到了这个份上  已经没关系了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.46,0:15:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.11,0:15:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我看来神凪好像是在勉强自己
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.76,0:15:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  对不起  说了一些奇怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.13,0:15:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.94,0:15:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游泳比赛临近  心气很高的缘故
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.80,0:15:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  和平常的感觉有点不一样…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.91,0:15:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  将悟同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.91,0:15:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游泳…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.48,0:15:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果  如果真是那样…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.72,0:15:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  将悟同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.73,0:15:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟同学…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.53,0:16:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  这个看起来好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.28,0:16:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这个也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.57,0:16:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是可是  这个也难以舍弃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.65,0:16:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这个看起来也好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.55,0:16:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是果然还是这个更…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.90,0:16:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是可是  啊啊  好犹豫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.38,0:16:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天导会长  请你正经点！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.85,0:16:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学生会教室的电脑不是搜索甜品的机器！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.04,0:16:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微查一下又没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.31,0:16:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.60,0:16:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就让我吃学生会教室的柜子里的点心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.40,0:16:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是给客人准备的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.67,0:16:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么非得那样不可  很奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.29,0:16:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来会长你…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.03,0:16:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.59,0:16:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了  帝野学长  门也不敲就突然…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.99,0:16:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国立同学
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.89,0:16:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.05,0:16:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事希望你能告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.14,0:16:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.21,0:17:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.64,0:17:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了  约好的时间早就…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.07,0:17:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.33,0:17:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  难道是看我看得入迷了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.39,0:17:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞎…瞎说什么  怎么可能…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.81,0:17:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.95,0:17:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  等一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.22,0:17:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛啊  好不容易约一次会
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.79,0:17:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制造点气氛好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.47,0:17:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.20,0:00:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.05,0:19:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  为什么连约会都要来泳池
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.25,0:19:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊  临近县比赛的预选
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.34,0:19:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能少了练习
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.84,0:19:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.15,0:19:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将悟不游也没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.59,0:19:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我游泳就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.98,0:20:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔  游得真爽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.63,0:20:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.89,0:20:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这样你也满足了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.70,0:20:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.99,0:20:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.79,0:20:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个地方要去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.09,0:21:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个要去的地方就是这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.14,0:21:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别磨磨唧唧的  来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.93,0:23:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错啊  干得好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.59,0:23:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试着再稍微把脚张看一点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.28,0:23:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在泳池边干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.23,0:23:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摄影啊  要刊登在校报上的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.52,0:23:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这次试着脱一点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.16,0:23:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只脱上面的就好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.27,0:23:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  新谷  你既然是部长的话就让她注意点…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.83,0:23:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新谷你在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.97,0:24:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在用水晶之力洞察未来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.20,0:24:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.16,0:24:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集是第12话  不识萌妹真面目  只缘实妹在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.16,0:24:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs20}标题原文：妹妹一直在身边
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.57,0:24:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些家伙已经没救了  我得想点办法！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
