[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-05-15 20:40:46
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Papakiki
Original Script:CASO&SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,49,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0A000000,&H00505C9D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,57,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9F9F9,&H1E22E468,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,5,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: EDtitle,方正准圆_GBK,57,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9F9F9,&H1E28A155,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,8,0,5,30,30,15,1
Style: OPJ,DFGMaruMoji-SL,41,&H003797EA,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H323797EA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,3,8,23,23,15,128
Style: OPC,华康少女文字W5(P),41,&H003797EA,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H323797EA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,3,2,23,23,15,1
Style: staff,方正黑体_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H3C000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,23,1
Style: INC,方正兰亭中黑_GBK,36,&H5A9C4817,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,20,20,20,1
Style: INE,方正兰亭中黑_GBK,36,&H5A9C4817,&H000000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,20,20,20,1
Style: EDJ,DFGMaruGothic-Md,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H323797EA,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,23,23,15,128
Style: EDC,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H323797EA,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,23,23,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.07,0:02:11.97,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,428)\pos(271.698113,583.5)}来我家里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.97,0:02:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很抱歉  虽然很突然  但我不是故意的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.06,0:02:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你妈应该有说过我会来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.84,0:02:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的啦  我明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.45,0:02:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.63,0:02:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得我吗  小空
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.28,0:02:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑且自我介绍下吧  我是你们妈妈的弟弟  濑川祐太
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.10,0:02:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小雏也来打个招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.10,0:02:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是小鸟游雏  三岁了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.63,0:02:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么  都三岁这么大了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.36,0:02:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是小鸟游美羽  十岁  五年级了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.41,0:02:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是成熟呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.54,0:02:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  姐姐也打个招呼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.89,0:02:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐有点怕生所以有时也比较冷淡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.45,0:03:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说多余的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.36,0:03:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空也变得很成熟了  稍微有点吃惊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.28,0:03:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少说漂亮话了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.97,0:03:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又说这种话了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.71,0:03:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得你是初二吧  刚才真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.28,0:03:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经够了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.23,0:03:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.76,0:03:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么放着不管  过会儿心情就会变好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.67,0:03:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来我该干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.06,0:03:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不用做也没关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.89,0:03:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边呆着就好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.89,0:03:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小舅舅  来玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.28,0:03:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汝还真能干啊  不过吾可不会放水哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.19,0:03:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.36,0:04:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雏的…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.36,0:04:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再来一局?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.89,0:04:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雏的被弄破了…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.97,0:04:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然哭了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.58,0:04:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是当然的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.15,0:04:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.45,0:04:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖不哭不哭  真是没风度的舅舅呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.36,0:04:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么  可恶  怎么能输给你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.10,0:04:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了要全力的吧  我不会手下留情的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.28,0:04:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还用你说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.15,0:04:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.19,0:04:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.89,0:04:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我输了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.19,0:04:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空姐好帅
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.36,0:04:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个大人  真逊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.54,0:04:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真逊真逊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.50,0:04:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午饭做好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.10,0:04:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午饭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.28,0:04:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.15,0:04:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雏要粉色的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.54,0:05:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了  让你来做
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.54,0:05:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  只是把挂面煮了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.58,0:05:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边的只是把祐理小姐做的加热了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.23,0:05:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃  真怀念啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.32,0:05:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.71,0:05:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大学是怎样的地方呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.36,0:05:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是个开心的地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.36,0:05:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有有趣的学长之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.50,0:05:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交到女朋友了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.45,0:05:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真直接啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.32,0:05:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为舅舅还算有点帅嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.89,0:05:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开我玩笑了  女朋友什么的我没有哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.67,0:05:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是单相思咯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.28,0:05:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.23,0:05:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都写在脸上了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.50,0:05:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  别开我玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.89,0:05:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过果然还是有喜欢的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.32,0:06:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是漂亮型的还是可爱型的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.06,0:06:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.67,0:06:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么嘛  就当做为了将来的学习
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.19,0:06:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我适可而止一点  美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.84,0:06:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉  姐姐应该也想知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.93,0:06:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.32,0:06:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人  听说舅舅要过来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.93,0:06:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明都已经洗了两次澡了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.06,0:06:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会被撞见换衣服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.23,0:06:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.10,0:06:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢款待
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.63,0:06:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.80,0:06:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.63,0:06:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.71,0:06:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在做扫除  流了汗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.58,0:06:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身上也弄脏了  所以才…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.89,0:06:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.19,0:06:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才又洗了一次澡…  仅此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.45,0:06:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.02,0:07:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡着了么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.80,0:07:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为闹腾过了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.06,0:07:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏  午睡的话要回房间哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.84,0:07:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然有兄弟姐妹真好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.19,0:07:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想睡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.63,0:07:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太  不可以在这里睡觉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.02,0:07:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿你没办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.80,0:08:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}Twinkle  twinkle  little star
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.19,0:08:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}How I wonder what you are
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.23,0:08:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  不能在这里睡觉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.15,0:08:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是拿你没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.58,0:08:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.84,0:08:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空  美羽  小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.32,0:08:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}大家一起去买东西了  美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.19,0:08:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.15,0:08:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.71,0:08:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.54,0:08:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你小子是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.84,0:08:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女儿们怎么了  你把她们藏哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.93,0:08:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  大家去买东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.71,0:08:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.10,0:08:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对我女儿们做了什么  说！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.36,0:09:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.63,0:09:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}混蛋混蛋混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.63,0:09:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛痛痛  快住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.71,0:09:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我啊  都说了快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.41,0:09:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼才知道你是谁  快说出真相
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.67,0:09:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静一点笨蛋老公
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.32,0:09:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看看  是祐太啊  祐太
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.19,0:09:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不在的时候拜托他来看家的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.89,0:09:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.06,0:09:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那脸上的恶作剧是美羽吧  真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.67,0:09:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.58,0:09:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.02,0:09:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在想些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.15,0:09:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你睡得那么香  就忍不住…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.41,0:09:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.45,0:09:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.50,0:09:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.93,0:09:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事  没注意到的我也有错
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.02,0:09:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了祐太
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.93,0:09:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过能和孩子们混的这么熟真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.80,0:09:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.89,0:09:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我就能安心和信吾一起出差去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.50,0:09:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.50,0:10:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去采购稀有金属  只有一周
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.06,0:10:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这期间女儿们就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.93,0:10:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你很闲吧  会给你工钱的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.45,0:10:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再怎么说这也太乱来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.41,0:10:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.36,0:10:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.67,0:10:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.67,0:10:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请说没关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.84,0:10:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想让他们去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.89,0:10:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸和祐理小姐还没去过新婚旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.67,0:10:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.28,0:10:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们一直在照顾着我们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.45,0:10:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有去的空闲  所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.50,0:10:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.84,0:10:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.02,0:10:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.58,0:11:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  那孩子们就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.23,0:11:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.23,0:11:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过禁止带那个大胸女朋友回来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.67,0:11:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了不是女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.63,0:11:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就快点去告白吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.02,0:11:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你肯定不会表白最后就无疾而终吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.93,0:11:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要放弃  好好努力
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.45,0:11:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢垂死挣扎是你唯一的可取之处
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.06,0:11:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算什么啊  再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.45,0:11:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈爸爸走了的话真的没问题么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.28,0:11:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  没关系  小舅舅会来陪我玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.58,0:11:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好孩子  我们很快就会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.38,0:12:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs44}谢谢你 祐太
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.76,0:12:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得的旅行第一天竟然下雨
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.32,0:12:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们应该早就飞上云端能看见太阳了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.58,0:12:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是坐飞机嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.06,0:12:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.71,0:12:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  舅舅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.58,0:12:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起那些
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.28,0:12:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是教你我家的规定
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.02,0:12:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教你规定
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.93,0:13:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先是这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.50,0:13:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是厕所…吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.28,0:13:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅只能用这里的厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.28,0:13:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2楼的是女孩子专用的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.19,0:13:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上基本不允许你来2楼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.41,0:13:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.50,0:13:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一条
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.23,0:13:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅的换洗衣服  请放在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.89,0:13:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不要放在一起洗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.19,0:13:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要洗…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.63,0:13:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后然后
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.45,0:13:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家庭旅行时候宾馆的一次性香波
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.41,0:13:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准用我们的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.32,0:13:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准用
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.19,0:13:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅睡觉的地方是这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.45,0:13:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,H的书不准带进来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.15,0:13:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.41,0:13:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.63,0:13:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.41,0:13:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好遵守规定 度过愉快的一周吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.37,0:13:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.67,0:13:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.80,0:13:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  现在开始就改叫你爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.02,0:13:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在胡说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.06,0:13:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为叫舅舅没有感觉嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.58,0:13:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小舅舅爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.84,0:13:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.54,0:13:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.58,0:13:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然这种叫法还是对信吾先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.50,0:13:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们真正的爸爸使用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.45,0:14:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害羞的表情也相当可爱呢  姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.97,0:14:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.54,0:14:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.41,0:14:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  接下来做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.15,0:14:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩游戏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.58,0:14:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教我功课吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.80,0:14:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是整理房间啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.76,0:14:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩啦玩啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.80,0:14:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,功课
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.76,0:14:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整理  当然是整理吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.80,0:14:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,功课  拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.37,0:14:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.58,0:14:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  全部都来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.97,0:14:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都过来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.32,0:14:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.63,0:14:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得今晚能看到流星雨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.58,0:15:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.50,0:15:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  划过了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.71,0:15:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.89,0:15:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经划过去了哟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.45,0:15:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.58,0:15:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.71,0:15:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经划过了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.06,0:15:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏也想看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.89,0:15:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖～小雏  我们一起找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.06,0:15:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.54,0:15:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星星会「咻」一下划落哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.45,0:15:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.97,0:15:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,===插入歌===
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.02,0:15:46.19,INE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}twinkle twinkle little star
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.02,0:15:46.19,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}一闪一闪亮晶晶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.58,0:15:51.89,INE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}How I wonder what you are
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.58,0:15:51.89,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}满天都是小星星
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.37,0:15:57.58,INE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}up above the world so high
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.37,0:15:57.58,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}挂在天上放光明
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.02,0:16:03.50,INE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}like a diamond in the sky
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.02,0:16:03.50,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}好像许多小眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.80,0:16:09.02,INE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}twinkle twinkle little star
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.80,0:16:09.02,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}一闪一闪亮晶晶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.41,0:16:14.84,INE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}How I wonder what you are
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.41,0:16:14.84,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\blur4\fad(100,300)}满天都是小星星
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,===插入歌====
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.80,0:16:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.10,0:16:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前帮我盖了毛巾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.37,0:17:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒来之后就想要对你道个谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.93,0:17:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么的  就那些事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.84,0:17:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.06,0:17:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.41,0:17:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  还醒着吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.93,0:17:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.19,0:17:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在做什么呢  爸爸和祐理小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.28,0:17:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边还是白天
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.76,0:17:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一天的话应该是在观光
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.28,0:17:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在两个人肯定热火朝天呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.63,0:17:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很甜蜜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.67,0:17:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.93,0:17:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  两个人出门
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.63,0:17:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.19,0:17:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.10,0:17:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,luna pure of galaxy！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.71,0:17:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.54,0:17:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.71,0:17:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是luna luna seven的必杀技啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.63,0:17:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.76,0:18:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是指你念必杀技时的气势不够
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.10,0:18:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.06,0:18:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.15,0:18:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.32,0:18:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.28,0:18:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,潘多拉的爪牙们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.45,0:18:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,luna pure of galaxy！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.41,0:18:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,===手机消息===
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.41,0:18:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs38}「乘客的名单呢」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.41,0:18:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs38}「真的假的」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.41,0:18:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs38}「竟然发生事故」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.41,0:18:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs38}「飞机发生事故了」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.41,0:18:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs38}「包括日本的一对夫妇\N200名乘客下落不明」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.32,0:18:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs38\fad(200,2500)}因事故下落不明的日本夫妇名字
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.32,0:18:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs38\fad(200,2500)}小鸟游信吾·祐理
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.97,0:18:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子们就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.76,0:18:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要放弃  好好努力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.15,0:18:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢垂死挣扎就是你唯一的可取之处
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.02,0:18:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果有联系到美羽妈妈吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.80,0:18:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有联系的必要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.02,0:18:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也不会答应让美羽去语言不通的国外
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.54,0:18:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果小空的妈妈还活着的话就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.93,0:18:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人还是挺好的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.28,0:18:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然也不会变成现在这样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.63,0:19:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥运气真不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.54,0:19:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也该得出结论了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.71,0:19:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这关系到大家的将来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.71,0:19:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你们能安静地听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.06,0:19:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏就过继给真由美阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.10,0:19:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽来我家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.10,0:19:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有点远  但是空气很好  是个不错的地方哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.50,0:19:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空则到全日制住校的中学去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.84,0:19:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.58,0:19:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不想分开
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.28,0:19:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想要三个人在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.97,0:20:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太先生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.50,0:20:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我明白你们的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.15,0:20:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那是没办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.19,0:20:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是去地球的另一端
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.58,0:20:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想见面的话随时能见到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.54,0:20:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.50,0:20:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是唯一一个能让你们最幸福的办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.50,0:20:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我们果然还是不想分开
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.10,0:20:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太  祐太就由我来抚养
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.97,0:20:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会打工或想其它办法  送他上大学
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.37,0:20:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…因为我和祐太
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.15,0:20:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是唯一的家人了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.80,0:20:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.15,0:20:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不会给你们添麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.89,0:20:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会很听话的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.84,0:20:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让我们三个人在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.32,0:20:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说这么任性的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.02,0:21:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说没法让三个人在一起了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.84,0:21:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来我家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.67,0:21:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然又穷又窄  什么都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.63,0:21:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但可以让你们三个在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.76,0:21:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.58,0:21:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你突然乱说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.50,0:21:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要光凭一时冲动说些不可能的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.63,0:21:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你和小雏有血缘关系
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.19,0:21:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但小空和美羽对你来说完全是外人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.63,0:21:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.93,0:21:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血缘什么的怎样都好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.76,0:21:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一家人不能在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.58,0:21:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.58,0:23:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小雏哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.76,0:23:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我们去小舅舅家了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.45,0:23:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  小空姐姐在尿尿的时候悲剧了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.71,0:23:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说才不会哭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.71,0:23:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  再见啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.94,0:23:36.02,EDtitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,529.5)\fad(864,0)\blur2}我才不会哭呢
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,============OP===============
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.96,0:00:48.05,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.30,0:00:51.34,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}いつからかな  不思議
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.68,0:00:57.81,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}この胸の奥はきみの欠片ばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.31,0:01:01.56,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs35\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.90,0:01:08.23,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}どうしよハート暴走  ドキドキ  デートの想像
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.57,0:01:11.36,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}キュンて飛び跳ねちゃう鼓動
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.49,0:01:14.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}自然に頬っぺたポッて  染まるの隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.70,0:01:16.91,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}気がついてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.08,0:01:22.83,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}傾いてく　ココロの角度
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.87,0:01:31.30,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}想いの視線はきみ向き　もう、恋をしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.01,0:01:35.80,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.30,0:01:39.39,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}エールを贈らせて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.60,0:01:45.81,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}きみが目指す空抱く  夢を一緒に追いかけるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.15,0:01:49.15,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Candy Candy Love  Candy Candy Love
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.52,0:01:52.49,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}リードはまだまだ頼りないかも  でも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.86,0:01:58.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}背中に寄り添うささえにね、なれたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.33,0:02:03.12,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}ソットソット·スキデ·イテモ·イイデスカ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.16,0:02:06.12,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs35\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.96,0:00:48.05,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.30,0:00:51.34,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}真是不可思议  不知何时起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.68,0:00:57.81,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}我的内心深处满是你的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.31,0:01:01.56,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs37\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.90,0:01:08.23,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}怎么办  忐忑不安  想象着约会的情景
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.57,0:01:11.36,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}不安的内心怦怦直跳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.49,0:01:14.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}就算我自然地鼓起脸颊  掩饰着这份心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.70,0:01:16.91,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}也请一定要注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.08,0:01:22.83,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}缓缓倾斜  心中的天平
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.87,0:01:31.30,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}看向你的眼神中充满爱  我已陷入了热恋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.01,0:01:35.80,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.30,0:01:39.39,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}请让我为你加油
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.60,0:01:45.81,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}拥抱你所追寻的天空  一起去追逐梦想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.15,0:01:49.15,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Candy Candy Love  Candy Candy Love
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.52,0:01:52.49,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}或许我现在还无法很好地指引你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.86,0:01:58.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}但若能成为你的后盾  支撑着你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.33,0:02:03.12,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}可不可以·让我·悄悄地·喜欢着你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.16,0:02:06.12,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs37\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,============ED===============
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.45,0:22:00.15,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}ピカピカと光る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.54,0:22:02.28,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}僕だけのSweet Love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.58,0:22:06.41,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}かなえるかな  この愛は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.67,0:22:08.28,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}満ちてくる恋は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.67,0:22:10.54,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}何色だろうな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.84,0:22:14.71,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}すこしだけ見せようかな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.93,0:22:18.54,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}トキメキと回る小さな瞬間
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.02,0:22:22.80,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}わき起こる色がある
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.10,0:22:27.02,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}ゆらゆらと揺れる小さな世界を
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.24,0:22:31.06,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}そっと  そっと  いやしてくるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.37,0:22:35.19,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}お茶目過ぎな君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.45,0:22:39.24,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}僕の中を巡り巡るよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.28,0:22:40.97,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}くるくる回る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.02,0:22:43.37,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}踊る君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.41,0:22:44.97,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}駆け抜けていく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.02,0:22:47.19,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}はじけたソーダみたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.24,0:22:49.19,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}すてきなカラーの君は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.19,0:22:51.37,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}僕を感じてるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.37,0:22:53.24,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.32,0:22:55.67,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}キラキラな甘いラブ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.71,0:22:57.37,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}くるくる回る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.45,0:22:59.54,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}踊る君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.80,0:23:01.41,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}舞い上がるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.45,0:23:03.54,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}柔らかなイチゴミルク
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.58,0:23:05.58,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}すてきなカラーの君は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.63,0:23:07.71,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}何を描いてるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.84,0:23:09.71,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.76,0:23:11.97,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}キラキラな甘いラブ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.45,0:22:00.15,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}闪闪发亮
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.54,0:22:02.28,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}只属于我的甜美爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.58,0:22:06.41,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}这份爱能否实现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.67,0:22:08.28,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}渐渐满溢的爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.67,0:22:10.54,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}究竟是什么颜色呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.84,0:22:14.71,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}稍微让你看一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.93,0:22:18.54,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}回荡的微小瞬间使我的心悸动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.02,0:22:22.80,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}浮现出了斑斓色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.10,0:22:27.02,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}将来回摇摆的渺小世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.24,0:22:31.06,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}静静地  静静地  治愈
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.37,0:22:35.19,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}你的色彩实在太过淘气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.45,0:22:39.24,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}在我的心中往往复复
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.28,0:22:40.97,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}咕噜咕噜地旋转
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.02,0:22:43.37,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}你的色彩开始起舞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.41,0:22:44.97,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}一路飞奔而过
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.02,0:22:47.19,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}如同喷发的汽水一般
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.24,0:22:49.19,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}色彩缤纷的你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.19,0:22:51.37,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}是否能感受到我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.37,0:22:53.24,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.32,0:22:55.67,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}甜蜜的爱情正闪闪发光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.71,0:22:57.37,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}咕噜咕噜地旋转
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.45,0:22:59.54,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}你的色彩开始起舞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.80,0:23:01.41,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}能否随风起舞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.45,0:23:03.54,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}这柔软的草莓牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.58,0:23:05.58,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}色彩缤纷的你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.63,0:23:07.71,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}正在描绘着什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.84,0:23:09.71,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.80,0:23:11.97,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}甜蜜的爱情正闪闪发光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,EDtitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
