[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-05-26 11:31:04
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Papakiki
Original Script:CASO&SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,49,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0A000000,&H00505C9D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,57,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9F9F9,&H1E22E468,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,5,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: EDtitle,方正准圆_GBK,57,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9F9F9,&H1E28A155,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,0,5,30,30,15,1
Style: OPJ,DFGMaruMoji-SL,41,&H003797EA,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H323797EA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,3,8,23,23,15,128
Style: OPC,华康少女文字W5(P),41,&H003797EA,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H323797EA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,3,2,23,23,15,1
Style: staff,方正黑体_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H3C000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,23,1
Style: EDJ,DFGMaruGothic-Md,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H323797EA,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,23,23,15,128
Style: EDC,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H323797EA,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,23,23,15,1
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,44,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0A000000,&H00505C9D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.85,0:00:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吧  舅舅好像非常紧张的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.13,0:00:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起打扫了房间  一定没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.99,0:00:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比想象中做的认真呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.62,0:00:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有担心这环境会不会束缚着她们的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.35,0:00:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之暂时算是放心了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.63,0:00:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是说…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.03,0:00:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  就再继续看看情况吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.60,0:00:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  祐太
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.22,0:00:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新学期开始的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.30,0:00:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况就会变得比现在麻烦很多倍  你明白的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.49,0:00:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  我知道  没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.63,0:00:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蚂蚁先生蚂蚁先生要去哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.43,0:01:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不得了的队伍呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.81,0:01:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店主
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.07,0:01:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.63,0:01:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.12,0:01:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们经常遇到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.04,0:01:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  今天也是帮忙家务吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.25,0:01:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.27,0:01:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三人都很了不起呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.76,0:01:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了不起？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.49,0:01:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们很了不起吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.65,0:01:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  了不起了不起哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.54,0:01:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就给这样的小雏一点奖励吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.64,0:01:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  冰淇淋  谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.89,0:01:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.02,0:01:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啦  不快点吃的话就化了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.51,0:01:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不好意思  让您费心了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.75,0:01:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用这么拘谨也没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.19,0:01:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是很可靠的姐姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.01,0:02:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  她是让人自豪的姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.44,0:02:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说美羽啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.76,0:02:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在害羞了在害羞了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.93,0:02:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.60,0:00:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.73,0:03:42.65,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(939,436)\pos(343,186)}每次都给大家添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.17,0:03:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏你能坚持干完啊  濑川
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.54,0:03:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和外表看上去不同  你还是挺有毅力的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.80,0:03:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然打工只到今天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.46,0:03:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们美式足球部一直欢迎你  再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.09,0:03:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然连续夜班会吃不消啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.80,0:04:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎～呀～  快～来～救～救～我～  救～救～我～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.74,0:04:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎～呀～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.35,0:04:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说…总之先救你就可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.70,0:04:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  哎～呀～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.29,0:04:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上钩了呢  濑川祐太
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.08,0:04:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐古学长？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.68,0:04:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濑川  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.06,0:04:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仁川你…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.13,0:04:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.14,0:04:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太萌捆绑巫女  又发现了一个新的性癖…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.13,0:04:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.30,0:05:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  到底有什么事  都做到这种程度了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.56,0:05:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼  那是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.69,0:05:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要见我家外甥女？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.74,0:05:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.38,0:05:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  好像学长跟美羽在电话里聊过了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.55,0:05:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到现在都无法忘怀的那美丽天使的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.43,0:05:32.19,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到时候就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.40,0:05:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一眼  让我看一眼那身姿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.75,0:05:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  这个的话你早点说嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.15,0:05:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.30,0:05:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.51,0:05:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.09,0:05:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想和可爱的外甥女在同一屋檐下吃饭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.69,0:05:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.99,0:05:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太的外甥女  可爱么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.43,0:05:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.56,0:06:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  要来我家吃个晚饭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.90,0:06:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.04,0:06:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK  今晚和幼女吃晚餐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.43,0:06:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.13,0:06:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.72,0:06:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.91,0:06:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是织田莱香  请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.73,0:06:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次见面  我是小鸟游美羽  今年十岁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.27,0:06:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐还真是个美人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.78,0:06:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个哦  那个哦  小雏三岁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.92,0:06:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次见面  请多关照哦  小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.88,0:06:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小空也去打个招呼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.26,0:06:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是长女小鸟游空  请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.22,0:07:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你这样对客人很失礼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.32,0:07:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  她还是个孩子…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.01,0:07:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.97,0:07:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次买点蛋糕什么的来弥补吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.15,0:07:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.72,0:07:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天承蒙邀请  不胜感激
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.89,0:07:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  好漂亮  谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.31,0:07:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终  终于找到了  my angel 美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.79,0:07:46.42,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.67,0:07:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后这边是前途不可限量的天使的种子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.26,0:07:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后宫啊  后宫  后宫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.11,0:08:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是小空吧  好像是14岁来着
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.95,0:08:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.26,0:08:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切  其中一个是大妈么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.24,0:08:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在意  小空很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.21,0:08:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱成分100%  纯天然
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.56,0:08:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.60,0:08:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是女生我也不会放水  因为是14岁的大妈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.74,0:08:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.65,0:08:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空姐姐加油
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.16,0:08:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很在意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.11,0:08:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然会在意…美羽？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.11,0:08:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  做好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.88,0:09:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.02,0:09:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先从祐太开始
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.97,0:09:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.07,0:09:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用费心  哥哥的那份我来盛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.89,0:09:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小空
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.70,0:09:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  我的话就不满意么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.25,0:09:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.23,0:09:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小舅舅小舅舅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.08,0:09:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.89,0:09:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那我就恭敬不如从命  让你喂我吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.82,0:09:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏  接下来是我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.17,0:09:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好狡猾  小雏  我也要我也要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.96,0:09:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要我也要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.25,0:09:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有学长是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.18,0:09:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么只有我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.05,0:09:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是一段美妙的时光啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.49,0:10:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次看到那样的莱香小姐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.62,0:10:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢可爱的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.64,0:10:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱的孩子就是正义  可爱最强
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.88,0:10:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工很累吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.11,0:10:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说累确实累  不过这是为了生活
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.75,0:10:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太有点改变了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.74,0:10:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.06,0:10:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不能很好地表达出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.21,0:10:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我觉得是个好变化
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.22,0:10:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.31,0:10:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔就好了  来活动室露个脸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.93,0:10:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太不来的话很寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.75,0:10:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂寞？谁会？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.75,0:10:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.80,0:10:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐古学长么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.12,0:11:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也少许有点寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.94,0:11:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.99,0:11:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那个  下次可以请你来教我做菜吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.87,0:11:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时都可以叫我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.33,0:11:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.70,0:11:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安  莱香小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.11,0:11:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,lunaluna～～飞踢！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.80,0:11:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,lunaluna～～手刀！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.28,0:11:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不会就这么结束的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.28,0:12:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会就这么结束的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.64,0:12:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒  赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.00,0:12:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是声优  总感觉演得好专业
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.64,0:12:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.29,0:12:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.60,0:12:20.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上潘多拉是不会有那么夸张的演技的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.35,0:12:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽  小雏  差不多吃午饭了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.43,0:12:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.47,0:12:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的午饭吃什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.59,0:12:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉面  凉面  还是凉面
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.62,0:12:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.32,0:12:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉面
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.12,0:12:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也终于结束了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.40,0:12:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很努力啊  濑川君
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.56,0:12:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.72,0:13:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能来真是帮大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.71,0:13:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.71,0:13:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个月也很努力地在工作  薪水帮你加了一点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.60,0:13:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢  店长
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.63,0:13:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽如此  但现在的处境也没法乐观起来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.65,0:13:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到池袋上学的月票2人份啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.01,0:13:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当高的一笔花费啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.34,0:13:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不能再削减饭钱了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.26,0:13:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大学一开始上课  打工的时间也会减少…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.43,0:13:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱香小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.80,0:13:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候来教你做饭？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.73,0:13:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的会来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.97,0:13:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太有点改变了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.56,0:13:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不能很好地表达出来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.70,0:13:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我觉得是个好变化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.34,0:13:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是气馁的时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.54,0:13:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还能更加更加努力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.29,0:14:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在小空她们才是第一位
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.41,0:14:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.84,0:14:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个人坐电车上学还是第一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.96,0:14:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.74,0:14:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了来了来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.78,0:14:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讲座其一  炒饭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.52,0:14:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.98,0:14:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是把蛋打碎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.23,0:14:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  蛋…蛋…蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.88,0:14:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  你肚子痛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.22,0:14:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说小雏  她痛的不是肚子而是胸口哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.03,0:14:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.67,0:14:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.22,0:14:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.73,0:14:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太你弱爆了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.54,0:14:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.11,0:14:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要一起学
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.96,0:15:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.45,0:15:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗  莱香小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.05,0:15:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以  不如说是很欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.51,0:15:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  你看…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.60,0:15:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里要这样…这么一来的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.34,0:15:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.81,0:15:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐  小舅舅他们在玩什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.42,0:15:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个不是在玩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.06,0:15:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个叫做修罗场哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.52,0:15:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我去打工了  之后就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.71,0:15:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽和小雏也是  不要给莱香小姐添麻烦哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.27,0:15:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.75,0:15:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏喜欢小莱香
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.95,0:15:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  不是小莱香  而是莱香姐姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.02,0:15:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太  没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.95,0:15:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫小莱香也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.84,0:15:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.19,0:15:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…对了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.53,0:15:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来时有个稍微想去一下的地方  会晚点到家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.32,0:16:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.54,0:16:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身材又好  长相可以和模特相媲美  还擅长料理
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.24,0:16:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么完美的人啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.45,0:16:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.47,0:16:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.58,0:16:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…哥哥在学校是给人怎样的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.76,0:16:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.47,0:16:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在莱香小姐看起来  哥哥感觉怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.36,0:16:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.07,0:16:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点兴趣是指…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.12,0:16:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…是作为男性来看的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.61,0:16:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为观察对象吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.91,0:17:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,观察…吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.00,0:17:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空  小空  放太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.02,0:17:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…那个…呃…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.73,0:17:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱香小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.98,0:17:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,no problem
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.26,0:17:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.93,0:17:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.73,0:17:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和小空一起洗澡反而很幸运
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.03,0:17:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌和我一起吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.83,0:17:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.66,0:17:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.87,0:18:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.77,0:18:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么样才能变得那么大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.32,0:18:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变大是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.99,0:18:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如喝牛奶  或者是按摩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.29,0:18:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并没有特意做过什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.41,0:18:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬要说的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.33,0:18:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢可爱的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.10,0:18:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盯～～～～
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.15,0:18:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.84,0:18:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次见到会说「盯～～～～」的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.94,0:18:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.90,0:18:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.93,0:18:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.65,0:18:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱香小姐  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.14,0:18:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小莱香  我也要一起蹭蹭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.37,0:19:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱香小姐果然脱了也很大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.18,0:19:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  挤不下了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.17,0:19:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.17,0:19:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  美羽  小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.93,0:19:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  这个能帮我包起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.41,0:19:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点忘了  惊喜  惊喜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.80,0:19:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.11,0:19:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小舅舅  欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.83,0:19:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.21,0:19:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  莱香小姐已经回去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.90,0:19:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空  美羽  你们过来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.15,0:19:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.07,0:19:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩今后要坐电车上学对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.84,0:19:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是 差不多该买月票了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.29,0:19:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.27,0:20:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.75,0:20:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想要休学一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.52,0:20:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏的幼稚园也还没有着落
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.80,0:20:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在舅舅去大学的这段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.93,0:20:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不好好照顾她的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.70,0:20:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.22,0:20:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  我会照顾好小雏的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.99,0:20:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  学分多少会少拿一些
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.04,0:20:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些之后再挽回就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.18,0:20:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但打工呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.36,0:20:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.45,0:20:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在的时候  就拜托仁村或者莱香小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.59,0:20:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  那两个人的话一定会过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.22,0:20:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  果然我们自己的事还是由自己来负责吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.30,0:20:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能再给大家添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.87,0:20:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.07,0:21:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.08,0:21:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  管理员小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.78,0:21:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在方便么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.58,0:21:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.42,0:21:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搬走？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.30,0:21:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了  招呼也不打一声就让4个人住在这一间房间
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.90,0:21:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想都不合理吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.01,0:21:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为是亲戚过来玩就稍微观察了一下情况
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.67,0:21:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这明摆着是违反合约
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.10,0:21:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濑川先生  一个月  请在一个月之内搬离这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.12,0:21:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.71,0:23:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一个喜欢的人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.58,0:23:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在身边  但却感觉很遥远
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.92,0:23:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不想再离他更远了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.53,0:23:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回  我不会让它发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.38,0:23:35.30,EDtitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,529.5)\blur2\fad(900,0)}我不会让它发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.79,0:23:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么做才能在明天也绽放出笑容呢
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,============OP===============
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.97,0:02:18.05,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.30,0:02:21.35,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}いつからかな  不思議
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.68,0:02:27.81,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}この胸の奥はきみの欠片ばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.31,0:02:31.57,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs35\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.90,0:02:38.24,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}どうしよハート暴走  ドキドキ  デートの想像
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.57,0:02:41.37,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}キュンて飛び跳ねちゃう鼓動
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.49,0:02:44.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}自然に頬っぺたポッて  染まるの隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.70,0:02:46.92,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}気がついてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.08,0:02:52.84,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}傾いてく　ココロの角度
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.88,0:03:01.30,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}想いの視線はきみ向き　もう、恋をしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.01,0:03:05.81,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.31,0:03:09.40,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}エールを贈らせて
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.60,0:03:15.82,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}きみが目指す空抱く  夢を一緒に追いかけるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.15,0:03:19.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Candy Candy Love  Candy Candy Love
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.53,0:03:22.49,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}リードはまだまだ頼りないかも  でも
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.87,0:03:28.67,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}背中に寄り添うささえにね、なれたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.33,0:03:33.13,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}ソットソット·スキデ·イテモ·イイデスカ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.17,0:03:36.13,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs35\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.97,0:02:18.05,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.30,0:02:21.35,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}真是不可思议  不知何时起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.68,0:02:27.81,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}我的内心深处满是你的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.31,0:02:31.57,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs37\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.90,0:02:38.24,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}怎么办  忐忑不安  想象着约会的情景
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.57,0:02:41.37,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}不安的内心怦怦直跳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.49,0:02:44.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}就算我自然地鼓起脸颊  掩饰着这份心情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.70,0:02:46.92,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}也请一定要注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.08,0:02:52.84,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}缓缓倾斜  心中的天平
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.88,0:03:01.30,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}看向你的眼神中充满爱  我已陷入了热恋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.01,0:03:05.81,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.31,0:03:09.40,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}请让我为你加油
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.60,0:03:15.82,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}拥抱你所追寻的天空  一起去追逐梦想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.15,0:03:19.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Candy Candy Love  Candy Candy Love
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.53,0:03:22.49,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}或许我现在还无法很好地指引你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.87,0:03:28.67,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}但若能成为你的后盾  支撑着你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.33,0:03:33.13,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}可不可以·让我·悄悄地·喜欢着你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.17,0:03:36.13,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs37\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,============ED===============
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.83,0:21:59.54,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ピカピカと光る
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.95,0:22:01.66,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}僕だけのSweet Love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.95,0:22:05.79,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}かなえるかな  この愛は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.08,0:22:07.67,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}満ちてくる恋は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.04,0:22:09.92,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}何色だろうな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.21,0:22:14.09,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}すこしだけ見せようかな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.34,0:22:17.93,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキと回る小さな瞬間
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.43,0:22:22.18,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}わき起こる色がある
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.47,0:22:26.40,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ゆらゆらと揺れる小さな世界を
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.65,0:22:30.44,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}そっと  そっと  いやしてくるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.77,0:22:34.57,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}お茶目過ぎな君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.86,0:22:38.62,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}僕の中を巡り巡るよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.66,0:22:40.37,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}くるくる回る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.41,0:22:42.74,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}踊る君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.79,0:22:44.37,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}駆け抜けていく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.41,0:22:46.58,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}はじけたソーダみたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.62,0:22:48.58,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}すてきなカラーの君は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.58,0:22:50.75,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}僕を感じてるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.75,0:22:52.63,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.71,0:22:55.05,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}キラキラな甘いラブ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.09,0:22:56.76,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}くるくる回る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.84,0:22:58.93,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}踊る君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.18,0:23:00.80,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}舞い上がるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.85,0:23:02.93,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}柔らかなイチゴミルク
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.97,0:23:04.98,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}すてきなカラーの君は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.02,0:23:07.10,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}何を描いてるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.23,0:23:09.10,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.15,0:23:11.36,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}キラキラな甘いラブ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.83,0:21:59.54,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}闪闪发亮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.95,0:22:01.66,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}只属于我的甜美爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.95,0:22:05.79,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}这份爱能否实现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.08,0:22:07.67,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}渐渐满溢的爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.04,0:22:09.92,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}究竟是什么颜色呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.21,0:22:14.09,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}稍微让你看一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.34,0:22:17.93,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}回荡的微小瞬间使我的心悸动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.43,0:22:22.18,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}浮现出了斑斓色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.47,0:22:26.40,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}将来回摇摆的渺小世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.65,0:22:30.44,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}静静地  静静地  治愈
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.77,0:22:34.57,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你的色彩实在太过淘气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.86,0:22:38.62,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}在我的心中往往复复
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.66,0:22:40.37,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}咕噜咕噜地旋转
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.41,0:22:42.74,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你的色彩开始起舞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.79,0:22:44.37,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}一路飞奔而过
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.41,0:22:46.58,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}如同喷发的汽水一般
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.62,0:22:48.58,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}色彩缤纷的你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.58,0:22:50.75,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是否能感受到我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.75,0:22:52.63,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.71,0:22:55.05,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}甜蜜的爱情正闪闪发光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.09,0:22:56.76,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}咕噜咕噜地旋转
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.84,0:22:58.93,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你的色彩开始起舞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.18,0:23:00.80,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}能否随风起舞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.85,0:23:02.93,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}这柔软的草莓牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.97,0:23:04.98,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}色彩缤纷的你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.02,0:23:07.10,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}正在描绘着什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.23,0:23:09.10,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.19,0:23:11.36,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}甜蜜的爱情正闪闪发光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.60,0:00:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
