[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-05-15 21:18:33
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Papakiki
Original Script:CASO&SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,49,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0A000000,&H00505C9D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,57,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9F9F9,&H1E22E468,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,5,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: EDtitle,方正准圆_GBK,57,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9F9F9,&H1E28A155,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,0,5,30,30,15,1
Style: OPJ,DFGMaruMoji-SL,41,&H003797EA,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H323797EA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,3,8,23,23,15,128
Style: OPC,华康少女文字W5(P),41,&H003797EA,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H323797EA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,3,2,23,23,15,1
Style: staff,方正黑体_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H3C000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,23,1
Style: INE,方正准圆_GBK,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,20,20,20,1
Style: EDJ,DFGMaruGothic-Md,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H323797EA,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,23,23,15,128
Style: EDC,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H323797EA,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,23,23,15,1
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,43,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0A000000,&H00505C9D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,15,1
Style: INC,方正准圆_GBK,37,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,20,20,20,1
Style: INJ,DFMaruGothic-Md,34,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,20,20,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.98,0:00:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来我家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.19,0:00:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很穷  房间又小而且什么都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.26,0:00:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过三个人一起也没有关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.46,0:00:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.33,0:00:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.09,0:00:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要趁势说些不可能的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.11,0:00:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且就算你和小雏是血亲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.68,0:00:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是和小空美羽完全是没关系的外人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.16,0:00:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这又怎么样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.58,0:00:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血亲什么的随他去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.41,0:00:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家人一定得要在一起才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.59,0:02:18.97,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,431)\pos(317,600)}我才不会哭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.14,0:02:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  跑哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.11,0:02:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二楼也没人  难道…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.60,0:02:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先到车站去找吧  应该还能赶上
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.31,0:02:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  他都干了些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.46,0:02:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐  小舅舅那是什么  黄色的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.90,0:02:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是西武线
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.87,0:02:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么那个银色的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.80,0:02:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是中央线
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.54,0:02:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.51,0:02:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个也是中央线
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.88,0:02:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.28,0:02:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛  很痛的啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.78,0:02:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很痛的啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.44,0:02:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.69,0:02:47.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.17,0:02:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏  不要太大声哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.80,0:02:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.90,0:02:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会给别人添麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.22,0:02:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.36,0:03:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅  你没有后悔吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.61,0:03:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  你突然说这个干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.09,0:03:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为最后不是把姑父姑母们都甩掉了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.26,0:03:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.53,0:03:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得以后会很辛苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.75,0:03:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.27,0:03:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是也不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.83,0:03:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被两位美少女和一位美少女预备军围绕着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.73,0:03:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸都笑烂了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.13,0:03:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.22,0:03:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.34,0:03:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你振作的很快呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.94,0:03:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为跑出家门的时候觉得像电影一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.41,0:03:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情绪很高涨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.52,0:03:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话也好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.70,0:03:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于到了  好像郊游一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.81,0:03:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂我们要去哪里  动物园?游乐场?Unauna haven show?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.81,0:03:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs40.000002}注：这里是小雏发音错误
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.87,0:03:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么天国啊  Unauna haven
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.10,0:04:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是luna luna 7  周日早上的特摄动画
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.98,0:04:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,lunacular～～闪光！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.99,0:04:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs40.000002}注：小雏的发音与鳗鱼串相似
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.46,0:04:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这听起来很好吃的招数是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.69,0:04:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小舅舅也来说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.12,0:04:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.96,0:04:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着  lunacular…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.77,0:04:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪光
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.72,0:04:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  比想象中要繁华呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.08,0:04:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  你这样会跟立川的居民杠上的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.77,0:04:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这样的小镇的话买东西也很方便的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.27,0:04:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.86,0:04:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要到我住的公寓  还必须得坐很久的那个才行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.32,0:04:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要坐么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.34,0:04:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过在那之前
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.13,0:04:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午饭午饭  家庭参听
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.00,0:04:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  是家庭餐厅吧  给我好好发音啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.77,0:04:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家·庭·餐·厅
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.55,0:04:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家·庭·参·听
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.51,0:04:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  就这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.93,0:04:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得不错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.07,0:04:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.85,0:04:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就进去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.23,0:05:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这么想着…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.05,0:05:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了  今天是周日么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.75,0:05:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是一家人来吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.30,0:05:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在看着这种温馨的场面还太难受了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.59,0:05:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里人满了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.94,0:05:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里不提供饮料畅饮
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.75,0:05:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐  这里空空的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.70,0:05:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么价格啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.38,0:05:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏觉得这里就好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.89,0:05:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里稍微…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.76,0:05:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是去刚才的店吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.58,0:05:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.71,0:05:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要不要  就这里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.16,0:05:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩都别这样  要听话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.17,0:05:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.53,0:05:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那在哪里吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.31,0:05:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就…对了  就去那里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.19,0:05:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来像是迷一般的国家的动画啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.71,0:06:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐也来唱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.38,0:06:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是二重唱么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.38,0:06:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  所以和舅舅一起唱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.54,0:06:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不会唱的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.24,0:06:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就跟舅舅来炒热气氛咯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.31,0:06:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好  点什么我都唱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.77,0:06:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让您久等了  这是炸鸡和薯条
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.27,0:06:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.49,0:06:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.82,0:06:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大学里同一个社团的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.11,0:06:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  突然有急事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.04,0:06:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次一定会好好补偿你的  抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.20,0:06:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么情况  你因为现实中没有恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.74,0:06:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以终于走上了罪恶的道路了么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.39,0:06:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  那是我的外甥女
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.53,0:06:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐的女儿们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.35,0:06:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个又漂亮又温柔而且还很漂亮的祐理小姐的？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.85,0:07:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  因为发生了很多事  所以我领着她们回来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.80,0:07:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么  那太好了  不用去报案
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.76,0:07:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.72,0:07:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}来电  好子阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.54,0:07:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.17,0:07:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.90,0:07:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲戚打来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.25,0:07:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不忍看着她们被分开
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.70,0:07:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以差不多算是强拉她们过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.33,0:07:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是呆子么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.43,0:07:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话得快点接电话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.94,0:07:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去让她们开心一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.98,0:07:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以和亲戚好好说下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.10,0:07:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仁村…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.31,0:07:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不吃吗  姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.77,0:07:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再等等
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.73,0:07:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是会冷掉的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.43,0:07:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了  等着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.21,0:07:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊  小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.05,0:07:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.77,0:08:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.74,0:08:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是舅舅的…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.94,0:08:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  好朋友仁村浩一
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.97,0:08:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次见面  请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.66,0:08:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.12,0:08:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是花啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.49,0:08:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙好像要上很久的厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.23,0:08:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我来做你们的保镖
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.64,0:08:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.13,0:08:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仁村先生很帅呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.59,0:08:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  你也很可爱哦  那头发是染的么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.71,0:08:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  生来就这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.48,0:08:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  你肯定能当模特哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.40,0:08:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  如果可以的话要来一起唱歌吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.19,0:08:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK  把气氛炒到最高吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.92,0:08:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.33,0:08:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.79,0:08:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.73,0:08:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干了这么一件大事  接下来打算怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.12,0:09:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会养育那些孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.55,0:09:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不容易  不过我会增加打工
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.89,0:09:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大学要怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.70,0:09:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果因为这样而落下了学业的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.24,0:09:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐理也会伤心的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.99,0:09:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.62,0:09:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有在听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.37,0:09:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.39,0:09:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之我先跟小鸟游家的人道歉说情了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.09,0:09:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.23,0:09:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你没有坚定的觉悟的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.16,0:09:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就立刻带着三人回来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.90,0:09:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然她们反而会变得不幸
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.55,0:09:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.35,0:10:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  没什么事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.35,0:10:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就去我家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.21,0:10:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.57,0:10:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单轨电车  单轨电车
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.39,0:10:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这之后是去有飞机的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.43,0:10:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这跟去羽田的方向不同  不会去飞机的地方哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.59,0:10:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  还以为去是迎接他们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.22,0:10:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏看那边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.83,0:10:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很漂亮的晚霞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.59,0:10:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里都行走着去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.70,0:10:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想哭的时候看上边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.62,0:10:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呆在原地就能看到梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.24,0:10:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能遇到黏糊糊先生么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.58,0:10:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黏糊糊先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.77,0:11:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在录像里看到的黏糊糊先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.96,0:11:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就住在像这里的一样树很多的地方哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.60,0:11:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏还真是有精神啊  不会累吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.87,0:11:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没问题哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.70,0:11:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么小孩子睡觉的时候会这么重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.73,0:11:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换我来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.60,0:11:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  马上就到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.40,0:11:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.67,0:11:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.82,0:11:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样小雏  这就是小舅舅的公寓
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.19,0:11:42.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒  比小雏家还大  有好多房间
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.38,0:11:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就收拾
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.22,0:11:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真…真是个可爱的厨房呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.20,0:11:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和小雏家的洗手间一样大
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.85,0:12:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.65,0:12:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用那么拘谨  进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.09,0:12:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.29,0:12:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗…洗澡的地方也好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.59,0:12:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起居室呢  还有别的房间呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.49,0:12:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有没有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.20,0:12:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整理的比想象之中要干净呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.79,0:12:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.39,0:12:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现H的书
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.16,0:12:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是仁村的  那家伙真是个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.14,0:12:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然忘在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.81,0:12:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的啦  玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.09,0:12:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开这样的玩笑啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.83,0:12:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你那么紧张  就说明一定藏在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.46,0:12:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.72,0:12:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想都觉得放张床太占地方了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.77,0:12:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐呐  这里是小舅舅的家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.71,0:13:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  现在开始也是小雏的家了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.97,0:13:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏的家？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.69,0:13:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏的家不是这里哦  在家能看到日照的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.11,0:13:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说  小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.79,0:13:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.49,0:13:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好  那里的家已经没办法回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.41,0:13:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.74,0:13:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢  对现在的小雏解释还太复杂了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.80,0:13:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  今天开始这里就是我们的新家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.19,0:13:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.38,0:13:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  先把床收拾掉腾出多点地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.43,0:13:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空  美羽  拜托你们帮忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.34,0:13:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.47,0:13:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏呢小雏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.73,0:13:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.18,0:13:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.79,0:13:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来四个人也没什么很宽敞了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.43,0:13:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错  总觉得有种去朋友家留宿的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.78,0:14:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…能不能借用一下厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.87,0:14:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用那么拘谨的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.02,0:14:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桌子也搬到阳台吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.22,0:14:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,lunaluna拳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.63,0:14:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  不得了了  怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.93,0:14:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  突然之间
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.26,0:14:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能听到哦？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.79,0:14:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.45,0:14:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说  能听到姐姐上厕所的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.38,0:14:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.36,0:14:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.41,0:14:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想上厕所了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.81,0:14:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.37,0:14:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  不可能  不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.94,0:14:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.54,0:14:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定还有残留
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.48,0:14:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残留？什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.97,0:14:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事不要让我说出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.23,0:14:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该冲掉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.74,0:14:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.71,0:14:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲掉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.20,0:14:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是肯定的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.74,0:14:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  是什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.24,0:15:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅  你真不体贴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.76,0:15:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.83,0:15:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我大概要等多久
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.21,0:15:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是很清楚  一小时左右？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.34,0:15:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.09,0:15:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还想上完厕所做一下洗澡的准备
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.72,0:15:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也由我来做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.02,0:15:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.26,0:15:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.36,0:15:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  提问
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.15,0:15:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次又是什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.94,0:15:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我们应该在哪里换衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.25,0:15:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换衣服？啊  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.95,0:15:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没考虑过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.70,0:15:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  不是  那种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.68,0:15:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  舅舅  你有图钉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.90,0:16:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是应付过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.68,0:16:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  水都溢出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.16,0:16:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几乎溢出一半了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.99,0:16:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空姐姐  可以玩揉揉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.57,0:16:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.55,0:16:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗澡的时候一直玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.86,0:16:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,揉揉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.64,0:16:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  好痒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.28,0:16:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏忍了好久了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.49,0:16:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  总是和祐理小姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.66,0:16:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.87,0:16:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不安稳的一天啊  姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.35,0:16:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.39,0:16:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性感的现场换衣  不可以偷看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.07,0:16:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  才不会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.92,0:16:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷看小孩子换衣服的也没什么意义吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.51,0:16:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么傻话  美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.56,0:16:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.27,0:17:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖啦乖啦  小雏  过来把身体擦干
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.53,0:17:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热  我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.70,0:17:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏  笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.79,0:17:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湿着身体会感冒的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.75,0:17:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs45}好凉快 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.22,0:17:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空  毛巾
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.90,0:17:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给…给
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.45,0:17:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  不要看这边
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.93,0:17:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  全身还是湿的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.31,0:17:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  转朝这边
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.65,0:17:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  接着是左手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.70,0:17:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离这里远点再弄嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.66,0:17:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.97,0:17:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.65,0:17:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得很紧张啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.77,0:17:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.88,0:17:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起来玩扑克吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.69,0:17:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我不会手下留情的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.13,0:17:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会手下留情的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.71,0:17:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.29,0:18:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽太容易看穿了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.23,0:18:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彻底被骗了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.84,0:18:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  接着就到小雏了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.69,0:18:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,困了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.08,0:18:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好困
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.42,0:18:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就睡吧  今天就到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.68,0:18:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  爸爸和妈妈呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.07,0:18:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸和妈妈什么时候会过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.21,0:18:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.56,0:18:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经回家了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.17,0:18:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏  我说过的吧  爸爸和祐理小姐已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.20,0:18:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了很远的地方是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.31,0:18:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是会回来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.27,0:18:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为妈妈抱着小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.23,0:18:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说很快就会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.83,0:18:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出去买点东西  姐姐看好小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.92,0:18:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.80,0:18:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小舅舅也去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.08,0:18:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.90,0:19:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.91,0:19:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空姐姐  好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.65,0:19:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.76,0:19:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽姐姐去哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.72,0:19:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  马上就会回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.38,0:19:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买完东西了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.94,0:19:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忘记带钱包了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.62,0:19:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.95,0:20:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.42,0:20:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.73,0:20:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.65,0:20:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋笨蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.25,0:20:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.58,0:20:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被子有两条  加我的那条就可以三个人睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.34,0:20:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,床单和毯子姐姐之前也从家里带来过  所以也没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.47,0:20:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.79,0:20:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用坐垫就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.50,0:21:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和家里的味道一样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.37,0:21:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.31,0:21:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.97,0:21:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.95,0:21:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个人要一直在一起哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.67,0:21:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.85,0:23:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我是长女小空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在非常紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.39,0:23:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉  预告什么的还是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.45,0:23:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该说些什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.39,0:23:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？还剩5秒？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.52,0:23:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回是…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.21,0:23:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没时间了…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.40,0:23:35.44,EDtitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,529.5)\blur2\fad(649,0)}wonderful Life
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,============OP===============
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.06,0:00:55.15,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.40,0:00:58.44,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}いつからかな  不思議
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.78,0:01:04.91,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}この胸の奥はきみの欠片ばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.41,0:01:08.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs35\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.00,0:01:15.33,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}どうしよハート暴走  ドキドキ  デートの想像
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.67,0:01:18.46,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}キュンて飛び跳ねちゃう鼓動
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.59,0:01:21.76,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}自然に頬っぺたポッて  染まるの隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.80,0:01:24.01,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}気がついてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.18,0:01:29.93,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}傾いてく　ココロの角度
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.97,0:01:38.40,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}想いの視線はきみ向き　もう、恋をしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.11,0:01:42.90,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.40,0:01:46.49,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}エールを贈らせて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.70,0:01:52.91,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}きみが目指す空抱く  夢を一緒に追いかけるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.25,0:01:56.25,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Candy Candy Love  Candy Candy Love
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.62,0:01:59.59,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}リードはまだまだ頼りないかも  でも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.96,0:02:05.76,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}背中に寄り添うささえにね、なれたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.43,0:02:10.22,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}ソットソット·スキデ·イテモ·イイデスカ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.26,0:02:13.22,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs35\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.06,0:00:55.15,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.40,0:00:58.44,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}真是不可思议  不知何时起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.78,0:01:04.91,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}我的内心深处满是你的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.41,0:01:08.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs37\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.00,0:01:15.33,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}怎么办  忐忑不安  想象着约会的情景
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.67,0:01:18.46,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}不安的内心怦怦直跳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.59,0:01:21.76,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}就算我自然地鼓起脸颊  掩饰着这份心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.80,0:01:24.01,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}也请一定要注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.18,0:01:29.93,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}缓缓倾斜  心中的天平
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.97,0:01:38.40,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}看向你的眼神中充满爱  我已陷入了热恋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.11,0:01:42.90,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.40,0:01:46.49,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}请让我为你加油
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.70,0:01:52.91,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}拥抱你所追寻的天空  一起去追逐梦想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.25,0:01:56.25,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Candy Candy Love  Candy Candy Love
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.62,0:01:59.59,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}或许我现在还无法很好地指引你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.96,0:02:05.76,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}但若能成为你的后盾  支撑着你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.43,0:02:10.22,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}可不可以·让我·悄悄地·喜欢着你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.26,0:02:13.22,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs37\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,============ED===============
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.00,0:21:59.71,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}ピカピカと光る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.13,0:22:01.84,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}僕だけのSweet Love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.13,0:22:05.97,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}かなえるかな  この愛は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.26,0:22:07.84,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}満ちてくる恋は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.22,0:22:10.10,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}何色だろうな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.39,0:22:14.27,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}すこしだけ見せようかな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.52,0:22:18.10,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}トキメキと回る小さな瞬間
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.60,0:22:22.36,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}わき起こる色がある
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.65,0:22:26.57,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}ゆらゆらと揺れる小さな世界を
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.82,0:22:30.62,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}そっと  そっと  いやしてくるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.95,0:22:34.75,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}お茶目過ぎな君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.04,0:22:38.79,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}僕の中を巡り巡るよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.83,0:22:40.54,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}くるくる回る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.58,0:22:42.92,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}踊る君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.96,0:22:44.55,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}駆け抜けていく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.59,0:22:46.76,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}はじけたソーダみたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.80,0:22:48.76,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}すてきなカラーの君は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:50.93,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}僕を感じてるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.93,0:22:52.80,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.89,0:22:55.22,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}キラキラな甘いラブ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.27,0:22:56.93,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}くるくる回る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.02,0:22:59.10,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}踊る君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.35,0:23:00.98,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}舞い上がるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.02,0:23:03.11,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}柔らかなイチゴミルク
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.15,0:23:05.15,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}すてきなカラーの君は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.19,0:23:07.28,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}何を描いてるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.40,0:23:09.28,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.32,0:23:11.53,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}キラキラな甘いラブ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.00,0:21:59.71,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}闪闪发亮
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.13,0:22:01.84,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}只属于我的甜美爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.13,0:22:05.97,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}这份爱能否实现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.26,0:22:07.84,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}渐渐满溢的爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.22,0:22:10.10,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}究竟是什么颜色呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.39,0:22:14.27,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}稍微让你看一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.52,0:22:18.10,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}回荡的微小瞬间使我的心悸动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.60,0:22:22.36,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}浮现出了斑斓色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.65,0:22:26.57,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}将来回摇摆的渺小世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.82,0:22:30.62,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}静静地  静静地  治愈
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.95,0:22:34.75,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}你的色彩实在太过淘气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.04,0:22:38.79,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}在我的心中往往复复
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.83,0:22:40.54,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}咕噜咕噜地旋转
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.58,0:22:42.92,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}你的色彩开始起舞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.96,0:22:44.55,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}一路飞奔而过
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.59,0:22:46.76,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}如同喷发的汽水一般
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.80,0:22:48.76,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}色彩缤纷的你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:50.93,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}是否能感受到我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.93,0:22:52.80,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.89,0:22:55.22,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}甜蜜的爱情正闪闪发光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.27,0:22:56.93,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}咕噜咕噜地旋转
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.02,0:22:59.10,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}你的色彩开始起舞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.35,0:23:00.98,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}能否随风起舞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.02,0:23:03.11,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}这柔软的草莓牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.15,0:23:05.15,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}色彩缤纷的你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.19,0:23:07.28,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}正在描绘着什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.40,0:23:09.28,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.36,0:23:11.53,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)\blur5}甜蜜的爱情正闪闪发光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.60,0:00:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
