[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2012-05-26 10:56:55
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Papakiki
Original Script:CASO&SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,49,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0A000000,&H00505C9D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,57,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9F9F9,&H1E22E468,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,5,0,2,30,30,15,1
Style: EDtitle,方正准圆_GBK,57,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9F9F9,&H1E28A155,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,0,5,30,30,15,1
Style: OPJ,DFGMaruMoji-SL,41,&H003797EA,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H323797EA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,3,8,23,23,15,128
Style: OPC,华康少女文字W5(P),41,&H003797EA,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H323797EA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,6,3,2,23,23,15,1
Style: staff,方正黑体_GBK,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H3C000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: EDJ,DFGMaruGothic-Md,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H323797EA,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,23,23,15,128
Style: EDC,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H323797EA,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,23,23,15,1
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0A000000,&H00505C9D,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,7,30,30,15,1
Style: INC,方正准圆_GBK,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,20,20,20,1
Style: INJ,DFMaruGothic-Md,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H78000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,20,20,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.63,0:00:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼  累死了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.71,0:00:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.33,0:00:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小舅舅  欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.64,0:00:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  这是所谓的不可抗力…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.36,0:00:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者说是飞来横祸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.65,0:00:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总…总之我  我不是故意的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.20,0:00:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.33,0:00:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅  你已经不是独居了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.89,0:00:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该多体谅一下别人了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.04,0:02:06.79,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(274,596)}少女这是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.77,0:02:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.68,0:02:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的打工是早班啊  再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.41,0:02:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路走好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.95,0:02:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路走好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.93,0:02:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.23,0:02:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要小心汽车哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.37,0:02:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把房间弄太乱了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.67,0:02:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.93,0:02:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  OK
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.19,0:02:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐真是的  还在为昨晚的事生气吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.08,0:02:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒没有
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.92,0:02:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房子小的话生活很不方便啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.92,0:02:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次洗澡都要把重新把床单钉在墙上  很费事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.37,0:02:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  画完了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.44,0:03:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.97,0:03:03.60,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\frz18.065\pos(613,55)}帘子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.02,0:03:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是像这样有帘子隔开就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.00,0:03:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.83,0:03:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样也不会占什么地方
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.54,0:03:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这要花钱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.78,0:03:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是问题所在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.46,0:03:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.46,0:03:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.16,0:03:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现响的搜集了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.84,0:03:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经是第五次响了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.30,0:03:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.36,0:03:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  终于接通了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.81,0:03:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濑川君  我找到了份不错的打工
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.50,0:03:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且工资还是每日结算哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.59,0:03:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.32,0:03:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你有在听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.50,0:03:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.86,0:03:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  出个声啊  喂  喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.54,0:03:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濑川君？你在听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.14,0:03:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.50,0:03:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦…喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.20,0:03:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.34,0:04:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  那个  我是他外甥女
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.04,0:04:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暑假期间到他家来玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.40,0:04:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是吗  原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.96,0:04:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是濑川君参加的研究会的会长佐古
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.09,0:04:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅承蒙您的关照了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.76,0:04:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个懂礼貌的姑娘啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.94,0:04:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要带着美好的回忆回去哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.52,0:04:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濑川君打工忙的话  我也可以做向导来带你逛东京哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.08,0:04:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到时候就拜托您了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.01,0:04:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问您怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.36,0:04:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不  抱歉  我没听清  能再说一次吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.08,0:04:36.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.30,0:04:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到时候就拜托您了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.14,0:04:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好难受
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.04,0:04:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.84,0:04:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐古先生吗  是个温柔的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.15,0:04:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然还能帮舅舅找打工的地点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.14,0:04:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到时候就拜托您了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.26,0:05:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这声音简直如同天使般甜美啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.71,0:05:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濑川君身上所散发的天使芳香原来是出自这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.04,0:05:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从声音来看她大概是10岁
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.50,0:05:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我希望她正好是10岁
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.25,0:05:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发型当然是金发双马尾
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.58,0:05:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再配上小恶魔般的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.98,0:05:18.15,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs35}てへぺろ是日笠阳子的固有捏他  表现方式为「哎嘿(>ω<)」地边笑边吐舌头
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.98,0:05:18.15,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多在犯错时用来装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.91,0:05:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.65,0:05:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天使
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.65,0:05:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40}My Angel
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.55,0:05:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,织田君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.98,0:05:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.38,0:05:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  又…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.33,0:05:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要…要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.71,0:05:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太的外甥女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.42,0:05:35.67,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要删除吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.84,0:05:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到时候就拜托…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.67,0:05:36.17,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,删除中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.17,0:05:36.92,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已删除
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.54,0:05:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给舅舅打个电话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.68,0:05:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊  万一打扰他工作怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.23,0:05:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.24,0:05:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是拿舅舅没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.95,0:05:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可真是个冒失鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.43,0:05:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我去去就回
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.23,0:06:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路走好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.87,0:06:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.72,0:06:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽姐姐快看快看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.00,0:06:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？看谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.38,0:06:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.51,0:06:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空姐姐欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.38,0:06:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.40,0:06:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.05,0:06:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我果然还是换下衣服再去比较好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.80,0:06:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.83,0:06:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.16,0:06:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问您是一位吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.02,0:06:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  虽然我觉得应该是这里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.71,0:07:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.63,0:07:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但果然不是这家店
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.63,0:07:02.31,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2}（但果然这家店不行）
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.46,0:07:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.45,0:07:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请  等…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.76,0:07:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.66,0:07:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.67,0:07:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是小空啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.72,0:07:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是来把那个送给我的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.49,0:07:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请注意一点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.33,0:07:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  下次出门时我会确认的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.96,0:07:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别忘了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.47,0:07:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键时刻要是联系不上可就麻烦了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.07,0:07:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.01,0:07:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就  就是  很麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.13,0:07:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好好打工吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.68,0:07:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.21,0:07:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你特意送来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.81,0:08:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.29,0:08:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任务完成  辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.05,0:08:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅有对姐姐的衣服发表什么评论吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.72,0:08:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他倒没说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.35,0:08:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然他不会体贴人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.64,0:08:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  我又没有在意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.65,0:08:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明姐姐你还特意打扮一番
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.59,0:08:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说我一点也不在意…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.50,0:08:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这身衣服明明是姐姐最中意的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.64,0:08:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.34,0:08:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手机快没电了  我先挂了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.93,0:08:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.75,0:09:03.84,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs36}两人的破绽只有一瞬
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.75,0:09:03.84,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs36}但却被抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.75,0:09:03.84,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs36}两人开始痛苦地挣扎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.75,0:09:03.84,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs36}「哎嘿嘿!!你们完蛋了LunaLuna7!!」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.75,0:09:03.84,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs36}重大危机!!!LunaLuna7!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.58,0:09:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.78,0:09:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了  请问哪一位…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.54,0:09:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出现了啊  西瓜假面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.61,0:09:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雏  不可以过来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.09,0:09:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lunacular～～闪光！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.75,0:09:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.11,0:09:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是住隔壁的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.15,0:09:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是乡下的西瓜  要吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.21,0:09:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就来打扰真不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.79,0:09:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  暑假期间你们到亲戚的哥哥家里来玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.75,0:09:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.97,0:09:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们才是  还未登门拜访  十分抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.49,0:09:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.36,0:09:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真懂事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.61,0:09:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫小鸟游美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.38,0:09:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫小雏
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.22,0:10:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫新子胡桃  请多关照哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.87,0:10:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此彼此  请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.72,0:10:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐是学生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.32,0:10:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是面向学生出租的公寓所以你才这么想的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.96,0:10:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看我这样  我可是声优哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.91,0:10:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  你会上电视吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.05,0:10:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？  嗯  虽然只是偶尔上
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.63,0:10:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  快看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.56,0:10:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是早上吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.47,0:10:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是中午？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.14,0:10:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.30,0:10:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在播LunaLuna
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.08,0:10:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说是暑假LunaLuna7的播放大会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.32,0:10:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你束手无策了吧LunaLuna7
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.20,0:10:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真卑鄙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.90,0:10:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出现了啊  西瓜假面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.19,0:10:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我出演了这集
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.78,0:10:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.97,0:10:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐有出演吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.82,0:10:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐是LunaLuna吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.27,0:10:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.69,0:10:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  不是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.27,0:10:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快变身  我想看Lunacular闪光
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.98,0:11:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…我不是LunaLuna7
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.25,0:11:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让我们听听你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.79,0:11:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  小雏也变成LunaLuna
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.50,0:11:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lunacular～～闪光！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.84,0:11:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就到此为止  再会了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.83,0:11:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶啊LunaLuna7
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.97,0:11:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就到此为止  再会了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.69,0:11:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.84,0:11:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.59,0:12:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空还没有回来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.82,0:12:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  她是不是在买东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.55,0:12:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小舅舅早点回来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.96,0:12:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.71,0:12:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.81,0:13:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.09,0:13:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空  你现在在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.93,0:13:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像坐错公交车了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.43,0:13:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我来接你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.80,0:13:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  我自己可以回去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.98,0:13:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.67,0:13:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了没事的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.76,0:13:22.76,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}请充电
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.96,0:13:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我也不想再给他添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.94,0:13:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您所拨打的电话已关机或不在服务区内
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.28,0:13:40.78,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拨号记录
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.28,0:13:40.78,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.13,0:13:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濑川
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.63,0:13:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.30,0:13:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 我还想着要不要去看你努力工作的样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.22,0:13:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.21,0:13:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濑川？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.93,0:13:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空似乎是弄错了公交车的路线
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.56,0:14:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是说能自己回去的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.64,0:14:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她毕竟初来乍到  不懂的事情也很多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.68,0:14:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们分头去找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.08,0:14:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.07,0:15:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太  听我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.08,0:15:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说想让我见一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.69,0:15:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且和他在以结婚为前提交往着
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.44,0:15:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你突然对我这么说  我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.06,0:15:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.48,0:15:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事出突然  你想必很吃惊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.05,0:15:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我一直觉得总有一天必须告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.85,0:15:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去一下厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.17,0:15:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祐太…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.30,0:15:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美羽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.94,0:16:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛的话就不要忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.75,0:16:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.21,0:16:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  快让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.53,0:16:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  看上去就好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.10,0:16:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  等一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.43,0:16:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不就像是我把你弄哭了一样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.31,0:16:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  别哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.95,0:17:00.05,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细细的小雨  下个不停  妈妈她
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.61,0:17:04.59,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撑着蛇眼伞  前来接我  真开心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.23,0:17:07.25,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啪嗒啪嗒  哗啦哗啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.33,0:17:09.03,INC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啦啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.95,0:17:00.05,INJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あめあめ  ふれふれ  かあさんが
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.61,0:17:04.59,INJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃのめで  おむかい  うれしいな
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.23,0:17:07.25,INJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピッチピッチ  チャップチャップ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.33,0:17:09.03,INJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ランランラン
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.07,0:17:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  贴好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.13,0:17:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐很久前就让我随身带着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.83,0:17:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我小时候经常摔倒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.44,0:17:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉怎么样  还疼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.09,0:17:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那你先回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.83,0:17:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.94,0:17:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.41,0:17:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅…舅…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.57,0:17:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.12,0:17:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.56,0:17:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.39,0:17:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所说的舅舅难道是指我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.32,0:17:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.04,0:17:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为祐理姐她…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.94,0:17:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说确实如此  但我还是初中生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.37,0:17:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫舅舅有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.37,0:17:50.65,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日语中おじちゃん也有大叔的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.75,0:17:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么小祐？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.76,0:17:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我老姐的叫法  还是算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.97,0:17:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…那么就…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.57,0:18:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.31,0:18:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.15,0:18:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前也发生过这样的事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.60,0:18:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  你还记得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.93,0:18:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小空才是还没忘啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.21,0:18:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会忘记呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.86,0:18:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.92,0:18:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…没有为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.40,0:18:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.06,0:19:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难得穿的这么漂亮  但却弄脏了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.54,0:19:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总觉得你和平时不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.40,0:19:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  到现在才发现
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.62,0:19:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好美的夕阳
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.63,0:19:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为雨过天晴了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.21,0:19:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.43,0:19:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.92,0:19:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.44,0:19:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.03,0:19:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.86,0:19:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以这么叫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.85,0:19:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫你「哥哥」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.85,0:20:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.98,0:20:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也希望你这么叫我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.45,0:20:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.82,0:20:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能找到小空真是太好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.10,0:20:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.39,0:20:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  再见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.19,0:20:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.21,0:20:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可真了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.45,0:20:41.45,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千春托儿所
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.45,0:20:41.45,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入所指南
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.22,0:20:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也得努力了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.03,0:20:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时间了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.50,0:20:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天结算工资的打工真是帮大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.14,0:20:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐古前辈  谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.22,0:20:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我站住
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.38,0:20:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.12,0:20:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快站住
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.69,0:20:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.06,0:21:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不是  所以说  这…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.41,0:21:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是因为不可抗力  是飞来横祸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.56,0:21:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灰来横祸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.99,0:21:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不是故意的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.20,0:21:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.91,0:21:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.80,0:21:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我去打工了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.03,0:21:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舅舅也该自觉些  学会体贴人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.04,0:21:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢草莓
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.88,0:21:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢草莓
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.29,0:21:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢草莓
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.15,0:21:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢草莓
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.20,0:21:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里看到的东西  不要说出去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.85,0:21:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.41,0:21:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花村糖果公司草莓大福
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.14,0:21:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说是森林中可爱的动物们做出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.74,0:21:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能破坏孩子们的梦想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.01,0:21:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.37,0:23:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是小雏哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.55,0:23:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.26,0:23:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和小舅舅  小空姐姐  美羽姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.97,0:23:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起出去玩了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.14,0:23:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…「美好的家庭旅行」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.99,0:23:36.00,EDtitle,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,529.5)\blur2\fad(906,0)}美好的家庭旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.89,0:23:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见咯
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,============OP===============
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.66,0:00:43.74,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.99,0:00:47.04,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}いつからかな  不思議
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.37,0:00:53.50,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}この胸の奥はきみの欠片ばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.00,0:00:57.28,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs35\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.59,0:01:03.93,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}どうしよハート暴走  ドキドキ  デートの想像
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.26,0:01:07.06,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}キュンて飛び跳ねちゃう鼓動
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.18,0:01:10.35,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}自然に頬っぺたポッて  染まるの隠しても
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.39,0:01:12.60,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}気がついてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.77,0:01:18.53,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}傾いてく　ココロの角度
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.57,0:01:26.99,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}想いの視線はきみ向き　もう、恋をしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.70,0:01:31.50,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:01:35.08,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}エールを贈らせて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.29,0:01:41.51,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}きみが目指す空抱く  夢を一緒に追いかけるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.84,0:01:44.84,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs39}Candy Candy Love  Candy Candy Love
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.22,0:01:48.18,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}リードはまだまだ頼りないかも  でも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.56,0:01:54.35,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}背中に寄り添うささえにね、なれたら…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.02,0:01:58.82,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}ソットソット·スキデ·イテモ·イイデスカ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.85,0:02:01.82,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs35\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.66,0:00:43.74,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.99,0:00:47.04,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}真是不可思议  不知何时起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.37,0:00:53.50,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}我的内心深处满是你的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.00,0:00:57.28,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs37\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.59,0:01:03.93,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}怎么办  忐忑不安  想象着约会的情景
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.26,0:01:07.06,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}不安的内心怦怦直跳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.18,0:01:10.35,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}就算我自然地鼓起脸颊  掩饰着这份心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.39,0:01:12.60,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}也请一定要注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.77,0:01:18.53,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}缓缓倾斜  心中的天平
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.57,0:01:26.99,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}看向你的眼神中充满爱  我已陷入了热恋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.70,0:01:31.50,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Happy Happy Girl  Happy Happy Girl
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:01:35.08,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}请让我为你加油
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.29,0:01:41.51,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}拥抱你所追寻的天空  一起去追逐梦想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.84,0:01:44.84,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}Candy Candy Love  Candy Candy Love
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.22,0:01:48.18,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}或许我现在还无法很好地指引你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.56,0:01:54.35,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}但若能成为你的后盾  支撑着你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.02,0:01:58.82,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)}可不可以·让我·悄悄地·喜欢着你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.85,0:02:01.82,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(170,200)\fs37\i1\bord4}Do you Do you trust me? Someday...please, say“Yes”
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,============ED===============
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.40,0:22:00.11,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ピカピカと光る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.53,0:22:02.24,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}僕だけのSweet Love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.53,0:22:06.37,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}かなえるかな  この愛は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.66,0:22:08.24,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}満ちてくる恋は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.62,0:22:10.50,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}何色だろうな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.79,0:22:14.67,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}すこしだけ見せようかな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.92,0:22:18.50,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}トキメキと回る小さな瞬間
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.00,0:22:22.76,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}わき起こる色がある
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.05,0:22:26.97,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}ゆらゆらと揺れる小さな世界を
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.22,0:22:31.02,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}そっと  そっと  いやしてくるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.35,0:22:35.15,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}お茶目過ぎな君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.44,0:22:39.19,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}僕の中を巡り巡るよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.23,0:22:40.94,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}くるくる回る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.98,0:22:43.32,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}踊る君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.36,0:22:44.95,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}駆け抜けていく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.99,0:22:47.16,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}はじけたソーダみたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.20,0:22:49.16,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}すてきなカラーの君は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:51.33,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}僕を感じてるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.33,0:22:53.20,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.29,0:22:55.62,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}キラキラな甘いラブ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.67,0:22:57.33,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}くるくる回る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.42,0:22:59.50,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}踊る君のカラーリング
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.75,0:23:01.38,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}舞い上がるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.42,0:23:03.51,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}柔らかなイチゴミルク
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.55,0:23:05.55,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}すてきなカラーの君は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.59,0:23:07.68,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}何を描いてるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.80,0:23:09.68,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.72,0:23:11.93,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}キラキラな甘いラブ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.40,0:22:00.11,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}闪闪发亮
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.53,0:22:02.24,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}只属于我的甜美爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.53,0:22:06.37,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}这份爱能否实现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.66,0:22:08.24,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}渐渐满溢的爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.62,0:22:10.50,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}究竟是什么颜色呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.79,0:22:14.67,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}稍微让你看一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.92,0:22:18.50,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}回荡的微小瞬间使我的心悸动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.00,0:22:22.76,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}浮现出了斑斓色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.05,0:22:26.97,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}将来回摇摆的渺小世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.22,0:22:31.02,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}静静地  静静地  治愈
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.35,0:22:35.15,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你的色彩实在太过淘气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.44,0:22:39.19,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}在我的心中往往复复
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.23,0:22:40.94,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}咕噜咕噜地旋转
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.98,0:22:43.32,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你的色彩开始起舞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.36,0:22:44.95,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}一路飞奔而过
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.99,0:22:47.16,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}如同喷发的汽水一般
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.20,0:22:49.16,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}色彩缤纷的你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:51.33,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}是否能感受到我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.33,0:22:53.20,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.29,0:22:55.62,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}甜蜜的爱情正闪闪发光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.67,0:22:57.33,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}咕噜咕噜地旋转
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.42,0:22:59.50,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}你的色彩开始起舞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.75,0:23:01.38,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}能否随风起舞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.42,0:23:03.51,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}这柔软的草莓牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.55,0:23:05.55,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}色彩缤纷的你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.59,0:23:07.68,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}正在描绘着什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.80,0:23:09.68,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}Staying in your love
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.76,0:23:11.93,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,100)}甜蜜的爱情正闪闪发光
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.10,0:00:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
