This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
Do you know there are rules when flying ?
Where every you go in the world, there must be a "high way"
In aviation, we call them airways, analogous to highways in lamen terms
All aircraft in japan fly from and to this predefined route- airways to ensure safety
TO maintain proper separation during takeoff, landing and enroute,
Air traffic controllers are there to instruct pilots on hdg, speed and alt to ensure safety.
for example a plane flying from fukoka to haneda
First the pilot contacts the atc and the aerodrome controller give clerance from ground movements to airborne
From aerdrome control, the a/c is pass to terminal control
then from terminal control is passed to the 4 major Area Control Centre
ACC uses radar facility to track the flight and guide them to their destination
The green is Fukoka Control and blue is Tokyo control area
The plane flies with the predefined route and contact fukuoka control then tokyo control
The plane is then transfer to the terminal control of haneda for landing
The ATC uses radar to maitain separation is called Air Traffic Control
In the world, Air traffic Control has a variety of complex rules and system
Because of These sets of rules and Air traffic controllers strive to separate traffic made flying in the air safe
EP10- FINAL EPISODE
how about diverting to handea ?
ITs better to make the deicision
Outan san, Japan central is..
Going to narita.
What is it doing ?
it make take something, but surely it will not crash
Do you mean that there should be a cause all behind this?
We have a report from RJSS, there is a unidentified a/c following the traffic
but we still do not know what is it .
Would that be related to the incident before ?
I wonder..
It is uncommon to have an unidentified a/c following one another.
The a/c is sticking to the rear-end of the preceding traffic
What if they are in the same altitute?
That would be the worse case
Well, it seems that this hi-jack incident is highly correlated with the system down incident before.
Don't let others know, it is the research of takahashi.
It is the report of investigation report about the system down
ok I shall confirm it.
How many aircrafts are flying at this time.
According to the data, it is 550 at this time.
You are going to land all the aircraft ?
There is not departures, so just landing them would not be a problem.
That's great, I am relieved.
You should not say that
what happened ?
Its better that he have something to do.
can you investigate the intention  of the hi-jack ?
sure.
Yama kun, its finally like working.
I wonder if he is fine.
What happened ?
The 3 aircraft that lost communications have been returning back on course
Don't you think its strange ?
do you mean that there was no hi-jack ?
no..
There is still not radio contact with the aircraft
Do you know more about it ?
no.. I wonder if there are some reasons behind it.
What happen ?
Yuki's daughter is in one of the hi-jacked flights
Are you sure about that ?
Yes.
He told me not to tell anyone.
Don't worry
He know that he can't just sit there and do nothing.
Its better not to tell the others yet.
Don't take it too hard
If I think its too much, i won't return here
Right.
If its about the airpace use, ATM will tell us, but we have to know the remaining fuel of the aircraft
What is it now ?
We still need time to deal with it
Do you have any skills to deal with it ?
Yes up to now.
Where is our chief ?
I ask him to contact the aviation board
I am worried even though its seems to be an easy job.
Let me take a look on him.
Yuki, oh no..
Atlantis is descending and seems to be apporach kansai airport final approach course
really ?
They wanted to crash land on an airport ?
They seemed to have planned it.
The aircraft have came to narita
For those aircraft bound for haneda, vector them off to the south
But you see they are already lined up
All station, heading for tokyo international airport,
tokyo control
runway closed
due to emergency situation
JAL108  fly heading 180 standby further clerance
Where did the a/c try to enter ?
It seems after japan center air
IF there is not enough fuel then use narita
Newjet 210, fly heading 190, standby further clerance
I will let all a/c vector to near oshima (XAC) and divert them to chuubu
yes
Jetair809, fly heading 190, standby further clerance
Expect radar vector to chuubu airport
it will be very dangerous as a lot of a/c are approach haneda and narita area
Please invesitage of japan centra air
PLease  alos instruct a/c if needed
What kind of help would you like me to do ?
Uweki san
Please help yama san.
yes
Kinoshita.
Please give up Kansai airport and land in itami
There are too much a/c in centraair
understood.
For a/c in kanto east , please contact shikijima for coordination
For those who have more fuel, divert them to chitose
understood.
We have confirmed with the pilots of rainbow airlines that rondo is the password for hi-jack
thank you
Can you write down the landing distance between different airports ?
So do you mean that narita and haneda cannot be used for landing ?
Yes.
maki,
Aeromexica is coming from the south,
We will handle it and update you with latest information
TOkyo control air america 197, we declare emergency due to low fuel.
we copy your situation, recleared direct to yokota.
Would they give permission ?
We don't have other choice.
Where could we land then ?
Its better choice to spare time.
Please change seat with me.
I will calculate the maximum capcity and landing distance of centraair airport
Uweki san please help these two pilots.
and report in respective regions
understood
Hello this is tokyo control, we have an emergency  civil aircraft,  his callsign is Airamerica 197
position is 40 miles  east of  yokota airbase
can you accept  his landing ? we need your help and cooperation.
ok, we  understand your situation
approved as you request.
roger, heading 260 vector to final, thank you very much for your cooperation.
Airamerica 197,
turn right heading 260 for vector to final approach course
and contact yokota approach.
good day
Please concentrate on other aircraft
so this is the truth ?
I should have know this earlier
I have just coorindate with Centraair
They said we have to maintain at least 2-3 mins separation between the aircrafts
The airport is now crowded due to the emergency aircraft
understood
at this rate, the aircraft will just run out of fuel by holding in the air
Yama san is now calculating the about the fuel and best landing aerodrome, standby
Yes.
What should we do ?
We just stick to our sector.
let's make them hold on enroute
Yes.
I don't enough man power,here
Here, is the best aerodrome for  aircraft to divert in your sector
Thank you very much
Let's be calm and face it.
It should be fine.
Tomo cyan,  I will be dealing with traffic to fukuoka
Captainair 610, request further clerance
Air united 039,  request priority due to minimum fuel
new jet 592,  request fuel damping due to heavy weight
All station standby
Which one has priority ?
I will ask the remaining fuel in time and determine their sequence
If there is emergency then that would go first
I understood
Captainair 610, recleared XAC and hold
inbound track 095, 1 and half min leg,  right turn, maintain 10000ft
Air united 039, request fuel remaining in time.
about 40 mins
newjet 592, request fuel remaining in time.
about 50 mins
I will give priority to air united
Yuki, it seems that its not going to centraair
how about other regions ?
It s getting busy, I will give you updates later.
Are you fine
let me help
Can you help coordinate a/c diverting to fukuoka?
I have read the data,
Let's discuss it when others are gone.
fly heading 270 for vector to niigata airport
d/m 10000ft
Can you give me precise figures of 747 and A330's remainting fuel in time ?
There is many traffic heading to centraair, its better to use other airport
Its better tohave runway length more than 2500ft
Orion 124, d/m 13000ft
Maki, these are the list of aerodrome that an a/c can divert
Yamada, give traffic information
Royalstar 697, traffic 2 oclock, 10 miles, crossing right to left ,
ROger maintain FL 370
This is narita airport
There is an official annoucement of ceasing civil aviation operation in japan
it may be a terrorist attack but we are not sure.
We are almost there, stay awake
Yuki, how was it ?
They are trying their very best.
What was it ?
The ATM said they did not send scamble a/c and its none of their business.
Look at here, it must be a military aircraft
Who are you calling ?
wait.
I will do the negotiation later.
No more waiting
if we know the cause we should report it.
I just said wait
They are the one controlling the japanese airspace
it is not a normal people can handle this.
We still do not know whether there is someone behind this is the criminal
it is not related to our job nature as an Air traffic controller
We have just done the best we can do as an ATC
Do you understand what does it mean when there is military aircraft flying in our airspace ?
They may crash on civil aircraft//
I won't let that happen.
Aren't out job is to ensure ALL aircrafts land at their destination safely ?
maki.. Calm down.
Should we just wait for a bet for it ?
The manger has his own stands also.
Please be considerate.
The a/c that lost radio communication can fly 30 mins at maximum
Thank you
I wonder if we can possible listen to the frequecy between the military a/c and the civil pilot ?
Even we know the frequency, it make take a long time.
We have that specialist in here, you know..
J-sky 456,  contact shizuoka radio good day
maki san. Is there any response from atlantis
yes.
There is no new information from kansai airport
It may take some time..
their fuel should reach its limit
Esepcially Japan air central should have not much fuel  left as it just returned from america.
10 more aircrafts left
here.
Its better to go down here
we should make the decision now or else we are screwed up
I will help youo to make the deicision
Open it
go to the airport
don't do unnecessary things
We as pilots have our own stands and point of view in flight safety
What happened
They are using a special equipment
They are using 10 channels at any given time.
10 ?
can you serach for it ?
Although we search for it, they would change it again ( the system)
And it would not be an easy job
Please search it.
Yes.
Here is sendai, we have the traffic lost of commnuication still with us, but will they run out of fuel ?
Its already more than 1 hour 30mins than their scheduled landing time.
I will confirm with their airline
Yuki san.
Kansai airport said they have radio communication with Atlantis airlines
Yuki kun
Tokyo control atlantis 808 request approach clerance to kansai airport
atlantis 808 ,contact kansai approach 120.25 for your request
What happened ?
They just contacted us in a sudden
Can you try to ask if anyone is hurt
Atlantis 808 , did you encounter and trouble or problems in flight ?
no.
How would you say no..
You have been lost communication for more than 2 hours and now diverting to kansai ...
The military aircraft is leaving the aircraft
Takahashi, did you found any transmission between the aircraft ?
no.
Yuki san,
We have radio communication with rainbow
They are heading to haneda.
Why do these traffic just contact as they were like in noraml flight ?
now , its left to Japan air central,
Its quite dangerous.
The military a/c has no repsonse to our callings
Now, former manager and the chief is now dealing with this problem.
Yuki, we have received information that the a/c from anchroage has diverted to New chitose and landed
understood, please follow up east sector
Was there emergency ?
No, not yet
How long can Japn centra air can fly ?
aoubt 20 mins
what is the altitutde now ?
20000ft
wait.
I can't get the precise information but.
58 miles left for flying
66 miles in total
We have radio communucation between atlantis and rainbow.
how was it with you ?
It is the information from ATM
The minister of the transport department has been arrested
Japan centra 776, this is tokyo contro, radio check, how do you read ?
reading 5
We just have radio communication with Japanair central
japancentra 776, fly heading 250 for vector to shizuoka airport
do you declare emergency
we declare emergency due to low fuel.
the succeding a/c has just left
how much fuel in time left ?
about 5mins
japan central 776,  cleared ils z rwy 30 approach, contact shizuoka radio
they have just entered the control zone of shizuoka
Sorry, due to strong winds we decided to go around.
There a lot of wind in that area
Another go around eh..
If they go around again, they don't have much fuel.
Japn central 776,  Let's do it without sweat.
The wind are becoming left strong, it should be fine this time.
JCL776, cleared for ILS Z rwy30 approach
we are in landing position
we have landed
TOkyo control, thank you
That must be very tired
It great that there was no accident.
do you want something to drink
I will bring it to you
no need
thanks.cheers for hardwork
I am fortunate to work with you again in tokyo control
cheers for hardwork
hello
did you called ?
you  are so late.
sorry, there is a lot of procedures after landing.
did you get injured ?
ofcourse not, we landed as usual.
but before we landed its was surprising.
what happening ?
i think they made some mistakes.
are you o k?
i am fine ,it is like a roller coaster on an aeroplane, that was fun
really ?
dad, you are wathcing us on the sky,
so I have nothing to fear.
because i know you must be looking after me, I am not afraid.
really.
I decided to be an air traffic controller.
what ever, ride the shikansen and come home soon, see you.
cheers for hardwork
I am sorry for the ..
Thank you very much for your cooperation today.
CAn you return to the control room, when you are ready
you are really charming person
Well, people always say i am ok ..
I must be the wrong cup of tea for you, right ?
how did you know ?
Joking.. that is cuel.
Its better I said nothing.
I am waiting at this direction
direction ?
We are pilots that fly in the sky which may the sky crowded
The burden for ATC would be increasing
yea
Because of us , who protect the airspace, it makes the sky safe to be flown
no matter how difficult the situation ,
We have to support and cope with it, because those dots in the screen are hundreds of life on it.
I finally understnad how horrible is it when you just sit infront of the screen and giving instruction
We ATC and pilot have a unseeable bond , that includes the trusts
See you.
thank you.
suzuki san,
Shall we meet again
Although we may not see agian, but I can hear you through the commnucations
see you.
No problem see you by then!
There are 3 officers has been arrested for hi-jack acitivty planning in japan
Its really great that we have just landed 550 aircrafts on the ground
We work as a team ,right ?
It does not matter whoever is the criminal
more important we have ensure air safety of the sky
What is better than have peace in the sky ?
right.
why did you not trust on your team mates ?
he did this even he know he will be fired.
Let's go to narita.
I have nothing to say to you.
Its nothing to do with our experience
Its just right in front of us
You can't change the fact that we are going to fired anyway.
???
PLease be calm and listen to me.
Its is our mission to ensure air safety of the citizen
We just shoot them down for the sake of the citizen in japan
I have received the conversation until here
Takahashi,
I know
I will delete all the data that I have recorded
I shall give this to you.
shimuro,
its better for me to hold this
don't get fired
this is the reaosn for  all the mysterious events that have occured
This is the reason behind those missle from russia, scrambble and etc..
There is a scambble departred from hyakuri airbase
And  they are the one who hacked on our database
They have hacked successfuly but they failed to hide their identity
that is really a troublesome
but ans an ATC, you guys really did a great job in ensuring air safety in japan
I finally unsterdand its due to these guys.
I don't understand what did the bouei daijin minter said
shimuro
I wonder if I can do something with these evidence?
I am not sure
but I will try my best to solve it.
Yuki, its better that you put your hands off this case
How could i do that...
I heard from tanabe san
You still have things you can do with your hands
Its my job and my fault to let you be troubled in this case
I did not think that the hacking incident would lead to such large scale of diasater
so, please forget about the incident
if i can help, please let me know.
thank you.
cheers for hardwork.
Due to the incident, the airspace will be closed for 3 days at least
so its going to be quite for somewhile
its great to be quite sometime..
So that means there will not be stress within these 3 days
since everyone is here, I would like to annouce my resignation after the day after tomorrow
I will change position to ATM
I have been looking at the airspace of japan for 7 years
Its my first time to feel that i have to protect this airspace
But, human will commit mistakes
we are not perfect
because of that I want to change it.
nowadays, according to the technology we have, when there is an error made by an ATC
the air traffic controller will take full responsibility on the incident
To change this policy, i have to change from the inside, that means I will go to ATM
is that already to leave the front line ?
I like to working in the front line
but, if i want to change the policy , I must go to the headquarters
I hope you understand the reason why I have to leave here
even I am not here, the operation here will not change
you guys have did a great job today, with your own hands and the help of team work
I am proud of you guys that you have build such a strong bondings between friends to ensure air safety
I may come back here again
and hope to see that all of you have grown up to be a great controller
Everyone, do you best!
Hara
How would the base ball become?
ofcourse we will still continue, though you did not even show up in the competitions.
To celebrate the leaving of Yuki controll,er we would like to give him a lift
wait.. I did not do anything..
man is really great...
I just see that they are very silly
Maki, let's go..
Afterall,
what about ?
You are trying to be cool ?
Really, I think so also.
no one would think like that.
naru sis ?
my daughter was on the last aircraft who landed safely
She said that it was interesting , as its like jet roller coaster
When that a/c was in emergency state, i really cared for her very much
When her mother passed away, she said that I am an annoying person.
when she learnt to make her own lunch set during her graduation.
was my greatest joy to see her smile in the entrance at the door
Really?
I have a thought at the very moment,
that I must protect her
but, I did not make time for her
I am the worse dad
if i change to work in ATM it would be more busier than before
because its near to my home
I hope to have dinner with her
and this is one of the reason why I have to move to Fukuoka to work
Maki, I shall leave this place
no. but...
I will be counting on you.
Please come back again
if i have changed the world , I will.
cheers for hardwork
I do not like to praise
but.. you did a great controlling today
shall we have dinner together ?
with you ?
are you afraid ?
yes, sure, why not.
joking.
but you just said my controlling was good.
If was not perfect though
Yes..
should i call kinoshita ?
forget about him.
(after one year)
did you know that shikijima have open a new caffee .
haven't you drunk his coffee
my first time to hear about that
here
thank you.
delicious
do you want some ?
its ok
why not,
I have drank a lot
The new magazine have delivered
Yama, can you stop it.
aren't you doing it...
why is your credits getting smaller ?
shall we do it ?
I am going do to the enterprise game..
wata san...
I shall start cleaning up
ya... its first time to date with Maki ?
If i am going to work hard, maki san said she will have dinner with me..
that is great.
I understand
What is it about him? people change when they fall in love.
we should give a name..
this is its a girl
how about ueno.
ueno shimuya..
how come its a surname ?
This time, it is not simulation, it is real traffic with real people on it
are you nervous ?
Let's return back to the simulation then.
I am fine
I am joking, relax..
hi yamada.
are you ready?
this is hata tsubasaku , the new trainee
Please let him know which locker he can use.
and bring him to the control room
OJT is by maki.
hey, say something.
pleased to meet you
What ever question you have, please ask Yamada senior
Let's go.
Can I use this locker ?
no, not this, use that
its not quite good over there
you are really self-indulgence
not this one.
if you don't hurry up maki will scould you
if you are scoulded by her, you hair will turn white
Yamada kun  seems to be coming great
no, i am just being harsh with the new trainee
will you come to my place tonight ?
My daughter would like to see you
Can i come ?
ofcourse, why are you talking like that ?
Outa san, what if I get marry with hara chan ?
You don't have to come anymore
I am sorry,
I am just kidding
Please don't take it serious
I am ready
Let's go
Excuse me, i have a monitor training today
Maki, the new trainnee is here for OJT
Today, lets do kanto east sector