This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
do you know where will the planes go after they wear out ?
Do you know there are rules when flying ?
Where every you go in the world, there must be a "high way"
In aviation, we call them airways, analogous to highways in lamen terms
All aircraft in japan fly from and to this predefined route- airways to ensure safety
TO maintain proper separation during takeoff, landing and enroute,
Air traffic controllers are there to instruct pilots on hdg, speed and alt to ensure safety.
for example a plane flying from fukoka to haneda
First the pilot contacts the atc and the aerodrome controller give clerance from ground movements to airborne
From aerdrome control, the a/c is pass to terminal control
then from terminal control is passed to the 4 major Area Control Centre
ACC uses radar facility to track the flight and guide them to their destination
The green is Fukoka Control and blue is Tokyo control area
The plane flies with the predefined route and contact fukuoka control then tokyo control
The plane is then transfer to the terminal control of haneda for landing
The ATC uses radar to maitain separation is called Air Traffic Control
In the world, Air traffic Control has a variety of complex rules and system
Because of These sets of rules and Air traffic controllers strive to separate traffic made flying in the air safe
Have you heard of the communication between ATC and pilot ?
Air traffic communication is used between pilots and ATC to ensure air safety
Actually , there is a place where you can hear the communication between the ATC and the pilot
It is the first airliners - united , that allow passengers to listen the communication in flight
United, as a well known big airliner company, the "from the flight deck" is one of the in flight service
Have you thought about what instruction was given to the a/c while you are in-flight ?
Takakucyan . Where is dad ?
ok, shall we dine out ?
Ok, let's meet at seven tonight.
Don't worry, see you.
Your daughter ?
No..
Are you married ?
I thought you said you hate men ...
That is why I am not yet married
Enough..
It's the daughter of Yuki, we eat often when yuki is busy
It's not what you think.
I'm returing..
Saito san,
How to make a women fall in love with a men ?
I don't know.
Do you know what type of people does Maki like ?
She said she like boys that will work extra time.
For those men like you, is definitely a no.
She likes men who work extra time ... ?
The amount of aircraft are increasly every year
Kabuto san.
Do you know the capacity of runway use in Haneda airport ?
The capcity / usage has increased from 30 millions 40.9 millions
As you have seen,when the number increases,
The air traffic management will get more complex to ensure air safety
It is obvious that the workload for ATC have also increased
Human error are prone to occur when stress and workload increases
Yamada kun, you seems not study enough.
Yokumini kun, can you explain a bit
Yes.
Human has a limited concentration capcity,
Regardless the personality, with prolong time in controlling, human are prone to make error
Yes.
So, as he said, we humans will commit human errors in Air traffic controlling
We cannot make error to be zero %
We , Air traffic control are as important as as medical care service
The boards are planning to upgrade radar systems to help reduce human error
We must must forward to embrace the furture needs
Therefore, we have to be aware of human error and reduce it to minimum.
Ep07
Cheers for hardwork..
Are you alright ?
Can I ask something ?
Maki, have you expeirence human error before ?
If you have, I was thinking if you could share me your experience and ways to deal with it..
I do not have
but look at your textbook, its a good reference .
Understood.
How was the seminar ?
Tired.
Yes..
But , it is still important to seminar to arouse their awareness of human error
It may occur when stress arise,
It really great to have an experienced instructor like you.
not really..
Yes.
Do you want lunch ?
Are you busy in that sector ?
Its fine.
I am looking afterhim very harshly.
Don't always play around, I will be looking at you very closely
Why is she so bossy ?
She is our boss..
Because Yuki, is not here, she gain power and always scold people.
Its about the responsibility..
If you are working like that, you deserved to be scoulded
maki,
Yokohama san said it was a pity you did not came to his cafe shop open celebration
I had something to do, how was the shop then.
He really enjoyed..
Shikijima coffee
Finally he used his name as the coffe shop..
Nice Scent
Maki, if you have time, can you ask Yamada to get the lunch orders ?
Yes.
There is a change in staffing next week.
Yes, i know.
For you..
Excuse,  Do you want lunch ?
ANA232 heading 250 is approved.
Karui bento please
Please make that 2, thanks
I want curry rice, extra large.. with egg and extra large..
Should I stop maki ?
Excuse me, do you want Lunchbox ?
2 Wafu curry please
Please tell others that you will be making the order now.
Everyone, I will be making the order now
Your voice is a little too loud.
Please use my phone here
Hello,  I want to order meals.
Its not emergency call
its about ordering meals
I am very sorry..
This is Tokyo Control Area Center
We have made a mistake
I am sorry
I would make sure next time we would not make the same mistake.
Yamada Kun...
What do you have to do that ?
This is the direct line to the rescure team  (RCC)
Maki ...
It is not time to laugh...
This will not happen if Maki did tell Yamada about these
I told him but he forgot.
I did not know it is a direct line to RCC.
You should know by looking it at first site.
It is written RCC on the phone handle.
cool, human error has occured.
Hara, is that really delicious ?
ofcourse, its delicious.
Do you want some ?
That is very expensive, becareful.
Do you know that by eating this, you got a chance to wind the luck draw
There is a silly boy here.
what .. ?
You know, I was abducted by aliens..
I am just trying to save the world.
Its definetly there is a silly man here.
What is the good smelling coffee ?
Oh, you have noticed ?
It is a gift from the shikijima coffee 's open celebration
I got a discount 100 yen for 150 g
That is because it was an opening celebration.
It is the best scent ever..
Can I have a cup of that later ?
Sure.
You can have this .
Did you lick it with your tongue ?
no ofcourse not.
eww , that is disgusting..
maki san, wait for a while, yours is coming up.
Thank you .
That is delicious.
I really want to go to the outter space.
Its great if he could go to the space.
Cheers for hardwork.
Did you heard anything from Yuki ?
Its seems to be difficult, as tokyo control is being hack
and the hacker is still not been found .
I felt quite tough, and the responsbility is building up while yuki is not here.
Don't worry so much,
I know.
I remembered when I was too harsh, its not the best to others.
If you don't have something you hate, the workplace would be boring, right ?
right, its no use to think permissiticly
I shall work hard tomorrow
See you
Good morning.
Saito san.
ex-manager is looking for you
What is it ?
Please sit
ok.
I am sorry to call you off before work.
i would like to discuss with you about your leading.
ANA188, turn right heading 110 for spacing.
JAL426, d/m FL 250, deviation heading 060 is approved, report accept right turn.
JAL18, request descent.
JAL18, d/m Fl230
Its good to give a command quickly, but becareful the separation are getting closer there.
Yes.
The deviation have started.
It should be break time for time, let  me take over.
After Yamada finish his OJT, can you be here, I will be on a meeting with ATM.
There is bad weather near Hachijyojima.
There would be a lot of affect to the routes over that area.
Let's change shift.
Yamada kun, Let rest.
There are holding a/c bound for Narita.
So lets go to MJE.
Malasian 554, hold south of MJE, maintain FL 210
The visibility in Narita have reduced due to rain and bad weather
Let's think of a way to better ensure the flow of the traffic
Fly heading 240
2 o'clock 10 miles,
Due to traffic.
Maintain 20 miles due to comprising traffic
Standby request we will call you soon
The pilot request this heading, it that fine, there is a cloud here.
J-sky 657, deviation heading 070 is approved, report clear of weather
Lets change.
Are you ok ?
J-sky657 is on deivation heading 070
After that you can do level change
Due to bad weather in Narita
There are already 3 aircrafts holding in MJE
ANA237 turn right heading 310
Princess air 56, tokyo control roger break break;
JAL010, contact tokyo control 133.6
Ok, I shall come back within 10 minutes
I am on break time.
This is Tokyo Control Headquaters
Everyone, give me your attention.
There is a trans a/c reporting microburst in Narita, all runways are closed.
Please inform a/c if divert is required as holding a/c increasing.
Skyward airlines 353, fly heading 350 for vector to kansai airport
Airmacau 655, standby
Is it ok to hold a/c in the south ?
Everone are diverting to this direction
Shikijima, can you stop putting a/c to me ?
There are enroute holding and not enough space here, can't you ask a/c to land in sendai, or chitose ?
All pilots requested to land in Kansai.
I have tried to say haneda but I will try again.
JAL25, hold southeast of MJE, d/m FL 160
This is not good.
Oriental343, emergency descent.
I would like to divert to chuubu ( RJGG)
At this time ?
All station, tokyo control, Emergency Descent in progress 10 miles south of milan b B777
FL280 , East Bound.
This is getting complicated.
It is quite tough here.
Let's get help from the ex-manager.
This is Tokyo control area center
There are many aircraft divert away from Narita.
Please contact Centrair for the divert.
Yes.
Centraair, this is tokyo control.
Oreital air343, emergency descent , declared time at 1140z
Requesting to divert to your airport
Its dangerous, please vector and handoff to my sector
Thank you
Yes
Do you need help ?
No, I am fine.
Understood.
united 85 c/m FL270
Shimusan, They cannot accept the emergency flight.
Kansai have reached their capacity, can we divert to other place ?
The Departure a/c are too much
I will do my best here
ANA223, Tokyo control, roger c/m FL280
ANA667, how do you read ?
ANA667, c/m FL 280
Kabu cyan please contact Centraair
They said its ok to accept the emergency a/c
Tokyo control, JAL113, request heading 240
JAL113, standby
Oreintal343, contact Centraair approach 119.17.
Airchina 23, request FL360
Are you ok ?
Airchina 23, standby
JAL113, turn left heading 240
understood
We have put on limits to departing traffic
We have to reduce the traffic flow as the diverting a/c approaches
TOkyo control area
Trans u air,  air america,atlantic airline, are going to be diverting to kansai airport.
oreitenal 343 has lost radio contact
Really ?
I will change shift then,
Oriental 343, has landed safely in chuubu
Understood
United 776, turn left heading 110,  d/m FL270
J-sky..
J-sky657, confirm heading 070
J sky657 we have accidently set heading 090, now turning to 070.
I am sorry I was concentrating on oriental343 and did not noticed this a/c
Are you ok ?
I have said heading 070 but..
That was dangerous.
Cheers for hardwork.
I am very sorry for what happened.
Good thing nothing occured, right ?
Its tiring when there is a lot of traffic
Maki,..
Actually, I will be changing positions
Really ?
I have sent a request of change position one year ago..
And I was accepted just now at the critical point.
Where ?
Fukuoka .
Really.
But if Saito san is leaving..
Its fine, Yuki, will be returning by next week.
But I will be lonely.
really ?
Yes.
You really look tired.
Shall we drink some coffee ?
but I can't make coffee as declious as shikijima kun.
Thank you.
ANA223,c/mFL280.
Anything ?
I am very sorry just while ago.
There was nothing happened, you don't have to apologise.
Americal 288, d/m  FL 250 devation heading 080 is approved.
Southair 18, turn right heading 110 for spacing.
ANL167, declare emergency
I'll explain in japanese.
We have touble in instruments, the numbers  of our fuel are decreasing..
we are not sure if we have enough fuel, we will confirm with our CA
We may need to divert.
AsianX167, understood.
Where would you like to divert ?
Please wait.
Please take care here
d/m FL160
Please contact Hachijyojima airport
ANL167 have faulty instruments request divert.
The nearest airport is hachijyojima..
There is strong wind over there
If the instruments are faulty, it would be difficult to land there.
ANL167, is there big hospital in hachijyojima ?
What happened ?
There is a 3 year old child in coma,
There is no medical personnel on board.
CA have been doing emergency treatment
It is possible to divert to hachijyojima, they said they can turn on the approach light.
There is a hospital in hachijojima..
If there are faulty instruments, there should be neither enough fuel too.
Considering there is a child, I think it better to land in haneda.
ALso, weather is too bad for a pilot to land with faulty instrument, try to ask the pilot's intention.
but, the pilot may not have enough fuel.
if I just ask the pilot
I think that suggesting the pilot to land in hachijyojima is a better choice.
ANL167, we would like to take hachijyojima instead
understood, please parpare for the emergency procedures.
ANL167, There is a hospital , please keep the patient as long as you could.
Understood.
There is a child on board, this must be tough.
ANL167, fly heading 070 for vector to final approach course.
expect localiser Z runway 26 approach
Standby Direct sago.
ANL167, roger.
We are on landing positing and we can see the approach light
roger
Please contact hachijyojima radio
pacific 780, d/m FL 270
Speed 290 for arrival spacing.
Hawaian 838, reduce speed to 270 knots.
standby approach clerance, we have departure traffic.
JAL178, tokyo control, c/m FL 260, turn right heading 290.
This is Kantou South Sector.
The call is from hachijyojima radio.
Yes.
ANL167 have landed safely, but
the hospital reported that child is still in coma.
Thanks for coming , can you change shifts with Maki ?
Yes.
There is an a/c did not get contact it should be arriving within 30 mins.
Maki, let's change.
maki san.
please.
Kabutan Cyan also.
I wonder if the child is fine.
I am hungry
Cheers for hardwork.
You have a tough day..
No, I don't think so.
I can see you are tired.
ok, let's go for a drink this time.
There are many handsome guy watching.
let's go.
Please knock at least.
Sorry.
Maki san.
I am not trying to invite you today.
I am the busy men that will work late
why did he came here for ?
I do not know.
Cheers for hardwork.
Are you tired ?
no.
Cheers for hardwork.
Can I turn on the television ?
ofcourse,
that rare , what do you want to watch ?
yesterday, a flight from taipei to narita, landed in hachijyojima. The 8 year old child is still in coma,
The medical helicopter has departed from haneda to hachijyojima..
Aiya..
I was finding this for a long time.
Sorry.
This is the one.
Maki, Go home and rest
I know you since i came working in tokyo control , right ?
yes.
its great to chat with you.
I think i won't have chance to walk pass this corridor again.
Its really lonely afterall.
I am very sorry for what have happened today.
Its more important how things finally worked out rather than the result.
Saito san.
Its about the news I just watched, I a bit worried.
I can't say its directly realated to air traffic controlling.
yes..
Wata san said to let the a/c to go to haneda instead
There is not right or wrong in terms of emergency situation.
As an air traffic controller, you did not do anything wrong at the point.
Yes,but
I understand , because it realted to the people's lives
When we have been working as an ATC for a long time, its seems safety is for granted.
We just forgot how dangerous if we are not been heard.
We have to deal with the pressure everyday.
I think you have done your best.
I couldn't say don't worry about the child,
I think its important for you.
I tihnk you are capable to be a great ATC as you have take every lives on board that serious.
Don't blame yourself, you have done your best.
I  respect you and admire you a lot.
You have been very professional in your position as an ATC
Thank you.
I also respect you.
That must be a lie.
I did not say anything yet..
I think thats not true.
Can you hang around with me
shall we have meal together ?
Yes
I would like to drink something.
The weather is also great.
Let's go.