This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
What is wrong.
Do you know there are rules when flying ?
Where every you go in the world, there must be a "high way"
In aviation, we call them airways, analogous to highways in lamen terms
All aircraft in japan fly from and to this predefined route- airways to ensure safety
TO maintain proper separation during takeoff, landing and enroute,
Air traffic controllers are there to instruct pilots on hdg, speed and alt to ensure safety.
for example a plane flying from fukoka to haneda
First the pilot contacts the atc and the aerodrome controller give clerance from ground movements to airborne
From aerdrome control, the a/c is pass to terminal control
then from terminal control is passed to the 4 major Area Control Centre
The ACC are radar facilities that track the flight from the flight plan route and guide them to their destination
Green is fukuoka area, and blue is tokyo control area
The plane flies with the predefined route and contact fukuoka control then tokyo control
After entering to tokyo control and sequenced by ATC,
The plane is then transfer to the terminal control of haneda for landing
Air traffic controller utilised radar to communicate and instruct pilots  is called Air Traffic Controlling.
In the world, Air traffic Control has a variety of complex rules and system
Because of These sets of rules and Air traffic controllers strive to separate traffic made flying in the air safe
Do you what is Estimated Time Arrival(ETA) separation technique ?
In peak hours, the airplanes are just separated 2 mins
If there is congestion in an airport
The approach and landing sequence becomes very important
It is dangerous to allow traffic to approach the airport at the same time
thus, the ATC have the priviledge to vector the a/c away to provide spacing
ATC, are the one who can change the route of an aircraft
Because of their active controlling makes the sky safe to be flown.
Maki san
Where will you be going the next holiday ?
I won't go
Don't say that, Its time to relax some time
Let's go to Shibuya
I hate to go to crowed places
Do you have time next week ?
Next's week Sunday ?
We shall have a great catcher this time
it would be yamada
Let's play that game
Let's play the real one with 120km
I can't catch a ball as far as 120km !?
I played when I was in high school
I catch with my heart
hahah...(oh on..)
I am going to coveinet store, do you need anything ?
No thanks.
Aren't you going to eat ?
I am on diet
That is not good
No, because I had bbq with friends yesterday
You have friends ?
That's an insult!
ok, I am going to the store
I lose
It seems you can still take a move
After a few steps I am dead
Really
You are always that strong
No, I am not.
He is always good response to deviation request from aircraft
What have you been saying about that separation method ?
First is to imagine the airways
flights are like a chess moving on a chessboard
if you want the traffic to fly straight, use "car"-in chess
If you want to vector the traffic to the left use " angle" in chess
If you need speartion use this
You may also need to juggle with speed and alttitude
When you need to maintain a vertical spacing..
please stop, I am quite confused
You can say,  turn right heading 090 for spacing
But, you may not follow my ideas, its my way of controlling
Becareful...
This board is very expensive
How much is that ?
33,000 Yen
Really ?
Its like your wage for 3 years
3 years ?
This board is subjected to distortion when contact with heat, liquid and mostiure.
Yamada, shall you play for a game ?
No, I think I will screw things up
Just think its another ATC training.
I'm back
Maki san,
I brought you something
Thanks, but I did not ask for
Today outa san is off duty ? I did not see him for 4 days
Outa san is attending her daughter's wedding cermony
Wedding ?
I wish I could aslo
You ? you should be doing it soon
No, I don't think so
You have a lot Boyfriends, right ?
You took photos with them right?
They are not my boyfriends
You see, the cute lady is confessing.
Becuase of women like you can fake men like us
Don't blame me for the lost of your girl friend
Usually you won't take photos with boys like this close, right ?
That is very confusing for outsiders
I would do so, its normal.
You did not took it with me
I don't like people who wears glasses
Hey, Yamada, and you take off your glasses
Would you like me now ?
Maki san , what are you reading ?
It is the flight plan of the govemernt flight this afternoon
today ?
Shikijima
What is it ?
I won't finish work until one
No, its not about that
I have something to tell you.
I would be retirng soon,
I was thinking to open a cafe after my retirement
Really, cool
There is 40 years of experience
I need someone that is capable to help me.
But it would be difficult to find
Yes, its really difficult
I was thinking is it a good idea to open a cafe
You are opening a cafe ?
I like the sets of cups and drinking coffee so.
I think i shall do it as a hobby of mine
That is very enjoyable life
Yokoyama san, that is not a good idea
You are competing with our coffee maker here , right ?
Don't say that
He, shikijima, is our best coffee worker here
but, its true, his coffee is the best in tokyo
Really,
I think so also
The colour is also very special.
The blend is great
No.
Yamada , don't add your opinion here !
Sorry
I think it is good
shikijma..
I want to help.
Please let me help
I was thinking recently, that working as a coffee is my another occupation aside ATC
If I go to the TV, i should be famous.
Is he narcassism ?
Its like message from the heaven, when its about coffee
I don't think that make any sense
Makisan, what do you thnk my suitable job is ?
Working in A coffee shop
See
I was said to be suitable.
Don't be exicted yet, I have not made my decision yet
I think I shall strive my best
It seems I am satisfied
The rest period is almost over
I shall make you the best coffee tomorrow
Bring your ear closer
can you hear the blending of beans ?
I can't
I can.
The sound of beans
Stop being fooling around and return to work !
Yes
I did no know he had such an compassionate in coffee
I think its a good idea, its his choice.
That's not a good idea to draw him off ATC
You did not just invite him right ?
Everyone, return to your position
What happened ?
The govement plane has just disappeared
EP04
Yuki, Please look closely at Kanto East area
Please go and report the case to ATM
What do you mean by disappeared
The cause is not yet found
The radar of kanto east is strange
There are many targets have disappear from that area
How about flights around it
Yes, flights around that are has disappeared also
We are using non-radar procedure in that area
001 was able to contact on radio but not on radar
Is it due to ES-6 a/c  that interfere with the signal ?
It seems not to be the cause
The trouble isn't due to radar reception ?
I don't think this would be a big, trouble
plus we are having less traffic in that area
How about divert a/c to the nearest airport ?
I have suggested, but rejected
There are many flights which don't want delays or divert ,right ?
Now, we have to do is to follow the orders from ATM
Until we find out the problem, safety is the priority
Please go and support kanto east sector
Understood
Please give restriction to departure a/c
and change the route to avoid flying in kanto east sector
understood
Maki san, which sector has disappearing a/c ?
Kantou  east,    that should be tiring
It seems that the prime minister's flight is also involved
Asian x 726, rgr, d/m FL 250
Is it a Radar malfunction ?
But our sector has no problem
What would it be ?
Japanair force 001 ,Tokyo control , if you hear me squawk ident
one more time
The flight of prime minister has no repsonse
What happened ?
I do not know
I will check on the guard ( emergency) frequency
The flight was in contact on radar, right ?
Now it is gone
What would it be.
How long was it on radar contact ?
about 4 mins
I have contacted ATM
Are they helpless on this case
Seem so
There are flights from hyakkuri, scramble
I wonder is that an escort to our prime minister's flight
But i did not heard of scrammble radar neither departure from hyakuri
There is no malfunction in the radar screens
ATM is helpless to us , its seems to be our system's problem
I shall check again
Radar System Control Room
Japan388, descend at pilot discretion maintain FL180
The flight of prime minister has disappeared, right ?
would that be ok ?
Would that be a hi-jack ?
Do you know the film of air force one ?
Roynson 999, roger
May be airforce one is fight with the hi-jackers ?
who ?
Hi-jacking our prime minister
Who is fighting with a 72 years old man ?
if there is emergency , the beacon code should change
That must be a fault, because it happens only in movies
You think movies are rubbish ?
You should think more like a soldier
Tokyo control, Royoson999, traffic insight.
Tokyo control roger
You should think that the world is in danger and might hit our prime minister
Skymark 308, contact chuubu approach 119.17
You know its the spirit of hero in america movie
I will contact you later
What are you doing ?
I am calling
Its the first time to have such a huge problem for aircraft disappearing from radar
and the boards is coming to investigate on the case
Why ?
There is a VIP flight on board
That is for the sake of our prime minister
That is really troublesome
Is it in a worse situation ?
Shimura ?
shimura , Its since a while we met last time
Me too
How long was that ?
7 years
7 years ?
You seems taller than before
I did not changed.
I will report to the boards after know the cause
Can I look closer at the radar screen
ok.
Do they know each other ?
Yes,
There work together before
Did they had an argument or so before ?
It seems they don't go along
Keep it as a secret, he seems owe yuki san something
Japanese air force 001,Tokyo control
Japanese air force 001, There is thunderstorm  around our vincinty, thus it may affect our transponder signal
Japanese air force 001 report present position and estimate ARMOR.
Estimate Armor 1335z
Japanese air force 001 ,roger
What happened ?
I finally have contact with prime minster's flight
The flight should be just before armor
Contact ATm and report about it
There is no malfunction, I shall go to check on the systems
Is prime minister ok ?
I don't ask such things
Please check it
If you so worry, why not you do it yourself
Please.. check it for me
Maki
Japanese air force 001, is our prime minster hurt ?
There was no movement of the a/c and he is fine
He is fine
Thank you.
Yuki kun, Is shimura kun ok ?
Did anything happened every since that incident ?
Yes, he would be returning  to his headquarters, thus its fine
It seems the incident is still not solve
Yes ?
Please change work shift with kanto south sector
Understood
Let's shift
That's good that the traffic has gain radio contact
I will come back after 10 mins
What is that ?
It seems something is moving quickly
Centraair nippon 562,  traffic 12 oclick, 7 miles ,
fast moving opposite direction type unkown,
but may be F15
FL210 is read out, and climbing
report traffic in sight
traffic will converge
Centraair 562 , the traffic has fly pass us
The distance between us was very near
understood
Matsumato, report this to yuki kun
OK
Where did the preceeding traffic went ?
It is heading to the east and the traffic is cleared of conlfict
The weather is not good, it may be unimportant
Please handout the report regarding to the converging traffic later
Yes , I will report later
It wasn't hi-jack
I was longing for that
How would someone hi-jack a 72- year old, old man  for ?
What if our prime minister is a kung fu master ?
I don't like to work with Hara san..
it is really annoying.
There should be america here , right ?
Seems to.
I did not watch.
it should be here
There is ..
See...
Mermadstar 56, reduce speed 280 knots for arrival spacing
Mermadstar 56, how do you read ?
Mermadstar 56,  how do you read ?
Mermadstar 56, reading you 5 , how do you read ?
Mermadstar 56, reading you 5, reduce speed 280 knots for arrival spacing
What happened ?
There are traffic  disappeared
which aircraft was that ?
skynex 776
Skynex776, radar contact lost recycle squawk  2204
skynex 776 rgr
let's change shifts
776 has radar contact lost
Please take an eye on that
There is problem here,
Yamada's radar scope has target disappearing..
These seems to be abnormal.
Yuki, there are traffic disappearing rapidly.
Here also
same here
What is this all about ?
What is happening ?
Radar resumed normal
Yuki speaking, the electricity just black out, now using the back up power supply.
Do you know what is going on ?
I am not sure also
The Secondary Surrveillance Radar (SSR) has no problem I shall check on the radar system
are you ok there ?
but please come and do a complete, check
it may require some time to figure out the problem, hang on .
Understood.
Maki, Is your sector fine ?
Its ok.
understood
I do not know the cause of the problem , once the problem has found I shall contact you at once.
Check the electricity breaker to find abnormality
You should check carefully
You monitor the control room
Can I come with you to investigate the problem ?
Understood, ok
What is happening, why did the system restarted ?
Can I take your position ?
It is rare that you ask for
There is not enough time to look through the manual
Great to know you can do it fater than me
I am sorry
Code ?
I memorised by heart
please fogive me for once
as i need to deal with this quickly
Being young is good.
Do you know what is the problem ?
Not yet.
Its bad..
Southairways 21, turn right heading 110 for spacing
What are you doing ? revoke the instruction
Didn't you get the wrong callsign ?
I am sure i did not.
Atlantas airline 118, turn left heading 90 for spacing
South ocean airways, turn right heading 110 for spacing
Southairlines 21, turn right heading 090 for spacing
I have received the instruction before, you want us to turn left this time ?
Your heading is wrong, that is why we are correcting it.
Please turn now
Hey.. what is happening
Japan air 878, turn right heading 270 for spacing
Japan air 878, turn right heading 270
why are you moving ?
ANA65 turn left heading 250 for spacing
No..
The data are being modified
It seems that someone has break te security system and mad e the modification
What a silly act
and it seems that they add a lock to prevent people to remove this virus
who would do something like this
please check the last access of the system
today ?
It s the time we just open
i will check the ip to locate the computer
There are a lot of type of hacker, he is called a cracker
it is similar to a hacker but the job of hacking in is called cracker
you really know a lot
To know where is it access needs so time
But i would know it at once.
What is it ?
oh no...
Everyone stop issue clearnce and stop instruction to aircraft
The callsign on your radar screen are switched
Re-identify the target's callsign again
now we are in a worse situation
Yamda stop dreaming
If you can't do it, just get away
sorry
Japanese airforce 001  was safely handoff to handeda approach
understood
Drop all the insrtuction to the a/c
Yes
The RDPC system is down and we know that the displayed callsign are incorrect
We will contact you when we have further information
how is your side
There is no problem in our side
I will give adequate restriction to all traffic
What has happened ?
The radar screen are inoperative
What do you mean ?
I will report it to you later
I have contact ATM
now we have to do is to identify the traffic with wrong displayed callsign
Takashita, kun
Can you explain what happened to the radar screen ?
There was a program that changed all the callsign into incorrect one
Is it possible to restore the original data ?
I don't know
Is that an easy job to change the data ?
We have a high security measures, and it requires a  password to access from remote computers
So that means we are screwed up ?
Yes.
Who would do such act, and why are they doing this for ?
We have found who access the computer
We found that PC from this room had access to the radar system
how could it be. ?
Really ?
We don't know which one, but its just a matter of time.
That mean..
The criminal is within us
667, tokyo control c/m FL 210
You should move that a/c away, watch carefully
What are you doing, get away
Go home, you are not capable for today's duty
Why did not you protect here ?
she is not suitable.
Yuki san.
That is the limits of a Air traffic controller
Please follow my orders in controller
We shall try our best to identify the traffic
so, is it yuki san, your deicision only ?
It is the order from tokyo control ACC
There is a very high possibility that the criminal is within us
It is wasting our time just to find the crinimal and we are lack of staff
it was done to protect you
The radar just shutdown
If we are using non-radar procedure in long term, the stress would accumlate
Here..
Please believe us as a team, we are not alone.
traffic..
3 mins due to traffic
fly heading 240
c/m Fl 280
Why did you became an " Air traffic controller " ?
I like jobs related the sky
I don't have a specific reason, but it doesn't mean you can be irresponsible.
I wanted to be a pilot, but i am near-sighted
which inhibit me from taking the pilots exam
Thus, I hope to be a support of pilots instead
I watched a animation when I was in high school,
and I found it is so cool to be an ATC
But , ATC exams are also difficult
Although I failed once.
But looking back, I was greatful that I was a ATC, not a pilot
I felt that it is worthwhile, as i see my hardwork paid off
It was my first exposure to the job of ATC and
surprised when I first visit tokyo control during high school
I thought it was cool, because of its important and its existence to maintain safety of the sky
I think what ever reason i wanted to be ATC, i want to be a smart clever ATC that provide high quality ATC service to aircraft
What is the charming point as an ATC ?
I think that would be love.
All the connection in controlling is conntected with love.
It is a sense of mission to ensure safety of every traffic you control
And also a sense of solidarity when working as a team
A lot... for example
If you did a great job, pilots would say thank you.
Although it just a thank you, it gives me strength, and lifted my confidence
I think that air traffic control does not limit to age, education,
It is the love from pilots, from passengers, love from teamwork
ATC is all about love.
Challenging and rewarding ?
I felt that I have to protect this large sector of airpsace is challenging and rewarding
But, its only my opinion.
Its like "you can't fly without me ", isn't remarkable as an ATC ?
Actually it is in fact the truth, but it require cooperation between ATC facilites and pilots to ensure flight safety
Its not the only all about me
But i would do my best to protect my airspace
What is the remarkable trouble as an ATC ?
This seems to be a difficult question
It would be difficult when you are panic and give the wrong instruction as it is real people on your hands.
There are still things we do not now nor foreseeable by our naked eyes, thus ATC is an important job that required communication
Eating quickly ?
The resting time is very short,
As a women, it s the greatest trouble
Did I answered your question ?
I found that we have to be quick in decision, which is stressful.
Thus, the trouble is to eat quickly,
What is the T-shirt about ?
It is my senior's t-shirt
In the drama, there is someone who make coffee, right ?
Thank you
You are taking this seriously
There is someone visitng, so remove that when someone comes.
Ok.
I have a friend called shikijima..(not from drama)
And he is also good at making coffee
And I also like coffee
Ofcourse, I drink during breaktime
The break time has ended
What is UTC ?
Universal Time coordinated is a synchronised time used in aviation, and in japan it is +9
There is a flight 179 with medical emergency, originated haneda diverted to cyuubu
What is it ?
Heart attack
There is first aid treatment but..
What is medical emergency ?
That means that flight is requesting prioirty to land due to patient on board need to be sent to hospital asap.
If pilots request, we shall prepare the pilot to land/ divert from its orignal destination
That means, we will make arrangements for such emergency
Turn right heading 310
Skyjapan 358, turng right heading 310
Orion 776, d/m FL 250
d/m FL 250, orion 776
CNF stands for conflict alert
The is a grave danger between 2 aircraft
It is an abbreviation to indiate potential convergence/ conflict between aircraft
Orian 776, in clouds, negative contact
They may not make it
When is blinking red, that means the traffic is getting very close,
thus we must give instruction to separate them immediately
What is downburst in ATC phrase ?
It means that the wind blowing downwards ( a type of turbulance)
When planes fly over that area, takeoff and landing may be difficult.
taking control of the aicraft would be diffcult in that downburst area
Although its normal and we can avoid by pilot reports or weather forcasting system but still its sacry