This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
xx
Do you know there are rules when flying ?
Where every you go in the world, there must be a "high way"
In aviation, we call them airways, analogous to highways in lamen terms
All aircraft in japan fly from and to this predefined route- airways to ensure safety
TO maintain proper separation during takeoff, landing and enroute,
Air traffic controllers are there to instruct pilots on hdg, speed and alt to ensure safety.
for example a plane flying from fukoka to haneda
First the pilot contacts the atc and the aerodrome controller give clerance from ground movements to airborne
From aerdrome control, the a/c is pass to terminal control
then from terminal control is passed to the 4 major Area Control Centre
ACC uses radar facility to track the flight and guide them to their destination
The green is Fukoka Control and blue is Tokyo control area
The plane flies with the predefined route and contact fukuoka control then tokyo control
The plane is then transfer to the terminal control of haneda for landing
The ATC uses radar to maitain separation is called Air Traffic Control
In the world, Air traffic Control has a variety of complex rules and system
Because of These sets of rules and Air traffic controllers strive to separate traffic made flying in the air safe
Do you know that ATC will sit at the cockpit to observe as a training ?
ATC are the one who give precise instruction to pilot and to make sure safety of the sky
It is important to build a trustworty relationship between the pilot and ATC
There are 4 times of cockpit observation training in a year
The ATC will join a flight and observe in the cockpit
This enhance their understanding on pilots difficulties during controlling
thus to imrove the quality of ATC  services
How many time do I have to repeat myself ?
I am busy
I will come back at 2000 ( 8pm)
how about dinner ?
I will have it outside
Its ok.
If you have time, at least let me see you, in person
You have do the washing and chores.
Ok.
Your daughter
She is growing
For girls, its better to have a mother to be taken care of
Women are always a troublemaker
when you grow older, you will think in that way
I think men are also troublesome
Just talk about Shikijima, don't generalise to all men
It is really troublesome for him
I said to him to help me fix something, but he said no.
If i ask you, you won't be like that ,right ?
may be..
I know you are a great men
No, you can't like this men, its not moral
That is really hurting.
I just wanted to said he is my cup of tea
You are lying
ofcourse.
You are really a silly type.
Women are really scary
Tokyo ground, ANA241,spot 65,  request push back
We seems to have a pretty vistor to take the cockpit observation training
its not my concern
Is she married ?
Whatever
You are really  special
Excuse me
The ATC who is coming for the training has arrived
Ok
please come up
Hi sakino Cyan
Shall we have meal after this flight ?
Sorry, I have a date
Is the opponent you ?
Its with a New CA
Really, are you going to eat Ramen ?
Its really a good idea, but I will be eating with them.
ok, forget it.
Don't keep the ATC waiting.
Let her in.
Yes
Its really good to get marry with a Cabin Attendant(CA)
Excuse me
I am Suzuki, ATC from Toyko Control Area Centre
pleased to meet you.
she is quite old-fashioned
I am Kimura, the captain, pleased to meet you
Ainichi ,the co-pilot, please seat now, we are in a hurry.
Sorry for the rudeness, he is a workaholic
Let's start
cockpit  checklist
gallery power on
Emergency exit lights on
cabin signs auto and ON
In tokyo control ?
After some research , we have found that Yamada's dad was an ATC
Yamada seems to follow the footpaths of his day to be an ATC
But , shouldn't we know it at the first place ?
The surname changed, and used the mother instead,
that's why we don't know
That's strange
Yoshimura said its better to keep this in low profile.
But we have to take an eye on it.
Cheers for hardwork
Do you like aeroplanes ?
Yes.
Do you often go abroad for trips ?
Sometimes
Where do you often go ?
Kimura San
ANA241, wind 160@9 rwy 16L cleared for take off
rwy16L, cleared for take off, ANA241
wish of luck
Let's go
This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
EP03
Thank you
You really making your own coffee shop
Remove that when the visitors are coming
Maki San is so late.
She is on the flight for cockpit obervation training
She should be meeting us later.
Do you know which flight she is on ?
She will be monitoring our conversation, so we would be more alert if we know
I will not tell you for the sake of fairness
Because my pronunciation is strange, please tell me
childish, I will use my beatles's songs to annoy her
She likes to scould us , you know ?
Would you cut it out, it won't help
Please tell us which flight ?
I say again, we are not going to tell you.
Let's start the meeting
There will be visitors visiting the Area centre
First , Hara,
I said to wear formal dressing
formal dressing ?
Are you discriminating the brand ?
what ?
Enough, anyone have extra suits ?
I have another meeting later and have an extra suit
great, we will use that
But the size...
It may be a little small for him
but its not a famous brand
its doesn't matter
I don't want to lend
Even so, its seems not enough time to buy a new one
We have an old locker with an old suit, is that ok ?
Let's use it
But does the size fit ?
And is it a good idea to use without permission ?
He is on a medical treatment, so he won't notice, right ?
Or else, we just force Yamada to say ok.
Ok I will lend you mind later.
Before noon, there will be visitors coming to observe us
There should be about 10 people will be coming
Although we have warn them not to run or talk loudly
if they are distrubring the normal operation of ATC
We will kindly ask them to leave
We hope you can give some patience during the visit
The visit will last for 50 mins, if there is a need to warn / scould them is acceptable.
Hara, please don't do something weird
Don't talk dirty things
Do something before the vistors come
Yes
I like aeroplanes , that's why I became a pilot
There must be a lot of people who like planes as an ATC, right ?
Ofcourse, there are amatuer that likes to take photo of airplanes
listen to airband and think being an ATC is cool
They must know a lot of planes, right ?
I don't think so.
A lot of ATC taking this training keep asking a lot of questions, like a fool
Comapred to pilots, this might be
But We as ATC have fundamental knowledge of aircraft
But, there are a lot of ATC do not know
Its not very good to answer all of their questions
I would like to suggest ATC to study more about aircraft performance
Indeed, it is a job that both parties must understand their work
Last time, when pilots visit tokyo control area centre
a lot of pilots were shock to see "that" is the work of ATC
Have you visited tokyo control area centre ?
Not yet
If you think we are useless, please come and visit us
You would know better on how do we work down there.
Is that a sarcasm ?
What is this atmosphere ?
Let's enjoy this flight, please !
Contact Tokyo Control
Tokyo Control, ANA241, Maintain FL 280
ANA241, Tokyo Control, rgr, Maintain FL 280
ANA241, Tokyo Control , say again.
Do you know this person ?
Yes, by guess from the accent
He seemed to have a low english proficiency level
esepcially in pronunciation
Can you do something about that ?
what about ?
Teach ATC to speak clearly , especially in ATC phrase
You should have english proficiency test, right ?
Like they should have at least level 4 or above ?
They must have pass, if not they will not be at the position as ATC
I know
There are rules like callsign
We also access the speaker's speak, accent
You really know them by heart
You know what ?
You as pilots also should pass an examination in order to fly in duty
Yes ?
Nothing.
Hey, Let's relax and make it an enjoyable flight !
Which flight is Maki san on ?
Japanair 1622, request descend.
JAL1622, d/m FL 230
What ?
I noticed my accent is getting better after being warned by Maki everyday
Btw, look at your back
That is a weird outfit
People around should laugh with that outfit.
Why is that person  wearing a mask ?
Yuki kun, He is on Japanese suit
What should we do ?
Leave it alone
Change  (work shift)
Ok
Are you having colds ?
No
I heard children will be coming, so I wore this
Its an additional service for them
I don't quite get it, please  be presentable.
Hara San, the sepration is getting close, better take an eye onto it.
Hara San
What is it ?
ANA241, haha.ha...
Fool
I will kill you when I return
We all make mistakes, its ok
I am sorry for having a silly ATC
Don't worry its just a loud noise from the radio
what about telling them that you on board,
I don't think so.
Really
ANA241, contact toyko control 125.7
ANA241, Tokyo control, Suzuki San is onboard this flight. Please becareful.
No.
You don't have to report that
That should give them a warning sign that Suzuki San is angry
Please don't making uneccessary actions
If i reported, everyone should be more aware, right ?
I would be happy though.
We see all traffic  (planes ) as equal
Please, make it a more enjoyable flight!!
Japancentra 35,c/n Fl 290
Asianx655, descend to FL 300 by 20 miles east of CUE ( otsu)
Let's shift
Please
Is it ok for 5 mins
Ok.
Have you get used to the working place ?
Not yet
how old are you ?
How is it ?
I will ask it later
What is it ?
Its is not something very important
Is the observation visting amusing ?
Its something I hate each year.
Ota san, do you have anything ?
There will be a turbulance near Oosaka
Really.
Please be prepared
Ok
That sign is not good
oh no ,remove it
No one saw this, right ?
Thanks for waiting,
Please come this way
cool
Don't go that way
Please keep quite
Yuki
Don't scould in from of the observers
The boards are also here
Ok
Excuse me
This is the enroute control and
oversees all the Japan's sky
You may have know there are different duties at the aerodrome level
There are separated into different section
TWR, DEP, APP, GND, DEL and CTR( ENROUTE)
and you are now in the enroute
We observe and maintain air safety here
Please look there
We are controlling more than 3700 of flights everyday
Cool
Mother, there is a strange uncle
Regarding to the communication between ATC and pilot...
We use headsets.
Please come here
There are very fine instruments here and please don't get near to prevent damage of them
Here
Ota san, should i vector them to the south
If we vector to the south, it would lost a lot of fuel.
JAL3531, d/m FL 250 deviation 080 heading is approved
what is it ?
What is your name
hana, 5 years old.
Now he is at working,
you cannot be here
please go back to your mother and father
Who's kid is this,
Don't say that in front of a kid.
Byun air 109, turn right ?
No, uncle...
Who are you ?
Yamada, can you please take care of this girl?
Yes
Where is your mother ?
Please go and find her
Hana
I said you cannot leave my vincity, right ?
I am sorry
Its ok.
Are we flying over that cloud ?
ofcourse, we will
But we have an angel watching for us
Its about outa's the Air traffic controller
Isn't it dark in there ?
Its always like that
are you worried ?
A little
Follow me
I give up
I think its better
Once i do that, I feel better
I will request deviation
Roger
TOkyo control ANA241, request heading 250
ANA241, heading 250 is approved.
You are interfering my work, get out!
You may be disturbing the work, please come over here
ANA241, heading 330 is approved.
What is the red mark ?
It is turbulance
Now ,there is  a/c being deviated to avoid the turbulance
The a/c is going through that narrow place ?
yes.
ANA241, turn left heading 230 for spacing.
ANA241, turn right heading 290 for spacing.
ANA 241, turn left heading 240 for spacing.
Please be quite
That is the work of uncle ?
Sorry for the little shake during flight
its's ok, I have learnt a lot from that turbulance
Did you do the facial exercise ?
If the ATC respond to our request earlier, we won't even feel the shake
Can't you stop complaining ?
I am just telling the truth
I will go first.
Please don't make a fight here
No I won't.
Because of you guys ( ATC) , we can be relived during flight
Pilots flying alone can't be totally safe in the sky
I not good at expressing this
but what I am trying to say is that
ATC and pilots have an interdepent role.
It is not often we see you ATCs in person, come and join us some time
Thank you for your cooperation, good day
good day
don't screw things up
aren't you leaving ?
I will observe until the end
There is nothing more to observe here
I am leaving now
What you are going to do after this
I will be returning to Haneda right now and write up my reports
I said that you ATC are no good
I was wrong
It was a lie
I also did poorly when I was a new pilot
I was nervous and make myself like a fool
Really
I didn't take it too personal.
I found that I may have misunderstand you ATCs
No, I don't think so.
Excuse me , I am leaving
Thank you very much today
I will certainly come to visit Tokyo control centre
I want to see you anyway
Please guide me when I come
Do not hesitate to let me guide you at that time
See you
Yuki
You did a great job
People are happy and contented
Whatever happends I just be myself, its nothing special.
Great that there is no complaints
That better than I thought.
What should i do,
Maki san will be returning here, right ?
Maybe
She is returning from Fukuoka
If she leaves now, she should be here before 3 pm
Really
Break Time
You screwed up today
Let's go to the simulator Centre
Kinoshita kun
yes
Please follow me
its a dancer out there
Its seems to be free to enter here
What a strange person
This way
Ask him to come to my office later
Oota san ,you did a great job in the deviation
Its not very hard
Dad
I do not have a daughter
I come to apologise
Because you don't listen to me
You are wrong
I am working now, can you please walk out ?
Is that a good idea ?
Why do you have to treat your family members that cool ?
Excuse me
Yes ?
Please take care
Yuki San, Maki San said to detain Shikijima San
I think I can just let him go
Will I be scould ?
You should also escape
Ok.
Cheers for hardwork
I went to the briefing room but was told to go to the resting room
I just know that we still have a meeting
Let's go.
Cheers for hardwork
Thanks, I'm returning it
Its ok. I don't want it anymore.
You see its quite dirty
I will return after cleaning
Please
cheers for hardwork
I really don't like wearing suits.
Hara San, I think you should escape.
Hara
Come with me.
Are you leaving now?
You are really a bossy men
Mind your own business
That girl was called Nanami ?
She was a pity  girl being scolded by you.
I don't have a daughter.
cheers for hardwork, take care
Impressed ?
Why ?
I give birth to this child when i was 19 years old
I was still having money from parents and just entered university
Ofcouese, I would be scolded
My husband did not enough introduce his parents to mine
I have a long argument with my dad, and said to get out if I am going to give birth
Please take some tea, if you don't mind
Thank you.
he never came back ever since this situation happened.
I wanted to come and apologise to him , but
But he refused
I come here to look for him because he left home 3 years ago
I came apologise now and them and seems to be a burden to him.
After that, he moved and I don't know where he was
So , you use this ATC visting as a chance to find your dad ?
I thought he would be in his working place.
I see.
How is the relationship between Ootasan and his wife ?
He get in touched for sometime
but , dad seems to have some arguments with her
My mom has saw my daughter
And she wanted to take the chance of see me, my daughter as a family reunion with my dad
But why she called oota san as "uncle" , instead of Dad ?
I gave her the picture of my dad
And she thought its an old uncle so..
i see
That's why she clings to oota san.
Actually, I have not established the wedding
My husband said that until my dad accept this marriage, he will not force it
I and my dad would like to follow the virgin rule
Turn around and say thank you together, but..
I want to apologise to my dad
He is my only precious father.
I don't want to keep at this relationship with him.
Cheers for hardwork
Where is Shikijima kun ?
He returned
Smart, He got away!
Who is this ?
I am Nanami, daughter of Outa san
Thanks for taking care for my dad
Welcome here
Dad
Please
Just hear
I don't have anything to say to you.
I don't want
I don't want to hurt you and mom because of me
I don't want a have relationship with you like this
I am sorry
Where did you come ?
It is the only place you would hear me.
This is my working place.
Do you know how much shame you had brought to me ?
I won't change, no matter how hard you try to apologise.
You are not my daughter.
Do what ever you want
please forgive me for once
I am the only daughter
Please
Please wait
It is non of your business
Get away
i cannot
Please try to listen to your daughter
Don't try to put opions on other family's problem.
Let go
Please
Please listen for once
You are the only father of Nanami, right ?
What ever you call youself, you are still a father
If you are father, take the responsibilites and accept the indulgence of your daughter
my dad did not care for me at all
He said, do what ever you like
I worked hard to my way of life
He left me and my mom
You are still a alive, right ?
If you are a dad,
Listen to your indugent daughter.
I ,..
I don't have that chance anymore.
Outa san, please
Listen to your daughter.
Yamda, Let's go
Outa san I am sorry.
It's ok.
I will take care of him.
Yamada, your dad was a splendid Air traffic controller
He was great  a person, and a great Air traffic controller
You want to hear this, right ?
Let's go
Kitana
Mama
Uncle..
You have been a Cabin Attendant (CA)
You are really a silly daughter of mine
You left your mother and fly up in a sky is selfish
You seemed did not understand why I was angry
If you don't raise the morale
You would lose the most precious thing in life
Call your mother
Let's have meal together
Thank you
Sorry,
You don't have to apologise to me, silly
Its useless
I didn't think i would say that to outa san
Well, emotions changes
But, I ..
Nothing
Please tell me
I want to know
Then continue to wait
Yamda kun, Today is a great day to look up the sky
Yes
Please remind me to capture Nakijima kun
Yes.
Come back , the Govemernt plane disappear
Maki san, which sector did the plane disappear ?
East of Kantou
The prime minister's flight is involved.
The aviation boards are coming to investigate on this case
Why ?
Because it is a VIP a/c
Shimuro ?
Yuki san, there are alot of targets are disappearing
also here.
Everone, stop your moves
What is the cause ?
We are not sure
Tell me the last time system is being accessed .
Oh no..
We have confirm it was accessed form the Controller's PC
The hacker is within us
Do you know that The FIR ( sky of japan) is called Fukuoka ?
In Fukuoka, Gannosu prefecture
The Fukuoka Area Control Centre
The headquarters of Fukuoka Air Traffic Management  (ATM)
Its manages all the airpace and oversess all 4 Area control centre of japan
It was established since 2005 to enhance flow ,effeiciency and safety of air traffic in japan
It is also responsible to notify individual airports , regards to
closing of runway and other relevant information
Because the ATM is located in Fukuoka, They call the Flying Information Region as Fukuoka
Thus, people called the sky of japan is fukuoka
The area of This airpspace is approximately 2400nm
The ATC has oversee and manage all 4 ACC, including
Naha, Toyko, Fukuoka And Sappro
They are the last resort to help prevent collision or accident to happen
We have to manage the traffic flow, the secotrs management
We are important also, to support Air traffic controllers
Japan is located in Asia, and there are lots of aircraft that we have to control everyday
To ensure High efficiency and safety ,they deply high technology system to help them make decision
The centralised system starts from ATM and various of information are then published to respective sectors
Nevertheless, these automated systems cannot 100% garantee a forcast of natural disaster
It is to be said despite the technology, the one who make decision is human
The last decision is made be human, not by machine
It is better to trust a human than a system depsite all its advancement
We take balance between the input from computer and interaction with human to make the final decision
Because of their endless effort , the sky is safe to be flown.