This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
Do you know there are rules when flying ?
Where every you go in the world, there must be a "high way"
In aviation, we call them airways, analogous to highways in lamen terms
All aircraft in japan fly from and to this predefined route- airways to ensure safety
TO maintain proper separation during takeoff, landing and enroute,
Air traffic controllers are there to instruct pilots on hdg, speed and alt to ensure safety.
for example a plane flying from fukoka to haneda
First the pilot contacts the atc and the aerodrome controller give clerance from ground movements to airborne
From aerdrome control, the a/c is pass to terminal control
then from terminal control is passed to the 4 major Area Control Centre
ACC uses radar facility to track the flight and guide them to their destination
The green is Fukoka Control and blue is Tokyo control area
The plane flies with the predefined route and contact fukuoka control then tokyo control
The plane is then transfer to the terminal control of haneda for landing
The ATC uses radar to maitain separation is called Air Traffic Control
In the world, Air traffic Control has a variety of complex rules and system
There are the ones working behind the scenes
which makes the sky safe to be flown
Do you know where is the radar located ?
As the technology advances, more are used
one is located kangawa prefecture hakone city , near a bus stop
It was the first established survelliance radar
It is the Hakone radar number 1
It is the foundation of air traffic control, which can  provide reliable atc service
It has been using for 50 years and still in use , nowadays
It updates targets every 10 seconds
overseeing kanto area
There are more than 20 of these radar located in japan
Which monitor the airsapce of Japan
Cheers for your hardwork
Thank you.
Kayoko, thanks for coming
Its a long time, cheers for your hard work
I am sorry also.
What ?
What  is this ?
You runaway from house because of this lady ?
No. this is not...
It is not a teenager
Is he ok ?
Should we wake him up ?
He need some rest
Isn't it too tired?
may be
No, its not it..
Itsu..
Horrible
What is he saying ?
Ep05
Maintain FL 250
Okayama san, 3 days left
That's getting lonely here
Yuki is off ?
yes he was sent to the boards for the investigation
Why is shima's wife is here ?
Did I told you they aren't going well ?
Although they chat with the manager, that they were good enough
They are here
This does not look good
Its not only about their character
its about how they view things
one is from international school
And this from baseball high school
This match seems to be interesting
So, Yamada, Shall we start ?
I am your instructor ,Shimoyanaki for today's OJT
I am the supervisor , shimuya narumi
Please to meet you
Yamada, you have been placed to Tokoho sector 1, is this your first time ?
no.
Why are you talking like that ?
You used to say things directly
I have been said to use pilote speech by the supervisor today
I have to make sure that silly man make her speech clearly
He is still a silly men
he does not like kids
he cann't build trust with them
I have been playing catch ball with them yesterday
This is how you train most of the time ?
That is very silly, right ?
He rename his child because he like the team
Yamada, you know what ?
its not worth to listen to a woman to look down at baseball players
who would listen to you ?
Really..
Hey..
Can you please keep you voice down ?
The meal are something very awful.
I don't have a choice,
I have night shifts
You should at least make a meal for the children or yourself
Do you know I have to wake up early and make breakfast and lunch for all of you ?
I have to do chores even I am tired after work ?
Yamda, Let's start training
Its strange when hearing their conversation
Nakajima make the meal by wraping things up ?
Takahashi
my break time is over, why not wake me up ?
I saw you sleeping very sweet, so did not bother
did i said something during my nap ?
you said " no, its not.."
That was not a sweet dream
Did you change your schedule ?
Yes,
That would be night shifts ?
that will be your last day ?
Don't worry
This is ATC technician Takahashi speaking
The pc on control room seems to be freezed
Why did you change to night shifts ?
Its our job to keep the system running, right ?
I want to take responsiblity to look over them at the last day of my work
What would you like ?
A present for my retirement ?
Try to guess
cofee set
There is no such thing
Sorry
A kiss of goodbye
Yokohama san I..
I can do it..
No you.. silly
There are cute ladies in the control room, right ?
I hope they can kiss me
You want maki san ?
No.. I will get a slap instead
Nakajima and kamoto san ?
Well, yes.
Its my dream
What happened ?
Takahasi,
Here should be in narita.
No its not.
I was saying the Japanair here
That is why I am saying its going to the south
You don't understand at all
Are those couples alright ?
Well
Done, its seems working now
Thank you
When I get older, I don't know how to fix things
Its much easier in the past
Before we admire the technicians
It was quite often to contact the technician in the past
You have 3 more days left ?
Yes.
who is on night shift on the last day  ?
uchihara.
Yuki isn't here ?
he seems to be busy in the headquarters
I will try to confirm it for you later
No need, its fine.
I will confirm it myself
Takahashi, Let's go
Yes.
Thank you
United 112, maintain FL 270
Have you get used to it ?
When the number of a/c increased, I get confused
Really?
My daughter went to Asakusa's Temple and get this for you
Thank you
Please send my greetings to her
Your dad was professional,
he would get traffic a beautiful one line separation
With a great precise separation between traffic
He was a great instructor at that time
Please watch carefully
Airmacau55, increase speed 310 knots for spacing
JAl253,
Descend and maintain FL 250
537, d/m Fl 270 and reduce speed to 250 for arrival spacing
break; DAL826, turn left 080 , reduce speed 250
ANA537
PAC937 d/m FL 290
That's cool
I wonder what's going on in her head
I want to see
What are you doing ?
I am scanning he brain
Sailar..
Hara san, I thought you can to change shift with me..
Will you come to my place for dinner ?
Thank you
Cheers for hardwork
I have brougt you the fine coffee
Thank you
May I be excused.
I wonder did he made all these when he is in break ?
He did these way before his break
He can't be a ATC and coffee boy at the same time
Stop escaping from me or in work..
so angry..
don't be that angry
I better marry a man that has a different occupation than mine
I don't like to be with a husband that is my colleague
its hard to work together when we are couples.
How much time did we spend in holiday ?
We don't have much.
We work at different shifts, we don't have much time to see each other
If we work together, in neighbouring sector, we would be together
but..
What do you mean ?
I was saying that you are such a beautiful women but..
Well, I feel that sometimes, i'm pretty
I shall get some tea
What should I do, I have to make dinner for my kids
Its should be ok for an hour or so
wait for a while
hello ?
Maki San ?
No thanks
Why were you working together?
i go so that I can have holiday
I have baseball competition later
I support for bench
Do you think I am silly ?
I was anticipating that team..
It is my training to my kid
Hey boy, go for it, ...
Yamada, theses are monster parents..
Becareful..
I will go for tea before home..
Ah really.
We are going to batting center ?
Really ?
I will go first, I will with you guys next time.
worse guys.
Again ?
Let's go.
Nakashima, where is maki san ?
There
I am not available (laugh)
Yokoyama san, you are early today
I let Takahashi to follow up
Young people are really keen on learning.
Its seems getting old won't help.
As we don't have aims / motivations to learn
but you have been working for 40 years
its long time.
I was invited by takahashi for dinner
Its a role model for him, and it better to call my wife to eat with
its hard to find a such good boy
How many times have you been switching positions ?
started Toko , hakone, kushiro, amori, sendai,
haneda, hachijyojima, fukuoka, itami and finally here
And my wife stayed with me where ever I go
I know that being a civil servant, we have a good amount of retirement pay
but i don't worry too much about that
I think the best is to be with my wife and to protect her for my life
did you have an affair with another women before ?
Well, once..
Well. still men are men...
Women should have found out that
they are not fools
They knew  it but try to hide it
they understand you work hard to make a living
Really ?
Did she knew about the date with mamoto ?
time to go
see you
Good morning
Thank you
please seat
How is it
That is delicious
It my special
Eh ?
I lose
I lose 13 time consecutive
no problem
really?
It would be you time to watch over them
So fast.
This is not a telephraph in showa times
I will be at headquarters tomorrow for the investigation
Its quite a long time and cheers for all your hardwork
so long,
I wish you enjoy your retiring days
That tricky..
Tomorrow is that last day
Expeditious And Decisive
It is time to collect suggestion
When can I receive the family crest ??
Can someone tear off hara's t-shirt ?
Yes, Let me do it
Please listen to me while tearing off the t-shirt
you might have know  that today, is the radar facility inspection day
as usual, we will start shutting down lights at 1500
We will leave only on radar scope for controlling and
others are to be inspected
And ...
Cheers for hard work
Where have you been
i went to brief the staff for radar scope inspection this afternoon
Thanks for the treat last time
My wife was happy about it
We don't have a child
She is gald that someone would visit her
I enjoyed the chat also
Have you heard of them talking about a farewell party ?
NO..
too bad.
Shall I say so ?
No.
It's ok.
It is different from the past.
What is this ?
You found it ?
If you are going to eat, please go somewhere else to eat
Its different, we are on night shifts
How about eating this together ?
It is forbidden
I don't think someone will found it
no..
Cheers for hardwork
Its time for inspection
understood
We will only provide service in Kanto south sector
The electricity will go off in 10 mins
please handoff your traffric to kanto south A sector
Yes
The room will become darken momentarily
Don't you think its like something worse will happening later ?
No..
I like this peaceful moment
Although ther is nothing happened, but to me its a fortunate day
I found that things changes
That is wrong
wake up..
Can anyway change shift with me ?
Again ?
I like to look at this peaceful place again, at my last day
I will be going
Cheers for hardwork
although its a little time we met, so long
How about breakfast ?
I will join
I want curry
Everyone are cool
I am here for a long time..
It may be difficult for technician and ATC to have a drink or so
Can you come..
What is this ?
It is the best words when I was a technician
although ATC should also be having those qualities
We are the one who ensure air safety
what ever happens in the control room, we are the one who gives support
At that very moment, we have to act expeditiously and be decisive
So I give this to you
Do you best
Thank you
Let me send you off
Its ok,
Let me be alone.
Ok.
Thanks for being with me for the long times.
be strong
I'll go first
men's stepping stone
That good to have this
I was fooled
cheers for all your hardwork
its was a surprise..
Please walk through this path
Yes ?
did you say about Sumako ?
How would I say so ?
I saw this scene in my dream
Dream is dream..
She is waiting
Hayako
Thanks for coming
I am sorry for being mean all the time
I was thinking its great to have a wife like that when I am old
Let's discuss about the kids later on
In my dream my ears are..
what ?
nothing.
Thanks for staying with me all the time
Yokoyama san..
I hope you like the farewell gift
Is that a dream?
you don't have to be that angry..
But you don't do that to me..
thanks for being with me 40 years
let's enjoy the remaining life together.
I am always there for you, no matters its cold, warm, happy or sad moments
you are going to oepn a cafe shop ,right ?
but
There is a condition
what is it ?
For the time being do not go for drinking
What..