This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
Do you know there are rules when flying ?
Where every you go in the world, there must be a "high way"
In aviation, we call them airways, analogous to highways in lamen terms
All aircraft in japan fly from and to this predefined route- airways to ensure safety
TO maintain proper separation during takeoff, landing and enroute,
Air traffic controllers are there to instruct pilots on hdg, speed and alt to ensure safety.
for example a plane flying from fukoka to haneda
First the pilot contacts the atc and the aerodrome controller give clerance from ground movements to airborne
From aerdrome control, the a/c is pass to terminal control
then from terminal control is passed to the 4 major Area Control Centre
ACC uses radar facility to track the flight and guide them to their destination
The green is Fukoka Control and blue is Tokyo control area
The plane flies with the predefined route and contact fukuoka control then tokyo control
The plane is then transfer to the terminal control of haneda for landing
The ATC uses radar to maitain separation is called Air Traffic Control
In the world, Air traffic Control has a variety of complex rules and system
Because of These sets of rules and Air traffic controllers strive to separate traffic made flying in the air safe
Do you know what is the relationship between aircraft and weather ?
Air traffic flow management center is located in fukuoka, Gannosu prefecture
They also manage different weather stations over the country
This is a doppler weather radar, a device to forcast wind direction and speed
This allows ATC to see how the movements of winds and prevent flying in severe weather conditions
If there is an adverse weather, They shall be assigned to nearest alternative airport, but
There may be not enough gates at the very moment.
which the aircraft have to divert to airports aside from their defined alternate airport
The coordination on diverting aircraft would be done in ATM
You are always strong
dangerous
This is very expensive
Is that really expensive ?
Its 33,000 yen
Everyone, let's return
The Goverment plane has disappeared
There someone on the radar screen
Collision
It is the first time to have a such trouble in radar
The boards have sent agents to investigate on this case
Shimuro
Do they knew before ?
It doesn't seem Yuki is in a good mood.
We have just experienced black out and we are on auxiliary power
Do you know what happened ?
I don't know either
EH ? what is happening ?
Why are you moving...
Why is the server in operating mode ?
I don't have time but i will try
The data modification has started
What is that ?
Somone has accessed the system and change the data
what is wrong ?
Everyone stop, do not give instruction
Don't look at your radar screen
forget the callsign and re-identify all your traffic
We have investigated the ip of access to the radar system
We have confirmed that it was accessed from tokyo control room
What ?
The criminal is within us
EP03
Really?
Please give me some time
Yuki, we shall try to recover the data
I will contact the headquarters and think of a way
Can you come with me ?
I have something to ask you
Hi, boss
What happened ?
What should we do ?
It about the callsign
The callsign are incorrect and interchanged with another a/c
If this continues, we can't handle this
Please follow up the case in Kantou East to South sector
Really ?
is it alright ?
Don't worry
Yuki, I'll count on you.
I will go to the security office
I will give you the survelliance camera video recording
Can I look at the radar system administrator list ?
Ok.
Shall we have a drink after this ?
Great
Which shop shall we go ?
Yamasan, we you join us ?
Not today
I would like to go baseball with you sometime
Your name is Yamashita?
You did not know ?
I ate the oniki made by Yamashita
He escape from the oniki ? (playing on japanese syllables)
By looking at the outlook its seems to be delicious
It was great
I got the tickets to the Baseball team this season
Thank you
How much ?
300,000 yen
You bet it
Are you busy ?
Let's work shift
It should be tiring yesterday, right ?
yes
Umi, The runways in haneda is closed due to snow.
Roger
Are you ok ?
Do you want someone to change shifts with you ?
I'm ok, others might be tired, also
I can't take rest for the sake of my selfishness
The runways in haneda is closed, right ?
Yes, due to snow
America 25, turn right heading 110 for spacing
Sky japan 157,Right engine has stoped, reason is not yet known
We would like to divert to haizan
Kimira san
This is Kantou South sector
We have one a/c have right engine failure
Which would want to use the runway
after 10 mins
Skyjapan 157, tokyo airport is closed due to snow
Removal operation is in progress and will reopen within 10- mins standby
why
vector the a/c away
Orienwings 667, tokyo control, c/m FL 210,  turn right heading 290
There is a jetaero, there,
look carefully
What are you doing ?
Change
orienwings 667, turn left heading 270 immediately
Go home
Yukisan
You are not suitable for the job
I call that an end today
Yuki san was right
I am a useless person
No, you are not.
I heard its holiday for Umi ?
Well its better that being fired after that incident
most likely she will be fired
I wonder what did yui said to the board
I heard that he said to the borads that she is a useless and should be fired
That quite mean of Yuki
Why did you not protect Umi from being fired ?
Did you tell the boards to fire her ?
Who told you I said that?
Everyone is talking about it
You believe those rumors ?
So believe it , if you like
Why did not you deny it ?
She is not suitable for the job.
Evenso, she is my girlfriend and she is suffering
Why did not you protect her ?
You are friends, in a team right ?
Let go
Yuki, san
You asked the board to fire her ?
Whatever.
Say something..
Here I am
This is the survelliance camera video from this morning until now
This is the data system's administrator list
This is everything ?
Thank you
What ever I have in hand, I shall report to the boards and start an investigation.
yes
Don't tell anyone about the investigation
When you find something contact me at once
If we found out who is it, will that person be fired ?
If you are right, this would be a terrorist attack
This means that terrorist is having an eye on the air traffic controller
We can't just let this happen again
roger
Tokyo control will cease operation and all traffic should handoff to fukuoka ATM for coordination
Ok.
What is the decision of the boards ?
Closed ?
Is that possible ?
It is the safest way
Don't worry about the handoff, Fukuoka ATM will take over the control of all a/c
Don't decide everything
The decision is made by me in here
It is about the safety of the japanese airspace
As the criminal is within us, I can't let tokyo control to operate
This is a terrorist  aiming at air traffic controller
Please think carefully
ATM shall contact you momentarily
It is not good
Prolonged use of non-radar procedure is not going work for long
Yuki
Sorry, can you please calm down
The radar scope...
We have taken undercontrol
This way
Yuki
Please make your decision
Hello, this is ATM
The radar has problem
We would like to mass handoff all traffic
We working on with it,
It would be difficult to do it all at once
please give us 30 mins for the preparation
When we are ready, we will contact you at once
Roger
The handoff preparation requires 30 mins
Yuki kun
What should we say to others ?
Please listen
ATM will takeover all a/c in here after 30 mins
It may be difficult, but we shall try our best to identify the traffic
Please give us a reasonable explanation
Is this the decision of Yuki ?
It is not a personal problem
I am asking the current elected manager
I am asking Yuki
There is someone who have hacked access the radar system
and changed the data in the system which made a chaos here
I think that before the investigation is made, its better to let ATM to take control
Let's stick to it before it recovers
Its not that
The operation in here must be ceased
And who's has that permission?
It is the direct orders from the boards of air safety
Kimuro
We have found that the radar system has been hacked from this room
thus there is a high possibility that the criminal is within us
This is the reason of ceased operation
We need time to coordinate with ATM, don't mess up the things
You should let them know the truth, these people can't just continue on
you will just make things worse and adding pressure to them
please stop arguing
It is not the time to argue
My radar disappeared
I will try to search for the Ip again
I may be again to make a trap
I did not search for it, as there was not enough time just while ago
It's strange that a person from outside can just breakthrough the security system
I am trying to connect via another server and locate the hacker
What are you ?
anyway, I shall try to recover the server
What happened ?
I don't know
May be some sort of trap ?
Yuki, what happened ?
We do not know, the computer just shutdown here
The display has just disappeared herew
It should be the problem from here
Takashi is trying his best to recover it, please wait for a while.
understood
The radar scope has nothing, is that ok ?
We are coping with non-radar procedure, its ok
I can't see anything, I'm worried
The manager really don't know anything ?
may be.
We have to wait for at least 30 mins
stress will accumulate when non-radar procedures are prolonged
Do you have any good suggestion ?
The only way is to follow up and give support as required
Its great to have a way to share information together
Yama san,  please take care of here
kinoshita, Can you do me a favour ?
Pacific area is at 10000ft
this will arrived in 11 mins
Yamada, its not your place here
help in other place
Its critical time here
Yes sir
What are you doing ?
Shimura san, please let Yamada san to continue
It is not the appropriate situation
Please..
What ?
I am saying to believe your partners
We are controlling as a team, and not alone
Because of this radar touble, it is important to work as a team, right ?
Yamada, follow up the rest there
Yes
The red highlighted are data that has been modified
If I can find the key to unlock the password, I can recover the data
Let me do I , I can find it.
What are you doing with these
please come with me
Kabuto, please come and help
Everyone, listen,
we will based on the information on the strip and arrange information on this enroute map
by position and altitude
If you need to handoff from one sector to another, report kinoshita and  karumoto
we will be the platform to share information to others
I will help
But do we have something to write on?
Let me borrow these
These are mine
I know
Let's use those to represent the traffic
Its quite expensive
Its time to use them
Should we write on something, like a note?
22 and ANA776 are quite near how was their separation ?
wait
wingsair22, reduce speed and  set as FL370
ANA776, increase speed, d/m FL 340
Pacific air , maintain current speed and c/m 270
Roger
Rainbow airways 587, request estimate prada
Report mach number and estimate arrival
Report present position
These is quite cool
Its a long time we use this method.
Can you help ?
Please write the callsign
Please use this
That is troublesome
This is much faster
They are coping with non-radar
I will try my best to solve it as soon as possible
This is tokyo control area center
How many mintues does it take ?
Please take the strips here
NWA31 and skyone jet 270 are near ,right ?
They are going to haneda
did you moved the planes ?
no.
That's amazing
maki, its quite tough, are you ok ?
I have to do it anyway
Kinoshita, can you come?
this flight to FL 280 and speed 280
Its dangerous here
Japan air and american should change altitude
Change
I shall tell them
c/m FL310 for delta,  airhong at FL 220
Count on you
Please be calm
janex635, request emergency landing
At this time ?
635, roger, standby
635 has engine trouble
Please adivse aiport for divert
I will contact ATM
Please take it carefully
should we tell this to other sector?
I shall
635 is in emerengecy, would land to land , can you give us a direct route for that ?
Let the a/c c/m FL 170
Jsky is at Fl360
Jsky did not contact us in 10 mins
so let's Airnippon 170, c/ mFL 290
We can give departing a/c with direct route
Thank you
Let me try to retrive the security
you did it ?
if I am not wrong
AAL025 turn right heading 110 for spacing
No problem now
Yuki
understood
The system have recoverd, all station please verify your targets
PLease re-identify your a/c before givng  instruction
Yes
You did it
I have change the login policy and password
it should be fine
You are really cool to have  such a skill
What is it ?
What are you doing ?
I am trying to confirm whether my deicsion is right
yuki,  ATM is prepared for the handoff
Everyone, stop your work now
We will handoff all traffic to ATM
Cheer for your hardwork
Now I announce the tokyo control area center to be shutdown
Due to the indicent, please rest for a while until further advice
I would conduct a individual interview later on
Have you found it ?
Manager, shall we return ?
yuki, count on you..
Yamada, you have my piece on your hand
sorry
thank you
cheer for hardwork
yes ?
Yuki, please come with kimuro kun
I will come back soon
Thank you
there is a little touble here
I will try my best to return
Please wait for a while
Is sister there ?
I am sorry
There is an incident here
I will be returning home late.
Is it ok ?
I want to talk to Umi,
Can i have dinner with umi sometime ?
sorry
What is it ?
The system seems to have some problem, i would like you to come with me
What do you have ?
I have found the hacker
The hacker used overseas server to bypass its original location
It is using tokyo control room as the bypass server
I think they made the control room to look choas
Do you mean that the criminal is someone else ?
Yes.
were you able to tracked it ?
I can track anything
Here
We have just found it the hacker located is not from here
where is it from ?
We do not know yet
it is confidently to be confirm its not from here
are we going to continue service ?
yes
Please return to your sector
Understood
What were you trying to say to the board ?
nothing
You were cool
That does not matter
just return to your place
sorry
Takashi, don't tell what you found to others
It may be the problem of your notebook
Its great that there was no tragic incident occured
Who are you really are ?
I am hacker that fights with the cracker
I lose
Cheers for hardwork
I just remembered we went on hiking before
kimura kun
yes ?
Its about yuki kun
8 years ago about umi being expelled from aviation department
I think there is a misunderstanding
Yuki did not suggest to the board to fire Umi
The board gave harsh punishment to umi but yuki tried to protected her
Umi is at her limits as an Air traffic controller
She might be in a poor health condition
But this should be our responsibility
She is still young and yet to be a great ATC
Please don't punish her, at least let her rest for a while
Please
Its a lie
I heard that he said to the board to fire umi
It was true to give umi a long break
Yuki kun noticed that umi is not suitable to work as an ATC for a while
that long holiday may grow rumours that she is fired
As I know Yuki, he did not said such things
Yuki is a person that won't save people that isn't worth
I do not fully understands him
why does he need to protect her ?
He did not thought of protecting her
if there is misunderstanding, i suggest you ask him in person
Kimura, shall we hike on mountain again
just joking
its was great...
sorry
see you
Returning ?
Are you still angry about me because of Umi's incident ?
yes
I am sorry for her
Sorry that I did not protect your girlfriend
I am sorry
I did not want to see you bowing to me like this
please stop it
I don't want to see this
I was there also
I shall have repsonsiblity
You have the responsibility
I was fortune.
As she is with me
I will take care of her
Kimuro
I am leaving
Can you tell me something
why did you lie at that time ?
I thought you would believe in me..
I am sorry, it should be me apologising
Its must be painful
She is on rehabiliation, it may be time consuming
she hope to return
she is working hard to stive for that dream
can you help ?
yes
It was great to return here
I shall visit  again at another time
shall we play basetime sometime ?
Do you know what is Air traffic controller technicians are all about ?
In air traffic ontroller, technicians are the supporting staff
Their mission is to ensure the system is working for the sake of safety
It is a job to keep constant monitor and ensure the system are of high reliability
It is important to make sure system are always on, and we should make small corrections immediately if error is found
The information are required to be done immediately for the safe of air safety
The information are also shared in a real time manner
One of the important job is to maintain the radar screen ATC are using
This is the computer room
This is the Controller radar screen interface that ATC  are using.
This screen reflects what the ATC see, so, when there is trouble reported by ATC,
we can see the changes immediately and take appropriate actions
We would try to fix the problem here and if not we go to their room to do it instead
We have a commitment that we have to make sure the ATC service should
be able to be continued even of system failure
Our job nature is.
from maintainence to management
When there is error reported from ATC, we would go to the scene and fix the problem
It is also a must to make sure the maintaining process will not affect the flight safety
We have to ensure we understand their worries and take appropriate actions to fix the problem
Despite the highly dedicated system we use, they are not perfect
It is ofcourse, human wo take final decisions