This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
do you know what is Air Traffic controller is all about ?
There are at least 600 flights each day in japan
They are separated with just 2 mins in peak hours.
As you see in the radar, There are alot of traffic in the airspace
despite of the business, Japan has been said to be the most safetest airport in the world
in order to maintain safety when fly into the busy and narrow airspace in Japan,
There is a need for someone to give precise instruction to the pilot
That person is Air Traffic Controller.
This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
EP01 -Tokyo Control
What is it ?
You can't sleep ?
I am afraid.
um, Don't worry, It'll be alright
ANA1005, turn right hdg 310 for spacing
Why did you vector away that aircraft ?
ANA1005, right hdg 310
Clear Air Turbulance is in effect
Why did you know about it, did you received Pilot reports ?
Descend and maintain FL 250
EP01
From today, you are not on simulation,
if you have mistake on the instruction, you are risking real lives on board.
Are you really ok
I am little nervous
nervous ?
So , Let's return, An Air Traffic Controller (ATC) cannot work like this
It's ok, I can do it
Joking, you don't want to repeat the training, right ?
Relax...
Yokayama San,
This is The new guy- Yamada
It is rest period now, This is Takashi.
You are doing the On the Job Training(OJT) today?
Don't get too exicited ? TBC
add oil.
this way
12 miles North of ..  expect radar vectors .. Report Clear of weather
There is a bad weather forcast
Full-Time ?
Yamada San, is there bad weather ?
There seems to be turbulance on enroute.
All flights are subjected to deviation , which leads to conjested traffic. Really busy here
COA113, Tokyo Control Roger ,Climb and maintain FL 280
Matsumoto san, The callsign isn't 113, should be 103.
COA103, Tokyo Control Roger ,Climb and maintain FL 280
Narita airport reported that Thunderstrom is observed, take off and landing is in limited operation.
understood,In Kyusyu, weather is not good, and conjested
How about kantou region, also crowded ?
At this situtaiton , its hard to make arrangement.
Please take a look on South of Kanto Sector
Roger
Emergency .. declared at 1140,  Divert to ...
Are you OK ? .. Yes.
Air america 281 declared emergency due to low fuel , I will give prioirty to that aircraft
Where is it going to land
Flight planned to Narita-RJAA, but request Centrair-RJGG due to bad weather
hey, Saitou,
We have reiceved reports from Air traffic Managment (ATM) that training area is closed.
Outa san went to rest period
Matsumoto , said he's ok, but it should be...
We don't have enough staff, thus...
Today's is Yamada's On the Job Training,
Oh,really, its today ?
The airspace is crowded today, let him monitor the traffic instead.
I 'm sorry, could you get out of the way?
Don't just stand there, you are blocking the way
Observe and learn something from it
American 153, descend and maintain FL 250, deviation heading 080 is approved.
American 153, descend and maintain FL 250
Allnippon 114, Turn right heading 110 for spacing.
Virgin 901, climb and maintain FL 380, recleared direct to Webber
shifts ?
You are late.
Why is it you ?
I need to help.
From who ?
Yamada san, The New ATC that will be joining us tomorrow.
Its ok for him to monitor, right ?
I am Yamada
Wait... I am busy here.
Delta 129, Go ahead.
Tokyo Control, Asian express 159, Request normal speed due to ,,,
Shutup
I cannot hear the pilots request
Yamda, I have something for you.
American129, delcared emergency  divert to chubu (centraiar)from haneda.
Nature of emergency ?
Heart attack patient.
Emergency procedure ( CPR) is done but required to land asap.
kinoshita kun, Can  you handle this and South sector
ok.
That plane over there, point out to next controller and handoff.
Don't ask.
I have something to tell you
I am yuki
Fly heading 290 for vector to chuubu
heading 290, United 87
Maki, time to rest.
I will be done, wait for a while
no, you haven't been resting since this morning , right ?
Go and have your meal,
I am suzuki maaki, pleased to meet you.
I am Yamada makoto ,pleased to meet you too.
matsumoto san, its dangerous here.
Here and there, you must do something.
Let me take over?
SkyJapan 358, turn right heading 310
right heading 310, skyJapan 358
Oriental 776, descend and matain FL 250.
descend and maintain FL 250, Oriental 776
SkyJapan 358
Traffic 10 o'clock, 5 miles , crossing left to right , descending to FL 250, leaving FL 260.
Sky Japan 258, looking out.
Oriental 776,
Traffic 1 o'clock, 5 nm crossing right to left, FL 260
Oriental 776, in cloud, negative contact.
they may not make it.
Skyjapan 358, Resume own nav, dct KEC  (kushimoto VOR), break break2
Clear of traffic, Climb and maintain FL 260.
I will changing shift for you.
Please take over the reamining traffic
Is there anyone free ?
Can you rest later ?, shifts starts now.
its working shifts, what are you hesitating ?
Politics don't change, ey ?
cheers for good work- otsukaresamadeshita
You have shifts from evening ?
After that I have baseball competition
Matsumoto, seems to be having a hardtime.
Good to have maki to save him.
But i have to report it to the boards
or else, I would be questioned by the boards
Hope that never happen again
I have book the baseball field
11 in the morning the day after tomorrow, oh great thanks.
Who is the opponent?
The Colleagues from the National Transport Department in Japan
We cannot lose this time.
Thanks for this
Please take care of Yamada from tomorrow,
Can you play catch call pose in base ball ?
Yes but..... That's a yes, right ?
I was in the baseball team when I was in secondary school...
Is that related to ATC?
Yamada, the catcher, what a nice name
Yes, it is.
note:Resignation Letter
I would like to apologise for the trouble that I have caused.
Is he really resigning ?
I will convince him to stay
Don't do extra things, just leave him alone.
Matsumoto Kun
its ok to have controlling mistakes, we're just human.
You should be feeling better tomorrow.
Thanks for everything you have done to me.
After compling these data , we will have to submit these reports
Is there anything you would like to add ?
please keep in mind,There is a low air pressure is blowing,
Ah, I almost forget, the new guy.
Today, we have a new ATC with us, .,, What's your name again ?
I'm Yamada.. ah yes Yamada.
Today, Yamada kun will be starting his first On the job training.
Don't you think you are trying to mock the new ATC ?
Let's make around of applause to welcome the new guy.
Becareful..
Who will be my mentor ?
Maki, please take over the OJT of Yamada.
I have not heard of this .
Maki have been trained overseas.
She have a seasoned skills in controlling
I think you would learn a lot from her
Leave it to me.
You are assigned to Kanto South A Sector
Is it alright to let Maki to handle it ?
There were many rumors happened before.
I think she will be fine.
Pleased to meet you.
yes..
Japanair1483 290 turn right heading 290, climb and maintain FL 260.
Japan 1483, right 290, climb and maintain FL 260.
Maki san you are shifting here?   yes.
I'm Nakajima, Nice to mee you.
The runways in kanto area is closed in here.
Please don't make her mad, it would be a disaster.
So, don't be the one falling behind.
Why do you have to lie ? Go to the resting area.
The punishment of God ? .. it a joke obvious.
Please sit down.
You are really falling into the punishment of god ( pilots are waiting for ATC)
Will he be ok, Its his first time.
If he don't try , he will never be able to.
Tokyo Control ANA52, Request Descend.
ANA52, Descend and Maintain FL 230
ANA52 , roger, descend and Maintain FL 230
continue
Japanair 315, leaving 1200ft, for FL180
Where is it ?
Take a deep breathe.
Here is Japanair.
Japanair 315,Tokyo control roger,
How high to ascend ?
FL220
Japanair 315, Climb and maintain FL 220
Moreover, until climbing to FL280,
Japanair 315, fly heading 270 for spacing.
You don't have time to panic, right ?
Input changes
Tokyo Control, ANA 903, climbing FL380....DAL293, tokyo control, how do you read..
Where are the traffics ?
Here, here and here.
You have to consider also traffic ( aircraft) from other sector
The target here is too close
speed adjustment is required here
Vector this traffic to the left for spacing.
Handoff this traffic to the next sector.
single 48, request descend.
Single 48 ,standby ( = wait for a while)
You must juggle with speed and altitude separation.
Single 48, turn right heading 110 for spacing, descend and maintain FL190
Its useless to just apologise.
Accidents are a result of not giving pilots the correct instruction.
Don't get nervous.
Let me take over.
jaysky674 , turn right heading 230 and descend and maintain FL 260
I am sorry for the incoveince that caused
Maki san, here is your coffee.
I went to a rest, too bad i did not saw your controlling.
I know there is a great place to eat tonight.
Although its a tiring that ,but its good to go and eat at sometime.
I would rather sharpen my air traffic controlling skills.
How is the new guy ?
Um... well it reminds me that it was long ago that I was once a trainnee.
in order to be a great controller like you , i have learnt a lot from you, masaki san.
it is not great at all, its busy all the time.
Your stamina and effectiveness is also important in working overseas, so i came back to japan
As a civil servant in japan is differnt. its better
Its much harsh, with less rest and effectiveness is a must in overseas controlling
I want to go to overseas, too.
Your english accent is odd, and difficult to be heard.
I was said that my accent are easily understood.
I am Shikijima Nice to meet you.
I am Yamada, pleased to meet you.
Weren't you nervous ?
I was sure who am I talking to, sometimes loss track of their position.
I also did not know it when i first control
That is not very good.
I am giving out something
This is the new trainee, Yamada
I am sorry, its ok ..
What's the matter with him ?
This is because the incident about baseball  lastime,
Did you know shinomura San ?
He was the team leader in the baseball team during high school.
He actually did not know how to play baseball ,but was assigned as the catcher
Why is it ?
Because they can make fun of him.
Isn't time for your shift ?
oh yea. see ya.
Really, I really want to buy it..s
The chracter was perfect.
I am yamada
What is it ?
Star striek, you don't know ?
speaking,
I am resting, please don't talk to me.
There are peoples with different personalities.
Let's work hard.
Speed adjustment.
Allnippon 35, reduce speed  to 300 knots;
Allnippon 35, correction, reduce speed to 270 knots for spacing
ANA35, rgr, reduce speed to 270 knots.
If you don't speed up Japanair, it will converge with AirAmerica within 5 mins.
Japanair 726, descend and maintain FL 250
Not here, should be there !
Asiaair324, descend and maintain ... this is 25,000
Yamada, get out.
Asianair324 descend and maintain FL 270,
Airamerica 87, climb and maintian FL..
Cheers for the good work  (sarcisim)
how was it ?
The trainee ? Your teaching method sucks..
Any thing wrong with him ?
He doesn't have sense, he is stll nervous.
That's way (masaki) is a strict mentor
But I have lecture him in a peaceful way.
It you let down your guard, that is not a good ATC practice.
And it is easy to have accidents due to carelessness.
Are you free now ?
How could I be free and nothing to do ?
I shall take care of Yamada san next time.
Don't worry much , its your first time ,right ?
Try hard again tomorrow.
Yamada kun, remeber the baseball tomorrow?
Did you think this is an easy job ?
no..
It's just that when I am giving instruction to pilots and thiking about passengers on board,
I feel the fear.
If you want to leave, i suggest you do it now.
There is more than afraid you can do.
maki have been being nice when mentoring you., right ?
If I were her, I would ask you to get out immediately,
ATC are not a job for those who just want to play around with aircraft
If you want to quit, send me a resignation letter , I will approve it tomorrow immediately.
Excuse me,
Cheer for the hardwork ( respective)
In order to be a great ATC, please strictly mentor me tomorrow.
American 187, contact tokyo control  133.6
very sleepy here.
I think i am not suitable to be a mentor.
Hope that the bad personality will not affect the growth of yamada.
Do you want me to punch you ?
Its time to rest
Have you seen this ?
Title- My Film,   Thanks I' not interested.
it shouldbe hara san's right ?
You have heard about it ?
I heard that he went to a funeral of a deaceased cousin
But that person always tells lies.
Harai san wrote something on the movie magazine page,
he have been writing a lot of movie reivews.
author - hara- butta ?
What is this old-fashioned name ?
Why did she not sleep at home ?
Matsumoto, sorry to call you up this early morning.
I heard from yuki san that the resignation process is not yet approved,
Please come back.
Please at contact me .
Is Matsumoto san the one...
He is in the same period in terms of ATC training
Despite the depature of matsumoto san
But still , we are in the same team.
now, I am left alone
ATC team is like a family
He is like my brother.
May be its only my interpretation
You are playing baseball now ?
That's great
There is a traffic jam due to trian accident which made late, do you know how many ppl is involved?
That is really tiring.
I have just received notice that due to an incident in chuubu, flight to from chuubu are all suspended.
Where are you going ?
don't you remeber about baseball?
I did not prepare anything for the game.
No worries, all you need is there, what I need is a person that can catch and strike the ball.
But, I am not good about that.
You will be going , anyway, right ?!
Yes sir .
something bad has happened.
There is an volcano eruption. near mount itou
I am now in the area of volcano eruption in ITOU
Approximately at 5:55pm there volcano eruption detected in mount itou
Can you help ?  ofcourse, there is not enough staff, right ?
That is great.
Report from the observatory.
It is not good to have Visibitlity of 3 km
A lot of traffic may need to be put on hold.
Volcanic ash may affect flight safety.
understood.
I received order from ATM, that restriction are put in departure aricrafts.
Maki,  the volcanoic ash are spreading into 60,000
There may be possiblity that volcanoic ash will be spread to handea and narita.
Flights within radius of 25 miles of the eruption site may requets divertion due to the ashes, report to me as required.
There are restriction put on departure traffic, thus there might not be enough parking bays on the ground.
Whether to hold the aircraft or allow approach will be subjected to our decision.
Cyuubu is closed ,we would contact the nearest airport avaiable for divert.
For any other information, please do report.
maki, sorry, can you stay for a way to help us ?
We need someone to compile the flight plans for the diverted flights.
Please do report if needed.
Volcanoic ash ey ? I know about it but first time to see it happen.
If the vocalnoic ash enters the engine, it may cause engine overheat,
and in the worst case, engine surge ( engine shutdown) may occur.
If that happends, that would be an emergency
Due to the effect of volcanoic ash, at time 2300z, runway of haneda wil lbe closed.
Please divert traffic that  heading to narita/ haneda such that they are 5 miles from A1 airways
um closing within 10 mins ..
Contact Tokyo Approach 119.1
Are you on-duty today ?
no, I came to collect my stuff.
Are you sure to resign from ATC ?
You were afriad, right ?
ATC, isn't a job that is suitable for you ?
You won't understand about it.
I think you are also in a difficult time.
If you stay here, your mental state would be tortued.
I am.. enjoying it.
Althought I am not yet perfect, but I enjoy it.
you just came in as a trainee, you won't undrestand me.
No, I do not understand your feelings.
I have heard from butsu den
You have a great friend that count on you
but , you have chosen to escape...
To me, I would not undrestand ,
I am returning to my workplace.
Cleaning up your locker ?
I have done a reserach on the (near miss) incident last time,
Knowing that its was not the fault of your instructions
they found that it was the pilot's fault that fly in the wrong altitude before you have insruct them.
So, please don't be guilty, it was not your fault.
I shall not mock you now, as we are lacking staff
but..
We have to go back now.
The aircraft that are affected by volcanoic ash are in verfication
Hamamatsu aiport's runway is close due to the effect volcanoic ash.
by, the way, your outfit is strange.
I know.
The winds are really blowing quickly
it should be time that the capacity of narita and haneda are reaching its limits.
I have told that there is not enough spot in the aerodrome
If spots are not enough, than let the aircraft hold on the taxiway.
This is emergency, please report this to ATM,
Concentrate on your work , everyone
Matusmoto, come and handle the double approach to help masaki.
Maki san, I shall conduct the double approach.
Beal999, climb and maintain FL 240,
Centracargo 8528, declare emergency
We have engine failure
Roger, request your intention
Allow me to speak in japanese, when able report your status.
Just while ago, we have flewthe near MJE ( miyakejima), and suspect failure due to volcanoic ash
We also have engine 2  and 3 that has shutdown.
We are planning to return to handea
masaki San, the aircraft's altitude is descending rapidly.
We have an a/c that declared emergency and is rapdily descending.
We have been trying just while ago.
We cannot confirm the number of affected a/c
Please open up the training airsapce to make space for the congested traffic
That is why we are saying it is important
There are no emergency from maki. One is emergency descent, another one has volcanoic ash in engines.
I shall report these to the boards.
centracargo , may not make it to haneda due to performance, ok keep me posted.
This is not good.
The a/c that is related to the ashes reported engine no. 2,3 are shutdowned
There are a lot of taxiway in narita and handeda
But the spread of ashes made the two airports inoperational.
narita has closed down the runways, and haneda will close down the runways after one arrival.
After collaboration from Approach, only one emergency is allowed to approach haneda.
I gave centracargo the prioirty, no.. give it to rainbow air
Centracargo declared emergency at the first place.
Centracargo are just full of goods, and can land anywhere
Whoever delcare the emergency, they have the prioirty
But, rainbow is a passenger and this make it the reason to have the first priority
You are giving up lives even though there are only 2  in cargo flight ?
How are you going to expect we transport the passenger if they are far from the departure airport ?
its better to let 2 pilots sacrfice than 265 passengers.
I cannot accept this order.
The decision has been made.
Don't ask, just follow my order!
I have recieved notice that rainbow has safely landed in handea
Centraair 8528,
The fourth engine has shutdown, and we are losing altitude.
Leaving with one engine it would be difficult for us.
The engine are not in our control
We decide to divert to chuubu
Due to the effect of volcanoic ashes acitivies, microbust are reported in all runways and are closed.
How about landing in komaki
No..  if they can't make it, they may crash into the sea.
After deliberate consideration, we decide to go to chuubu.
understood.
As I have mentioned, microburst in all runways of centraair, safety is not assured if landing in there.
We understood.
We will try our best
We will make arrangement for you.
Takajima, contact centraair
saito, crashing may occur in vincinity of chuubu, please contact ATM and prepare for the worst.
um. it seems to be the only way..
If it is due to volcanoic ash , all engine should shutdown due to overheat
According to the altittude FL 230
How about shutdown the engine one and try to restart all lthe engines?
it would not be a good practice for ATC to instruct pilot to shut their engines.
There are exception for restarting engines
If they are going to chuubu, their speed are not fast enough and its too far away.
If you fail, they will fall onto the sea
Tell me what to do then
You want me to wait and see the target to disappear form the radar scope ?
Operations are in your command,
The one who speaks to the pilot is -- me
Aren't Our job is to assist pilots and try our very best ?
Centraair8528
After consulting my co-pilot
We have decided to shutdown engine number 1 to prevent overeat and restart all engine after cooling
Understood.
They are not able to reach chuubu ,if they don't get their engine starting.
Are you able to make turns
All engines are off, electronics are in limited service,
It will be difiicult as it will be a non-gyro , ( no navigation display) but we will try
understood
It would be fine?
We have received reports that Thunderstorm is enforced near chuubu.
We will descend to FL150 and try to restart our engines.
undterstood
We bet on this restart of engine will work.
Engine one and four came alive, and we are able to ascend.
Centrecargo 8528, turn right heading 290
understood.
Matsumoto kun, take my position
You must continue on your shift.
I have reached my limits, I can't handle much traffic for today
I am counting on you for the remaining traffic
Please change shifts with me and be an " air traffic controller"
Centracargo, Tokyo control, tell me your status
We are at 20,000ft and there is thunderstorm
I shall give you more information later.
Don't stop the engine..
Centracargo 8528,  report your status
We have all of our engines shutdown, with unknown reasons, are we safe in this altitude.
You are safe, there no traffic around you, do not worry
If you need help ,please contact us
Please confirm the airport information in chuubu
The airport in chuubu are ready to accept the emergency aircraft
Why is the plane not contacting me ?
It is critial moment for them.
It should be time ..
Centraaircargo 8528., resume of navigation, direct to chuubu.
Undrestood
Centracargo 8528, contact centrair approach 119.17
Good way, afterward, let approach deal with it
PLease promise me that you land safely and return on the ground one piece,good day
Tokyo control, thank you We shall return safely, good day
I am not that great as you think ,  I am just a coward
There is information from the airport
He did not contact chuubu ?
ey, we have instruct centraaircargo to contact you
Approach did not have radio contact with the aircraft
Centraair 8528, speak if you hear us
Nakajima, check with the approach again.
What could happen to them
it seems they have disappear ?
The radar cannot receieve the beacon signal
They might be in trouble
Centracargo, 8528, speak up if you read me
Centrcargo 8528
You did tried your best
Centraair8528, has landed safely!
Thank you very much
Even you say thank you, I have'nt done anything.
Its your job  to do you best, as an "air traffic controller", right ?
Thata's great, that the plane landed safely
I have a message from the pilot,
They thought they did not make it, but because of your encouragement, they made it.
Matsumato have revoked the resignation.
If he revoked it, he shouldn't submit it at the first place
he wanted to say something, that's why he stayed, right ?
I have thought the my decision, were wrong .. but
No.
If you have something, to say, you are more than welcome to tell me.
What I want to tell you is we you already see, plane has landed safely
The decision i made was right to protect the pilots.
I will not regret for what I have decided at that moment, but
I had one moment that felt scared.
Our very decisions will decide the fate of people's life
Which criteria should we base on to make the right deicions ?
I was thinking about the passengers's faces of the families
It would be a pity if the passengers die
Pilot also have family
Well, this would be an endless debate
Shall we bet on the next full duty of Yamada san?
What shall we bet ?
Cream, no. I do not like sweets
Well, you should know which side will win, by just looking at your face.
take care, see you
There is a missle has be launched into Sendai Area, please inform me for more info
How is the situation there ?
There are traffics from the east side are disappearing
Kinosakun change shift with Yamda kun
Please let me do it
You are not ready for non-radar controlling
please
Please let me do it
I will allow as requested
Do you know where is Tokyo control area centre locatecd
In Saitama prefecture, Near the Aviation park station
Here, there is the first invented a/c ys-11
This is where the aviation history starts
100 years ago, the tokizawa airfield has established
Now, its has been transformed into a museum,  there are various of planes being kept as display
And Here is Tokyo Control Area Centre