This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
Do you know there are rules when flying ?
Where every you go in the world, there must be a "high way"
In aviation, we call them airways, analogous to highways in lamen terms
All aircraft in japan fly from and to this predefined route- airways to ensure safety
TO maintain proper separation during takeoff, landing and enroute,
Air traffic controllers are there to instruct pilots on hdg, speed and alt to ensure safety.
for example a plane flying from fukoka to haneda
First the pilot contacts the atc and the aerodrome controller give clerance from ground movements to airborne
From aerdrome control, the a/c is pass to terminal control
then from terminal control is passed to the 4 major Area Control Centre
ACC uses radar facility to track the flight and guide them to their destination
The green is Fukoka Control and blue is Tokyo control area
The plane flies with the predefined route and contact fukuoka control then tokyo control
The plane is then transfer to the terminal control of haneda for landing
The ATC uses radar to maitain separation is called Air Traffic Control
In the world, Air traffic Control has a variety of complex rules and system
Because of These sets of rules and Air traffic controllers strive to separate traffic made flying in the air safe
Do you know there is a school specialied for Air traffic controller ?
it is located in Oosakim isumi city, the aeronautical safety college
it is different from other college, because  it is directly under provision of tokyo control.
There are students who wanted to be an air traffic controller, aviation technician.
here is where they have theorectical and practical lessons
Koreanair721
The system they used in simulation are the system that also used in the real world.
After few years of training, they will be the one who protect the sky of japan.
In the enroute, charts, we have approved Fl280-Fl410, and deviation may also occur due to weather
Please not of our normal operating procedure and training is enforced as usual.
My report is done , anyone have something to add ?
I have returned from the investigation, please to work with you guys again.
Let's go.
Cheers for the hardwork
anything you have in hand ?
no, not quite.
I really have the case is solved as soon as possible.
I was thinking if  out technician can keep track of the hacker's location.
Have you heard of Saito san..
Yes.
She requested for change of position.
She finally got what she wnat to transfer in Fukuoka.
Oh i see.
That would be lonely for us.
Yes.
How are you , are you a bit tired ?
No.
Maki.
Are you okay ?
What is it about ?
Just asking.
ANA232, 124
ANA215, tokyo control roger, maintain FL 280
maki san , ANA215,
Maki san.
Yes ?
ANA215 ..
where?
here .
Should we vector him to here for spacing ?
Yes.
ANA215, turn right heading 090 for spacing.
That's good.
Saito san will not be coming today ?
I think she is in the ceremony for changing position to fukuoka.
its quite boring without that "harsh" women around.
I thought you do not like her around.
Am I that bad ?
I do not know.
Have you watched the the latest start shriek ?
no.
that's why
why are you that angry.
I am sorry.
The enteprise commerical video is something like this.
Do you understand ?
Here you are.
Too hot.
delicious..
I know everyone must be tired, i added some more beans to make it smell good.
The good smell can let you relax.
You are right.
There is nothing special here.
shikishima...
I do not know.
Yes ?
Would you like some coffee ?
I just came to get my cell phone.
The 8 years old girl who was inANL flight emergency landed in hachijyojima, is still in coma
If the incident was coped ealier , this would have saved the child from coma.
There is hospital in hachijyojima, but its not fully functional
If the instruments are faulty, the fuel should not be remaining that much also.
taking the worse condition, landing at hachijyojima would be the best choice.
ANL167 has landed safety
But the hopstial have told us the child is unconscious
Tokyo control roger, maintain FL 370
That is great, it must be the good training of Maki.
Let's get rest, please ask for shift from another.
What do you want to tell me ?
Actually nothing, I am sorry.
maki, where are you going ?
I want some fresh air outside.
Yuki San,
is maki still worrying about the incident of ANL ?
Why do you ask ?
She did not control today.
It was the first time when OJT, she lost her attention.
isn't because you are okay to be on solo, thus she let go, right ?
I always felt the same was as Yamada.
Well, women has lots in their mind, including worries of men.
I did not ask for that.
Well, let you 2 handsome guys follow up the case then.
Handsome ?
What should I do if Maki has a boyfriend ?
You really can imagine things.
Please stop mocking me.
It is hard to graps the heart of a girl.
right, yamada ? shall we go together?
ok.
Cheers for hardwork.
Have you watch the news ?
What happened ?
There was a divertion traffic this morning.
But she did not did well, she must be worried about that incident.
I hope she is fine but.
You will be the last one, here, right ?
so i will leave first.
Ep08
let's invite saito to say the last words before she leave.
Although it will be lonely to leave tokyo control.
To work in ATM is my dream for a long time.
Its really a relive for me to have my dream come true
I know i may have problems or fights between you
please forgive my bad acts.
But this does not mean to say goodbye forever,
I can still hear your voices when you contact ATM
Let's work hard to ensure air safety of japan as an Air traffic controller.
Saito.. I will be lonely.
No..
Thank you for words during OJt.
Please be a great ATC
Thank you.
Add oil.
Cheers for hardword,
You can handle it,
please come and play in fukuoka sometime.
Why did you not say goodbye to me ?
Cheers for hardwork.
Thank you.
Saito san.
No., That is too much.
Thank you.
Please come and visit us sometime.
With you daugter ?
I will be returning to work.
Please take care.
I will return after clearing my locker
I will give you a call after I have arrived Fukuoka.
Its still lonely afterall.
Thank you.
You can change shifts.
Isn't because of bad health..
How is yokohama san ?
he seems to be famous in the village.
People say his coffee is delicious.
He thank shikijima for the techniques also.
That's great.
Yuki san, please look this after work.
I will be returning.
What would it be.
yes ?
you don't know ?
Crush ban ?
JAL73 d/m FL 250
Maki san, can you change shift with me.
The departure from handea are retricted.
There should be reduced traffic.
Are you ok ?
understood
Tokyo control, DAL554,  we delcare medical emergency ,  request divert to haneda airport.
DAL554,
Tokyo control, DAL554, request descent.
AMU886, request FL360
Aircraft are calling you.
I know.
Maki.
the aicraft are calling you.
I am ok.
Give instructions now.
I know
AMU886, c/m FL360
ANA308, c/m  FL 260, turn right heading 270
DAL554, d/m FL 230
Don't do extra things for me.
if I don't do extra thing, why would you not give instructions ?
If you cannot do it, just go home and rest.
I am fine.
I did not sleept well, I should be fine.
You can go home and rest today,
What are you talking about ?
I said you can return home.
I am ok
no..
You should know yourself,
i will give you a day off today.
I heard Maki just returned, is there anything happened ?
she is not feeling well.
I let her off
Is it related to that incident ?
May be.
I have suggest her to return home for some rest
if she returned, please take her off radar control.
Ok.
Maki is a human being afterall.
I don't think that is a nice way of saying her like that
I am not bad mouthing her.
I was surprised.
She must be still worried about the incident happened recently.
I am not sure.
If it is the wish of herself. we should respect it.
The new has reported ...
It would be good if she did not saw the news report.
If she is really worried about that incident, should be clean up this room?
Let's remove all the newpaper.
Yes.
Let's make the TV inoperative.
shikijima, please coordinate with other team.
Cheers for hardwork,
what are you doing ?
before maki returns, we hope to clean up this room.
Hope that no information about the incident can come to her mind.
We are trying to inhibit her to switch to the news channel.
Its really difficult to move this thing.
How about removing the batteries ?
See, if you remove the battery, you can still operate the tv by pressing buttons here
We did not ask suggestions from a trainnee
Are you trying to say I am just wasting my time ?
No.
How about I bring home this TV ?
Please stop that.
Let's just use the TV at the least.
Yamada, please help.
hey, go and help.
Good morning,
you look energetic
can you be at my pose,  i will be busy in meetings.
Ok.
We have a new member uwekisa
I have been on a rest for something and now assigned to work in tokyo control
I have a long time no working but pleased to work with you.
The mentor will be oota.
Let's go.
Yuki, I am sorry that my husband had caused you troubles.
No,..
It is really great to work with you again in tokyo control ever since that incident.
Yea.
I'll go back to work.
Excuse me, can you come over please ?
I will go there.
Can I go for rest ?
Sure.
JAL148, c/m FL260, turn right heading 290
Yuki,
Its great to have eweki back with us.
That is great.
Yuki san,
I have the informaiton for the vistion of our center from pilot.
I am sorry, after saito left, I have been asking you to help.
I am strong men and can work as you command.
Great.
Is Maki fine ?
are you worried as a boyfriend ?
Please don't mocking me.
is she on rest , I did not see her outside
Cheers for hardwork.
its  a long time ever since my last control.
There are a lot of deviation.
I hope that everything is fine.
Its sure to be fine.
You have done a great job.
Maki san,  We are planning to visting yokohama's cafe shop,
no thanks.
Hey, lets go..
It may be great to change your mood.
Mood ?
I am the one who need to change my mood ?
No,
HOw many years have you been working ?
2 years,
that's is why always make mistake and being scould all the times.
maki san.
Are you okay,
I thought that she would come .
Forget about it.
Let's go together.
Cheers for hardwork.
Suzuki San, yokohama san is wanted to see you, can you come and join us this time ?
Thank you.
Yuki, please, I want to help..
I would like to discuss about the pilot vistation of tokyo control, today and next week.
We have arranged people to bring them around during the visit.
Hara, you would wear suit, during their visitation, right ?
I don't think that is a good idea, he will make something weird again.
I will prepare it.
But, why did you not wear it today ?
I have allergy to suits.
I think its better to work at the outfit.
So, there will be 2 pilots visting our control center this afternoon.
There will be also simulation training for our new atc training.
Nakajima san, don't think its a date .
Its not ?
The OJT for the new ATC will be conducted next week, please be prepared, thank you.
This is the briefing room.
The control room is this way.
You are scheduled to visit there next week, do you want to see it today ?
Yes, please
The briefing room is quite old, it started 8 yesr ago.
The machines we have been using are of the latest technology.
Really
Haha..
The attire seems to be..
He is special, he does things freely
What is the position in there ?
It is the manager of the Area center
All the communication between ATM and coordinate with other sectors
She is like in the heart of the control
She quite cool.
Let's go to the simulation room.
I have a request.
Maki san, there is a handsome pilot looking for you.
Its not it..
Go back to your position
I will go for toilet
Can you do something with Hara's attire ?
That is too much.
Sorry, he wanted to visit here
Its ok.
Please.
You know her ?
I am the pilot in charge when she visit the cockpit training.
Aren't you controlling today ?
She is now working as the manager today.
That is a pity,
I wanted to  see how you control
I wanted to see how strong were you , when you said come and visit us in the control centre
I am sorry.
The simulation demonstration will be starting, we should be going.
Sorry for bothering you.
Excuse me.
I have similar expeirence like you
The a/c was identifiable, how could they run on Conflict.
Sorry, please stop it.
I am fine.
But I think the one who suffer is you.
although I could not protect you but at least I understand you, as an ATC
If you need me, just let me know
How did you get over with it ?
I have someone that support me wholeheartedly.
Whatever I do or whoever say o me, he supported me and be with me.
I..
You must have.
Friends here, care a lot for you.
You must know the answer.
Can I sit next to you ?
I was surprise when I came here.
I am ashamed of myself when I say ATC don't know about aeroplanes.
After your cockpit training, I have change my way of thinking
I really respect ATC
Suzuki San,
Work hard,
I hope to hear your voice in the sky again.
I shall leave now.
Maki san, The child have recover from coma.
Maksi san,
Thanks for the words during training, which now , I could control  calmly
We are all waiting for the energetic Maki.
I am sorry for doing this for you.
Please scould me again!!
From Yamada.
That is really childish
Maki
Please be on the Kanto South sector
Yes
Let's change shift
Thank you.
Pacific 433, tokyo control, maintain FL 370
020, c/m FL 130