This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
Do you know there are rules when flying ?
Where every you go in the world, there must be a "high way"
In aviation, we call them airways, analogous to highways in lamen terms
All aircraft in japan fly from and to this predefined route- airways to ensure safety
TO maintain proper separation during takeoff, landing and enroute,
Air traffic controllers are there to instruct pilots on hdg, speed and alt to ensure safety.
for example a plane flying from fukoka to haneda
First the pilot contacts the atc and the aerodrome controller give clerance from ground movements to airborne
From aerdrome control, the a/c is pass to terminal control
then from terminal control is passed to the 4 major Area Control Centre
ACC uses radar facility to track the flight and guide them to their destination
The green is Fukoka Control and blue is Tokyo control area
The plane flies with the predefined route and contact fukuoka control then tokyo control
The plane is then transfer to the terminal control of haneda for landing
The ATC uses radar to maitain separation is called Air Traffic Control
In the world, Air traffic Control has a variety of complex rules and system
Because of These sets of rules and Air traffic controllers strive to separate traffic made flying in the air safe
Was there a scrabblem request ? please confirm it.
Where is Rondo ?
Rondo .. ?
He should be heading to Kansai airport, but he descended withou request.
How about you get into Kantou south sector ?
There is sort of a/c or thing that is following that a/c
Its better to get all the planes down, it might be a hijack.
EP09
(3 days before the incident)
What ever it is ..
i want to have a date with you.
I just came back from america, I am definitely going.
If I have time I will come..
You always say that but...
Did you remember how similar am I to my mother ?
But I want you to learn to be independent.
That cruel.
Its should be time to go, I'll contact you when you arrived.
Please give send me an email when you arrived.
Sure, see you.
Where is she going, that is your daughter , right ?
She is going to america
It is her holiday from school.
She seems to be very active.
Its better you spend time with here
but you know as an ATC, we have limited time.
Right..
JAL53, rgr, d/m FL 220
ANA328, fly hdg 110  for arrival spacing,  reduce speed to 270 knots
DAL12, rgr, d/m FL280
tokyo control , coa726, FL350
coa726, tokyo control ,rgr, c/m FL 370
You are really getting good with this.
you should be ready for the test.
Thank you
Matsumoto, please point out this to mika.
Look ahead
Please concentrat
Tokyo  control, JAL34, request descent.
JAL34, d/m FL260
ee.
What is it ?
The training area seems to be difference.
Should we confirm it ?
PLease ask ATM.
The charms that we gave to maki is really great
Well, yamada is the new guys, he is quite nice.
how will you cope with the incident few days ago ?
I am still thinking.
I think it is not the timing yet.
You might be put onto a long vication.
I know.
So, see you
maki san , There is a sales in shinjuku, are you coming ?
Great, when are you going ?
ee ?
When are you going ?
How about the day after tomorrow ?
Sure
Cheers for hardwork
You know what ?
Maki just said she will go shopping with me in shinjuku.
That is rare of her.
Yea..
Its my first time hanging out with her.
What is he doing ?
He said he got tickets to star striek and exited about it.
What ?
Are you trying to get my enterprise ??
Can I stop here ?
I am a loser..
SHikijima.
Shall we watch a movie later ?
Which movie ?
Jacky chan.
What kind of title is that ?
It doesn't feel like action film
The reviews are good, I'm going by the way.
I 'm not going, really ?
Really ?
!@#$%^&
Shall I come with you ?
I don't know about jacky chan, but I am interested in what film you like
Really
Let's go.
What ?
Am I smelling good ?
Do you like me ?
Well....
Its quite sudden for such a question
Cost tari ?
You have a coast tari perfume that like
I am happy,
ridiculous!
What happened ?
I said she had a good smell, of coast tari but..
And she got maid
Girls don't like boys to be too playful.
Do you know its means something else when you are talking about coffee ?
PLease feel the taste of sawaji
finally, its your rating exmination tomorrow.
You should be doing fine as I observe you today.
No, I''m not.
are you desperate ?
don't worry
Believe in yourself
Its good to appreciate yourself sometimes.
Thank you.
What  are you thinking.
I was thinking that I did not change at all
I was told by my father that I kept crying when I fell down in a racing competition in kindergartens.
my father said: nothing is impossible if I do my best.
I should gain self confidence
So I will do my best
To let me dad know I am capable
Great.
Am I getting close to what my father has done ?
entirely.
Well, there is a slight difference but
But whenever you control, it reminds me about your father.
He is always in put lives in the top priority
he was a silly man
Sorry,
I am not bad mouthing about your father.
The son of your father (yamada), had save many friends
well, not really save..
I think, even we do nothing, Maki shall stand up again.
Really.
Yes.
Maki, cheers for hard work
Suzuki, I have something to ask you
What does young lady like ?
Who are you dating ?
NO.. That is not what you are thinking.
Its my daughter.
Its my daughter's birthday.
Its better to ask Nakajima, as she is much similar age with you daughter.
Yes.
Is your daughter doing well ?
She is flying around the world.
I said to play or hang out with me sometime,
She is really cute
That is great.
Yamada kun,
do  your best for the Rating Examination tomorrow
Yes
Cheers for hardword
(two days before the incident)
Its okay to break now.
ok, thanks.
Matsumoto, what is that?
VFR at this time ?
Is that..
It disappear
I hope that is not relevant.
Should I eat this here ?
Hello ?
Shimuro.
Can you come here ?
(a day BEFORE the incident)
Its bad though .. to have such thing happened
Yes.
He may not even noticed.
He said its good to have chicken today ?
Cheers for hardwork
I wonder how is Yamada doing.
You are worried ?
He is in my team if he fails, people will point fingers to me.
I think that should be fine.
May be.
Can you bring us some fine coffee in the celebration next week ?
That's quite expensive.
Its ok to use a little bit
After Yamada San came, I have been doing great
should I say that to him.. ?
Yama, san are you trying to find chances to retire ?
well.
Please come and help tomrrow.
Cheers for hardwork.
I will need to collect your Pan-fried noodles
Ahaahahaha....
There was a box saying "Pan-fried noodles", right ?
I don't have it anymore.
ok.
Good morning.
Its seems to eat something good.
It really feels good
Why do you have so much bandages ?
You like it ?
Ouch.
What is that ?
You did not noticed that ?
When was it on ?
Sataharau said she is coming by to practice
What ?
Don't be joking.
I was the one teaching them..
Is it from the soccer team ?
Ah that is a good backbround ?
The uniform number 1...
That is annoying
(3 hours before the incident)
A continuation of the previous week, the pilots will come again to visit our area center.
There should not be anything special,
Yuki, do you have something to annouce ?
For those who have not submit the report that is due yesterday, please submit asap
Firstly, Shikijima kun, shikijima and shikijima..
I would like to apologise on behalf of shikijima kun
I  don't know who is who, what ever, please give us your proposal plan about coffee.
And Hara
Please wear a normal suit
I don't have enough money.
It because you spend it all on watching movie.
And one more thing.
Yamada,
Please report to everyone.
Yes.
I have passed that rating up examination
Thank you.
It is the result of your every support.
Thank you very much
That means Yamada can control independently without a mentor monitoring him.
Shimo, Follow up him and not OJT anymore.
Understood.
Let's workhard for today.
Yamda,  you don't have to thank me, its all credits.
Thank you.
Thank you
Congratulations,
The game has just started
Try your best!
Yes.
It is the result of your harsh training.
It is not harsh..
You...
You have such impression ?
Fine, its ok...
Yamada, that great.
Thank you.
It's great to see Yamada
It is the result of your harsh training.
I have been trying to say..
It is all of his efforts.
Its nothing to do with me.
But becareful that he much use his feelings over logical in making decision
Yuki san, is the my husband coming today
Yes, To come and dicuss with me about something
I was worrying about you ,as you have lots of things to do and may not sleep well.
Did you have anything to tell me ?
Did you know anything about it ?
A little
I was thinking to discuss it later.
Have you return to the feeling you were ?
Well, a little, thanks to the great effort of others to follow up me.
Is your daughter return tonight ?
Yes.
You really know a lot.
Do you know which flight ?
JCL776
I am in that sector I will tell you.
Its ok, its not that important
(2 hours before the incident)
Let's change shift
that is fast
Jal501, fly heading 080 for your climbing purpose c/m FL280
This is TOkyo area control centre
Can the pilot start their visitation to the control room ?
sure.
Ok.
Some system in ATM have reported to be malfunctioned.
The departured are held for release as the data for recovering required time to accomplish
Understood
(1 hour and 12 mins before the incident)
(32 mins before the incident)
I have returned
The departure has released)
What were you talking about kakashikun ?
Its about the system
You can change shift
Suzuki San
Thanks for your support.
No ,thanks.
SHimoro san, its time for break
ANA35,  turn right heading 110 for spacing.
(7 mins before incident)
This is the radar scope of current a/c in japan
That is alot of aircraft
Although I don't know which a/c I am flying but this seem like perfect
Its really different  compared to a simulator
Is it always stuffed with a/c like that ?
No, its just the peak time now.
ATC really take is easy to protect the airspace of japan
We all have vigorous training to learn how to take control of airplanes
Enjoy.
What speed is that ?
Is that a military aircraft ?
Was there a scrambble request ?
No.
Please contact ATM and confirm the case
Rainbow 203, tokyo control how do you read ?
If you read me ident
Rainbow 203 should be heading to Chubu, but it did not say anything and entered kanto south sector
Here atlantis airlines should be landing at Kansai airport, but  the a/c descend and made a turn without request.
Try to call the traffic again.
Ok.
Atlantis air 808, tokyo control , how do you read ?
What is happening ?
There is nothing reported to the ATM, we have to confirm it again.
understood.
It seems not to be a military aircraft
What is that thing flying
It is confirmed not a military aircraft
Is that another attack ?
That should not happen in japan.
It should be strange that we see that again in japan
Is that VFR ?
That may also be..
But why is it flying at this time ?
Where is Japan central heading to ?
Japan Central 776, Tokyo Control, how do you read ?
Shimira san,
Can you return to Kanto South sector and do a follow up ?
It should be fine, Yamada is doing well there.
besides, my noodles are ready.
Please.
Ok, sure.
Which aircraft did not that you cannot contact ?
This one
Rainbow 203, If you read me fly heading 270 for vector to chubu airport
It does not work.
Rainbow, will be coming to my sector, leave it ot me.
makisan, there is something here
JAPAN central was offcourse 20 miles and no response in Guard frequency (121.5)
Please contact the airline company directly
What happened?
Its just something bad.
Yuki, can you come I have something to dicuss with you .
I don't know what the problem is.
There are aircrafts in different sectors that we cannot contact
Well, its not uncommon to have it.
But ..
There are aircraft in different sectors have aircraft that cannot be contacted, and they are on holding.
Did they request anything ?
We did not heard from them.
We have tried , but they have no response.
They did not disappear from the radar, its not radar contact lost, would that be due to wind ?
It is strange to have  3 aircrafts with same situation simulatenously.
What are you trying to say ?
Its not working, handoff to the next sector.
Rainbow203, direct Rondo VOR.
Where is Rondo ?
Check again.
Rainbow 203, say again
Excuse me, did they say Rondo ?
They said rondo.
Can we hear the recordings again ?
There are a/c that are off track and cannot be contact through the radio
Its better to get all the planes on the ground.
Its hijack
hijack ?
Rondo is a password for being hi-jack
Please wait, we have rules here
If we don't verify the conversation, we cannot take actions
Which sector is that ?
Its in kinki toukai
Please verify the position of that aircraft
Please fllow me.
Tokyo control, rainbow 203 , direct rondo VOR.
This is the one.
it is a survival message from pilot
The aircraft is a different airline from yours , right ?
The password may be different
We have training for that
I have heard that before..
but.. if this is a mistake, we would be in big trouble.
Yuki san,
rainbow was bound for chubu but now entering Kantou South sector
Yama san, please call our manager and former chief.
Hi-jack?
your voice is too loud
We have that aircraft in tokai area
It is diverting to haneda..
The aircraft is off course and we cannot contact the aircraft,
isn't that just a coicidence ?
We can't defintely say it is. but ..
We have three aircraft having the same problem and chances of incidence would very low.
What should we do ?
Can you contact The ATM ?
If this is real hi-jack, we have to tell ATM and cease operation in the sky.
fool.
Don't say that,it would be a disaster if japan's airspace have something like that happened.
America have hi-jack incident before ,right ?
What if the information is faulty ?
What if the information is ture ?
We have identify those 3 aircrafts and it seems there is something following behind the traffic
What is happening  ?
We are stilling searching for the cause
We will tell you when we know it.
ok.
are you very certain with such information ?
Yes.
Chief, let's discuss with ATM
We can't get connection without you.
I understand your situation, but we cannot make the deicision for you.
As mentioned, we cannot just close down the airspace
What happened ?
Japan central have just descended and heading towards sendai.
Which flight was that ?
776.
Your daughter is returning ,right ?
Yes. it is JCL776
I will contact Sendai for emergency landing.
Yuki
There is a/c that we cannot contact
We will divert it to sendai airport
Is it about malfunction ..
no.
Do you think the pilot wll risk their life to just let the plane down ?
Yama san, can you please confirm whether are there other aircraft that cannot be contact ?
Understood.
We have contacted the sendai and they have visual contact with the aircraft
Please inform other a/c about the aircraft that have lost radio commnuications
This is tokyo control area control centre
Please tell us the situtation.
This is sendai airport.
Japan central have in their finali landing position.
The aircraft is not landing, it just lift off again.
Please make the decision or else, it would be a disaster
This is sendai airpor.t
There is something following the a.c
We don't think it is a military aircraft, please let us know if you know what is it .
What do you mean there are a/c
What is happening now ?
I do not know.
Can we handoffthis aircraft ?
Understood.
Sky-Y 587,  Reduce  speed to 270 for arrival spacing.
The aircraft is climbing
This is tokyo control area center
If there are situation  like JCL happening in other airports will be dangerous.
Please consider about the safety of the sky
We cannot do a lot of things in this kind of situation
Who would take the responsibility when the airspace is closed due to faulty decision ?
I understand
neverthless, our job it to ensure air safety, right ?
We cannot make the deicision, that is why we are calling you to help.
Yuki..
This is former manager, Tanabe.
Can you please make the decision as soon as possible ?
I would confirm with the prime minister,
Please give us some time.
Why can;t they just make the decision ?
what we can do Is to wait.
For safety reaons, we shall change shifts as usual.
Please be quick
734,  d/m Fl 290
It seems to be fine.
I will return asap, can you take my place for a while ?
Sure
Yuki san,
mika.
Don't tell others about my daugter.
Just follow up other's flight.
Pandora 884,  c/m FL 320
Should we call rainbow ?
If it is a hi-jack, its better that we do not contact the a/c
Understood.
We will handle it.
Yuki, I am counting on you.
Understood.
Everyone, listen up.
There is a high possibility that aircraft in tokyo control area has been hi-jacked
There is a restriction effective from now that no aircraft can be on the air
Please land all airborne aircraft in the nearest airport
To reduce error, we will adopt double approach.
Act now.
All station,  This is Tokyo control
Due to Extraordinary Circumstances
The Japan Goverment issued an order at 0520z
to shut down all civil aviation operations in japan
ALL IFR aircrafts are  requested to follow instructions from respected ATC units
ALL VFR aircrafts are requested to land  at neartest and suitable aredrome.
As soon as possible.
And Terminate your flights.
Maki, please change with Yamada.
It may be difficult for him in this situation.
Please also let shimuro to follow up.
I will confirm with rainbow's airline.
Yuki
I have confirmed that only RAA203, ATS808,JCL776 that lost communication with ATC
Thank you.
PLease be on double approach in Kantou south sector.
Yuki san,
Are you ok
We have a serious situation,
can you lend me your help.
Royal start 101, fly heading 240 for vector to kansai airport, standby further clerance.
Jetway 29,  fly heading 100 for vector to sendai airport
descend to FL210 within 4 mins
J-sky 272, we would like to go to Fukuoka.
J-sky 272, there is an order to ceased air operation, you must land in nearest airport
PLease follow our intructions and land in Itami
J-sky 272 roger
nippon x 1003, Descend to reach FL 160 by saeki
Orionwings 35, fly heading 090 for vector to kansai airport
What happened ?
Atlantis has just moved.
really
It is directing to Kansai airport
isn't it being hi-jack
That is strange.
I will confirm with other sectors
Are we going to land all aircrafts ?
This Kanto south sector
We have 4 emergency a/c here
Yamada kun Let me take it from here
This is the orders from Yuki
Yamada, Let Maki take over
Mamado 20,  d/m 5000
standby approach clerance
Please let me continue to control.
Rainbow is descending and reducing speed, seems to be heading towards haneda.
it is not much time left, let me go.
I understand your feelings, but this is an emergency situation
Maki...
Double approach is something important
I want to protect the aircraft with my hands
Please let me do it until the end
Yamada kun
Let him do it.
He have passed the exam
he should know that he have the repsonsibility
ok.
stay here
becareful for rainbow.
I am counting on you.