This is for language exchange,please delete in 24 hours, I will not be responsible for any unlawful actions.
English Translation: IssacTang  QC: Franeux Provider:Peter
Do you know there are rules when flying in the skies ?
Where every you go in the world, there must be a "high way"
In aviation, we call them airways, analogous to highways in lamen terms
All aircraft in japan fly from and to this predefined route- airways to ensure safety
TO maintain proper separation during takeoff, landing and enroute,
Air traffic controllers are there to instruct pilots on hdg, speed and alt to ensure safety.
for example a plane flying from fukoka to haneda
First the pilot contacts the atc and the aerodrome controller give clerance from ground movements to airborne
From aerdrome control, the a/c is pass to terminal control
then from terminal control is passed to the 4 major Area Control Centre
The ACC are radar facilities that track the flight from the flight plan route and guide them to their destination
Green is fukuoka area, and blue is tokyo control area
The plan flies with the predefined route and contact fukuoka control then tokyo control
After entering to tokyo control and sequenced by ATC,
The plane is then transfer to the terminal control of haneda for landing
Air traffic controller utilised radar to communicate and instruct pilots  is called Air Traffic Controlling.
In the world, Air traffic Control has a variety of complex rules and system
Because of These sets of rules and Air traffic controllers strive to separate traffic made flying in the air safe
DO you understand what does this map tells you ?
There are rules up in the sky
ATC retrieve information from the radar scope and
Give precise instruction to pilots to prevent collision
The numbers, characters on the screen are information of planes flying in the sky
ANA448 is the callsign reading Allnippon
climing from 4500ft to FL 190
An aircraft type of A320 and going to RJOO- Osakaitami
See, how tremondous amount of a/c in japan
ATC maintain a safe separation between a/c with high effecicecy to bring a/c from A point to B.
There is no report from other sector
There is no visual contact with the missle?
We received reports that the military practice is conducted in russia
They have failed to launch a missel and reported that it may accidently enter japan airspace
Where is the estimated location ?
It will be located 300 km east of sendai area
Are you kidding ?
The exact position of the missle and affected planes are not yet known
Please contact ATM and keep them inform about any news
It's really difficult.
we are not sure if russia gave us the correct information
I think Russia isn't a country that holds secret military activities
And even so, I do not think they would report such incident to us
Even so. we still cannot identify the location of the missel and affected planes
I hope there is no planes that are shot down by the missle
What could we do
We have no control on navy force, thus we vritually have nothing to do
Everyone, please pay attention, there is a missle in the air of japan area
Please collect any valuable information from pilots and of any source
EP02
what  ever happends, it is our repsonsibility form now on
I am not very good at encountering conflicts
Whatever happends, it is not our fault, it would be the fault of russia.
you really can be that calm ?
even we get panic, the situation will not change, right ?
Is there any visual contact with the missel report from the pilots ?
no.
Its time, let's shift
Can you let me continue ?
No, stand back and observe
ANA10, reduce speed 270 knots for spacing
There is an air force a/c released from hyakuri air base
I really do not want them to fly around.
As it is the peak hours
Maki san, There was a american flight has visual contact with the missle
And also Asia85 have radar contact ( in TCAS)
How high ?
at 32000ft
PLease adivse the crew about missle
Asian85, if you read me contact Tokyo Control
I will help on the another side, you guys concentrate here on alerting crew
thank you
Asian 85, Tokyo control, how do you read ?
I have received pilots report missle at 32000ft near kibaki prefecture.
But asian 85 has lost radio communication.
He is flying near that area ?
if you know its, that area, why not close that area and vect a/c away from that area ?
If we move now its dangerous
The missle is moving within IFR( intrsument flying rules) flight level,
And have no other space to move a/c to
It is also not a precise piece of information
If it is a there is real a missle? what will you do ?
We shall take actions accordinly
What if we do something wrong and caused more trouble?
We react different when there is a real thing, we should not do extra things at this point
Are you trying to say pilots mislook the flying object ?
I can't say the pilots are wrong
but we have a military a/c flying in hyakuri
Whatever happends, It is my responsibility
In order to let my orders come alive..
yes.
understood
we have received information that the missle has landed safely in the pacific ocean 267km from originated area
The missle isn't landed on its planned location ?
It was a failure
we have radio contact with asian85
we found out, that was the transponder malfunction
Don't think you are hero, just follow the rules.
but what are russia are thinking
why would they send as information
the world of politics is really scary
Yamada No, you are going make traffic to collide with Allnippon, right ?
JAL579, fly heading 190 for arrival spacing.
Dad!
ah
Thanks for picking me up
cheer for the hard work
Makoto, I might be away for a time
please take care of mom
what time is the flight
I will track your flight from here
I will be going
contact me we you arrive
bye bye, dad
cheers for the hardwork
what happened ?
nothing.
He seems to be causing a lot of troubles
I have warned him but he still.
Good thing, that the news told us the missle was landed safely
I really hope that does not interfer us anymore
see you
where are in a hurry
I would like to prepare for the information
you have a trainee workshop today, right
what time was it ?
roger
cheers for hard work
it would be great , if he would at least say hi
he wasn't  like that before
really?
I am really dead tired after 16 hours of work
Asa san, sorry,
I was being criticised by my cousins
Can you stop mocking around, we just finished briefing
and are very tired
did you saw de coupuli ?
Yes.
joking
my figures in auction worth 50,000,
I wish the seller would be me
Watasan , good morning,
I am sorry for disturbing your morning
I hope you won't be here as it would be quiter in this room
You are right.
did you prepared the gift ?
yea..
what is it ?
Hellin's sain ???
There should be only a few knowing what is that
It is a famous model
Hey voice is too loud and annoying
I ask watasan to help me get this.
Yama San, I am very sorry
Nakajima, please make him shutdown
If this happends, it would be a very dangerous situation
Remember this metar ( weather information) is important
Despite of all the training, we may commit mistakes.
To prevent tragic, we have reproduce a movie about the control screen with voice recording in the past incident
In 1998, 6.1 event we have reproduced a film for you to prevent same mistake happen again
The speed you are now is ok but at this altitude, it s dangerous
Skywhy airlines 364,fly heading 170 immediately due to emergency traffic
Why is the traffic not responding.
sykwhy airlines 364
Maki san, I have something to talk to you
Not you.
It is something serious
A propose ?
No, stop that please, its disgusting.
Not today
Yamda kun ?
You did not heard about it ?
He have heard a lot from oversea
it was his first time to hear bout tokyo control's recording
He was good in overseas controlling, but no in tokyo control ?
Both controlling are similar but he said it better to follow maki san
Now they are resting at the breifing room
If you have any new information, please let me know
ok.
Tokyo control , good morning star point 929, maintain FL380, direct HKC ( kagoshima)
Time for lunch ?
Shut up, you are too noisy
He found himself a game about finding virtual girilfriend ?
Do you know what you call that kind of person ?
ofcourse, I don't know ..
??
Nevermind..
I was the worse person ever.
are you willing to be my girlfriend ?
She does not have a boyfriend
really, but I won't be your GF
really
Please
Hot coffe
I said iced coffee
Hot , Please
ice
hot
Here are you
It is really delicious.
Makisan, can you take over, I want to go to toilet
There are times that we have nothing to do
Is there times to be busy ?
I hope so
um
What ?
nothing,
What are you asking about?
where were you 18 years ago ?
It should be study time, it should be easy to concentrate when there is less planes
yes.
What happended ?
Here
What ?
18 years ago, I was here
Thank you.
Tokyo Control ANA 8426, maintain FL380, direct HKC-Kagoshima
Yamada,What are you doing ?
Yamada kun ?
Yes ?
traffic
ANA8426, Tokyo Control Roger, Maintain Fl380, good morning
What are you doing ? concentrate here!
Good morning.
I was very tired
Stop mocking around.
Its great to have you as my boss sometimes
That's why I said I will not take holiday
I have morning cofee for you
Where is it from ?
Hawaii cofee, its really great
Here is a list of shops that you can find the cofee beans
If you want more , just ask me
What do you think ?
He should quit as a civil servant and open a coffee shop, right ?
yea, he pay more effort in cofee than air traffic controlling.
He seems went to columbia last year
why did he came here to work ?
working full duty will drastically make me look older
So angry..
What happended?
my wrinkles increased due to long hours of working
Maki San, are you available tonight?
I am NOT avaiable
You made he get mad
That's adorable
i think you can get marry with her
Good morning.
Thanks for OJT with me today
Cheers for hard work
its great to have early leave
Ota san don't even greet you , neither want to build friendly relationship with other
he wasn't like that before
but he changed at some point in the past
Let me treat you a meal,
Its ok , no need to treat me a meal
What are you talking about..
Excuse me
What ?
YOu are the mentor of my next OJT , right ?
So what ?
I was thinking if you can tell me something to be cautions about before controlling,
do you have time before the breifing ?
Do you mean to begin class earlier ?
I do not want to cause more troubles
I was always scould so I wanted to study more
and I want to be graduated to be an independent air traffic controller
I do not teach that way
I won't be there until the OJT starts
YOu know what ?
yes ?
um.. Let's talk about that later.
cheers for hard work
She won't give you time before class
she did not gave time to me when i was a trainee
she said it is a waste of time.
really ?
It was better to say things clearly and precisely
really
she is a strong women.
she is really cool
I will tell maki san about the mocking
if you don't treat us breakfast
that is not really good
let's go for breakfast.
I will tell you what I know about controlling.
As you also that the suicidal rate of ATC in overseas country are very high
I shall conduct this research on stress within this 2 days
I don't think its is necessary
Aside from stress at work that contribute to concentration, there is no need for the research
but various of sources of stress can accumulate
As a supervisor, I am just trying to give more care to my subordinates
Is Yamada, he is acting strange
he is just tired
how about the meal ?
How about coming to my place
I don't think it is a good idea
personal stress ?
There isn't a job without stress
Let's make vertical separation
Let's change position
Japan centra 1553,Fly hedaing 100 for arrival spacing, break break
Asian 219, descend and maintain Fl 250
break break; japan cargo 77, turn left heading 080 and reduce speed to 270 knots
This is brilliant
so, I will change shifts from here
There is turblance near haneda
TOkyo contorl atlanta 645 maintian FL 370
TOkyo control Japan 316 request descend
atlanta 645, rgr maintain FL 370
Japanair 316, say again your request
Japan 316, descend and maintain FL 230
You can locate the traffic
It just a coincidence
I have been watching the traffic before I switch position
Starjapan 6283, c/m FL 180
orion 25 rgr, descend and maintain Fl 230
Tokyo control orion 25, say again, please ?
orion 25 ,roger, d/m FL 230
Wasn't my message transmitted ?
Orion 25, d/m FL 230 ? ( with hesitation)
Affirm, that is correct, good day
good day
You just laughed, didn't you ?
is my english that bad ?
its not just the pronunciation
What should I do ?
I am being laughed all the times.
TOkyo control pacific 433, mainta Fl 350
Pacific 433, roger, maintain FL 370
No....
Information about Visiting the Tokyo control area centre
This is from TOkyo control area centre, I would like to discuss about the visitation next month
Can youprint the information there?
Tokyo control headquaters
yes,
understood
ATM reported that at time  at time 0000, 116 and 121 airspace is close
trainig ?
May be
I shall inform others
Excuse me, I have an coordination annoucement
is there planes in 116 ,112 area ?
There isn't
There isn't here either
understood
what is happening ? there are a/c disappearing
Someone please check
What is it ?
The radar scope is acting strange,
planes from the east side is disappearing
I will check
Yogamoto san, please come to the control room
contact ATM and see if there are trouble in other dvision
what is the status
It is getting worse
almost half of the target are disappearing from the radar screen
what is the cause ?
I wonder.
Approach area also don't have contact with the target.
Please use non-radar procedure to cope with the remaining traffic
What happend ?
OJT may have to stop here
should i find someone to replace ?
look for kinoshita kun
ok
yamada kun, don't worry, cope with this in a calm way
yes
ATM reported traffics from East side of Kanto A sector has the same siutaiton
Now, the whole sector disappear, someone come to double approach ?
I will do it
what happen
we have traffic disappearing from the radar scope, please help to find the solution or the cause
narita approach has reported the same situation in their radar scope
undrestood.
The traffic are disappear
change with yamada kun
please let me do it
you cannot do non-radar procedure yet
wait
let's think it calmly
Please,    let me do it.
I don't want to cause any more torubles
I wanted to be an independent ATC
I shall approve yamada do handle it
hey, wait, it is a radar malfunction,
it is not something a trainee can cope with
I am the person in charge today
I shall hold the final decision
Ymanishita, please monitor him
yes
What would you do if in case of accident ?
I won't let anyone to escape from harsh decision
plus he insist to do it
If there is trouble and you pull him off, a trainee will never grow and learn
If there is problem I will follow up and take over, don't worry
Its you are the one who asked for it, don't cause any troubles.
Did you remember the traffic you had before ?
ANA624, d/m FL 230
There only way to separate traffic is do by vertical sepration
We shall take control of S and W of kanto as much as possible
We have confirmed the systems are normal,
um, so what is the cause ?
try to intruct PDA82, to approach MJE  (miyakejima )
roger
The traffic regain
The traffic reappear in the east side of MJE
Yuki san, please check with ATM and see if there are american military aircraft in our airspace
It may be an a/c that interfer with radio signal that identify  other ac on the sky
The training area was closed just while ago, right ?
It is near the lakefront and it is the only way to maintain our service
understood
Yamada, just hang to it for a little while, we are almost there
BinAir1965, reduce speed 310 for spacing
ANA31 reduce speed 270 for spacing
maki, bingo they are using ES-6 flying in that area
We have also reported the problem of radio wave interference
understood
Traffic is back online
trippleA 575 is in coasting mode
Tripple A 575, how do you read ?
they may be experincing a wake turbulance
bliss air 63, reduce speed 260 knots for spacing
The pilot is non-repsonsive ?
There should be some sort of trouble on board
Yamada kun, calm down,
Look at the surround a/c
Tripple A 575, how do you read ?
Please respond
Tokyo control triple A 575
Great, that nothing happened
Sorry for calling you
It is our job
we are going back
It seems that they forget to turn off the system which causes interference to the radio signal
Its really impossible, I don't really know what they are thinking, I want to punch them
compensation is a must
Just make sure this does not happen again
Looks like someone replaced my spot
Nowadays, wodays are stronger than before
she is always angry anyway
cheers for hard work
i heard that you are conducting outside classroom lesson ?
Not me
I was thinking that everyone are nice
Don't put me into the topic
Don't push it too hard for yamada
But bring sharpen his skills
No, I think experience is important to grow
yes, but
You have meeting ?
going by car ?
No, I will going by syagen kai ?
You can go by train, right ?
I don't like to travel alone ?
I will go now
I am busy
Still, she is cute
How could you say that  ? she just turn down you !?
I just can't stand by looking at her like that
you reall strange
right, nakajima
Its really tiring, when it really happends in real life
yes
Thank you
you really did a real great job,
usually as a trianee would need to request a position of relief
maki is also great
Why would you want to be an ATC
I like aeroplanes and want to try
but i am always a coward
How about you ?
is it not a very question ?
it is because my dad was an ATC
but he died when I was in primary school
What I like is to use the airband from my dad
Everday afterschool, I use the the airband to listen ATC transmission while looking at the sky
It is like I am talking with my dad and i would also like to say sorry to him
apologise
I always thing only old, boring people would do such jobs
My dad was a great ATC in
Tokyo control
My family was torn apart because of this job
I regret and want to apologise for not respecting his job
The last time i saw him is when I was sending him off from tokyo control departing tokyo
I remember this scene everyday, which reminds me the precious memories of my dad
I am sorry for talking such heavy emotions
its ok
I am now in the path my dad went through
My mom did rejected the idea of me being an ATC
Rejected ?
There are a lot of reasons..
But I show her that I am capable
After sometime, she said it is a great job
Enroute seems to be an unimportant job
But because we are part of the team to ensure safety of the sky, I think its imporant
So , when the time you quit isn't it a waste ?
I am sorry
it should be me.
I shall be a be a great ATC , for the sake of my mom or dad
maki San
Did you heard everything from here ?
What about ?
I did not heard anything.
are you talking bad things behind me ?
because matsumoto is acting strange
here, its for you
Thank you
Maki San
Its great to see you avaiable
what are  you doing
chatting
You are really annoying
Shall we have dinner ?
yes
I don't want to go with two men
Why are you so harsh ?
you are the one .
Maki, come, I will give you a ride
No need
no need ?
I am going back to sleep
Bye
See you
Yamada kun, shall we start outside class lesson
can I also join?
yes
leave it to me
can I call shikihjima ?
I think he should also join
yes.
I do not allow mistakes, is that o k?
yes
Let's go
The birthplace of Japanese Aviation, have you ever been to Tokorozawa?
Tokyo Area Control Centre, also known as “Tokyo Control”
In here, the safety of the sky of Japan, 365 days, 24 hours, without intermission
and give precise instruction to aircraft to ensure air safety
The city where Tokyo Control is located is Tokorozawa City in Saitama Prefecture
where it is said to be the birthplace of Japanese Aviation.
We met an ex-ANA pilot Mr. Masao Yokoyama here in Tokorozawa.
Rode on Mitsubishi A6M Zero during war time, then as a pilot of civil aircraft,
Mr. Yokohama entered ANA. He was flying the only airliner that Japanese manufacturer YS-11
There is not many people are still alive to talk about the history of japan
I miss the feeling, and I want to touch it (The Airplane). It is still my lover;
I can only say it like that now though.
We asked him about what is the most difficult work to do when he was a pilot.
Back to the days, in the past, people are mostly travellers around the world
There were different kinds of food avaiable in the flight services
The airconditioning system also improved at the time.
And then we talked about the time when he started his Air Traffic Control career.
The content of the lessons…
It is so hard to talk about it…
After the establishment of Air traffic control
Aeroplane
Passengers have gain confidence in air safety
as there is rule in the skies, which make flying more safer.
Flight rules
Safe